to the
al
to the e
al e
[Music]
[Música]
I promise to bring you breakfast every
prometo llevarte el desayuno cada
Tomorrow I will promise that my life begins
mañana prometeré que mi vida empieza
where you
donde tú
you just don't want false expectations or
acabas no quiero falsas expectativas ni
live within a lie of yours and
vivir dentro de una mentira lo tuyo y
mine is true despite what
mío es verdadero a pesar de lo que
say I will remember that I walk through that
diga recordaré a que yo paseo por esa
square that we could not shamefully
plaza que con vergüenza no nos podíamos
Neither
Ni
look the moment came and I took your hand
mirar llegó el momento y cogí tu mano
as we continued walking to the 12
mientras seguíamos caminando para los 12
remained silent in The Great
quedó en silencio en La gran
City City City City
Ciudad Ciudad Ciudad Ciudad
City, why do I want Villar?
Ciudad para que quiero Villar
the star in the sky If by my side
la estrella en el cielo Si a mi lado
I have the most beautiful of
tengo la más bella de
firmament I don't know if you will understand me, that's what
firmamento no sé si me entenderás es lo
that you
que te
a story that will make your heart feel like
cuento que sentirá el corazón como
smile
sonríe
By
Por
to
a
[Music]
[Música]
with which I feel that every day
con que me que cada día Al
wake up that if I argue it is for
despertar que si discuto es para
know you
conocerte
but there is no fog that can darken
más no hay nieblas que pueda oscurecer
this
este
[Music]
[Música]
love it
amor lo
I know that we will go through moments that are not
sé que pasaremos por momentos que no
We imagine that the pain will be so strong
imaginamos que el dolor será tan fuerte
that we will think about
que pensaremos en
leave us but this feeling of ours
dejarnos pero este sentimiento nuestro
will put the
pondrá las
wounds that fall on the soul breathe me
heridas que le caemos al alma respirame
by
por
please because this life is for us
favor porque esta vida se nos
escape that I want to see
escapa que quiero ver
shine that I want to see shine
brillar que quiero ver brillar la
star in the sky If I have by my side
estrella en el cielo Si a mi lado tengo
the most of
la má del
firmament I don't know if you will understand me
firmamento no sé si me entenderás
feel the heart like
sentir el corazón como
smile
sonrier
I want my side
quiero mi lado
I don't know if I have
tengo no sé si me
you will understand, I'm telling you that there is something to be said.
entenderá heo queo a te cuento hay que
feel the heart as it smiles
sentir al corazón como sonr
[Music]
[Música]
What's up, gorgeous, how are we? How are we?
Qué pasa guapísimos Cómo estamos Cómo
we are
estamos
Well, I hadn't warned about this because
Eh bueno no había avisado esto porque
Honestly, I'm really lazy, okay?
sinceramente me da mucha pereza vale
This was going to be a live show that IB is going to do.
esto iba a ser un directo que IB vamos a
do in the main channel in the channel
hacer en el canal principal en el canal
main we are going to upload some videos
principal vamos a subir algunos vídeos
Okay, by the time I'm done
Okay en el momento en el que termine
This live will be released on
este directo pues se estrenará el
first and obviously then this then
primero y y evidentemente pues esto pues
It has to be this way because everything has a
tiene que ser así porque todo tiene un
limit and it's over, that is, I am a
límite y ya se acabó o sea yo soy un
man who is I think with me in
hombre que es yo creo que conmigo en
The one who gets along badly is because
internet El que se lleva mal es porque
you want to get along badly eh or so I have
se quiere llevar mal eh o sea lo he
said many times I think that people
dicho ya muchas veces creo que la gente
who follows me here knows it very well
que me sigue aquí lo sabe de sobra
eh Precisely in the last few days
eh Precisamente en los últimos días
I am organizing a fairly large project
estoy organizando un proyecto bastante
a brick that's why I didn't feel like it either
tocho que por eso no me apetecía tampoco
nothing eh having to have to talk about of
nada eh tener que tener que hablar de de
This guy, maybe it's okay, I didn't feel like it.
este tipo ot vez vale no me apetecía
nothing because we are in other things
nada porque estamos en otras cosas
We're doing powerful things, okay?
estamos haciendo cosas Eh potentes vale
You'll see what's coming, eh? During the
Ya veréis lo que se viene eh Durante las
next weeks Okay and but that's it O
próximas semanas Okay e pero ya está O
It's over now, cap. It's over now.
sea ya se acabó gorra O sea ya se acabó
because it is so that you are all the
porque es que para que tú estés todo el
[ __ ] day all [ __ ] day and we're going
[__] día todo el puñetero día y lo vamos
Let's see now talking about me. Well, that's what it's for.
a ver ahora hablando de mí Pues para eso
I'm not being an idiot doing
yo no estoy haciendo el capullo haciendo
a pact Well I'm missing out
un pacto Pues me estoy perdiendo
content and there are a lot of videos
contenido y hay un montón de vídeos
eliminated that makes me very sad
eliminados que me da un montón de pena
that are not on the internet and you
que no estén en internet y tú
taking advantage of this and that people
aprovechándose de esto y que la gente
that he is meeting you new, well no
que te está conociendo nueva pues no
know who you are then as there is
sepa quién eres tú entonces como hay
many new people who have been
mucha gente nueva a la que se le ha
forgotten Who are you then let's go
olvidado Quién eres tú pues vamos a
remind him
recordárselo
Okay, really. I mean, it gives me a lot.
vale De verdad O sea me da muchísima
laziness would have preferred not to have to
pereza hubiera preferido no tener que
that touch This is worth it But as I tell you eh
que tocar Esto vale Pero como os digo eh
everything has a limit, everything is worth it
todo tiene un límite vale todo tiene un
limit
límite
[Music]
[Música]
and but you don't have to
y pero no a a tien que
the like is free beautiful like free a
el like Es gratis guapa like gratis un
kiss you are the only one who has
beso tú eres el único que lo has
respected usually happens usually happens when
respetado suele pasar suele pasar cuando
I make pacts with people but of course
hago pactos con la gente pero claro a
see with all a kiss
ver con todo un beso
One thing is that one does not enter into
em una cosa es que uno pues no entre en
the situations Not for nothing one does not enter
las situaciones No por nada uno no entra
in the situations But because there is eh
en las situaciones Pero porque hay eh
people who die in the media AND
personas que mediáticamente mueren Y
so when they are asking you to
entonces cuando te están pidiendo a
shouts that you answer him answer me
gritos que que le respondas contéstame
not shouting because that's when you don't know it
no gritando pues es cuando no se lo
you have to give because obviously you
tienes que dar porque evidentemente te
They are asking for it because they want it But
lo están pidiendo porque lo quieren Pero
what I am not and have never been is
lo que no soy y nunca he sido es de
to remain silent with absolutely no one
quedarme callado con nadie absolutamente
with no one If I keep quiet It's because I'm
con nadie Si me callo Es porque estoy
busy with other things because I haven't
liado con otras cosas porque no lo he
seen or because I'm not interested in making you a
visto o porque no me interesa hacerte un
gift that you are with less than 10,000
regalo que estás con menos de 10,000
views on a channel of 600,000
visitas en un canal de 600,000
subscribers Okay then I'll do it
suscriptores Vale entonces e lo voy a
do it here okay I'm going to do it in
hacer aquí vale lo voy a hacer en
telesalseo yes it is true that I am going to
telesalseo sí que es verdad que voy a
upload some videos that give me a lot
subir algunos vídeos que me dan mucha
It's a shame they're deleted from the channel
pena que estén borrado en el canal
main obviously and if you want firewood
principal evidentemente y si quiere leña
Well, we continue to work hard, we are here
Pues seguimos a la leña estamos aquí
every day to the firewood as far as you
todos los días a la leña hasta donde tú
you want as far as you want, colleague
quieras hasta donde tú quiera colega
but it was already over last month for all
pero ya se acabó el mes pasado por toda
the [ __ ] face last month all over the
la [__] cara el mes pasado por toda la
[ __ ] face he made a direct that he
[__] cara se marcó un directo que él
I was surely hoping that there was going to be
esperaba seguramente que ahí iba a
the thing exploded and that we were going to do it there
estallar la cosa y que ahí le íbamos a
answer we pass from his ass because that
contestar pasamos de su culo porque que
Honestly, I found out after two or three
sinceramente me enteré a los dos o tres
days and when I was watching some clips
días y cuando estuve viendo algunos clip
I found it pathetic. I mean, I found it
me pareció patético O sea me pareció
completely pathetic the guy with a
completamente patético el tío con una
Yellow T-shirt, a vertical direct
camiseta Amarilla un directo en vertical
who is still on the subject of the
que está todavía con el tema de los
vertical to falsify visits is worth it
verticales para falsear las visitas vale
screaming super exploded super
gritando super estalado super
deranged man screaming at the camera
desquiciado gritando a la cámara
failed and we passed on his ass we passed on
fracasados y pasamos de su culo pasamos
from your ass okay I'm doing it
de su culo vale lo estoy haciendo
interest in gossip Because for me it's like
interes salseo Porque para mí es como a
At this point that man already has the
estas alturas ya ese hombre tiene la
impact of a Lolly Huerta of a one
repercusión de una Lolly Huerta de un un
ar of Troy of a Peppa or of with
ar de Troya de una Peppa o sea de con
This is what he collaborates with without further ado. That is to say
esto con los que colabora sin más O sea
you know and now we are going to be with you
sabes y ahora vamos a estar Nosotros con
many little things that are going to come out this week
muchas cositas que van a salir la semana
that comes and the other and have this guy in
que viene y la otra y tener este tío en
my main channel Well the truth is that
mi canal principal Pues la verdad es que
I didn't feel like it, I don't know what you think
no me apetecía no sé qué os parece a
you but what I do have
ustedes pero lo que sí que yo tengo
Of course, okay, and I think that anyone who
claro vale e y creo que cualquiera que
knows me or rather, scratching his
me conozca o sea es que rascarle las
balls to the tiger is to have desire is to have
pelotas al tigre es tener ganas es tener
you win okay I mean what need if it is
ganas vale O sea qué necesidad si está
each to his own, each to his own
cada uno a lo suyo bueno cada uno a lo
not yours he is doing mine now we are going to do it
suyo no él está a lo mío ahora lo vamos
Let's see here, okay, but what's the need?
a ver aquí vale em pero qué necesidad
uncle when you know
tío cuando se sabe
perfectly well that there is no one in the
perfectamente que no existe nadie en la
face of the earth neither on the internet nor in the
faz de la tierra ni de internet ni en la
life, whoever I am afraid of, is clear
vida a quien yo le tenga miedo claro es
that one becomes silent, one becomes silent and
que uno se va callando se va callando y
It seems that you are afraid to answer
Parece ser que te da miedo responderle a
This guy is a puppet to me.
este tipo y es un monigote para mí me
you understand then of course no longer I know
entiendes Entonces Claro ya no Ya se
finished Okay I'm going to put you a little in
acabó Vale Voy a poneros un poco en
context Okay when we finish the
contexto Vale cuando terminemos el
The first video will be uploaded live. And if
directo se subirá el primer vídeo Y si
keep going, more things will be uploaded, okay because
sigue se subirán más cositas vale porque
I have a lot of little things that, well,
tengo un montón de cositas que Eh bueno
Let's see, I expected no, no.
a ver yo me esperaba que no que no
we had to resort to this but you
tuviéramos que recurrir a esto pero te
She is envious and very bad, she is very bad
tiene envidia y muy mala es muy mala
person for me is a very bad person to
persona para mí es muy mala persona para
He envies me. Well, obviously.
mí me tiene envidia Bueno evidentemente
You already know the topic of inspiration that
ya sabéis el tema de la inspiración que
I had with me no Well then you will
tenía conmigo no Bueno luego os lo
I will remember okay then I will remind you in
recordaré vale luego os lo recordaré en
game over
el game over
new but this live more than anything goes
nuevo pero este directo más que nada va
to be eh
a ser eh
to put people in a bit of mood
para poner un poco a la gente en
context so I don't have to put up with it
contexto para no tener yo que aguantar
in the next few days
en los próximos días
a that Why a Why not why is it
un que Por qué un Por qué no por qué se
does this why now this no he does not you
hace esto por qué ahora esto no él no te
has said nothing because he will have the few
ha dicho nada no porque tendrá las pocas
followers who are left saying
seguidoras que le queden diciendo
still what is it that he doesn't say anything or that
todavía que es que él no dice nada o que
he hasn't done anything Or that we are
él no ha hecho nada O que lo estamos
attacking for free no no no look to
atacando de gratis no no no mira para
Let's start by putting a little bit in
empezar vamos a poner un poco en
context okay I think I'll give you 24
contexto vale Yo creo que te doy 24
hours I think we should start a
horas yo creo que deberíamos empezar un
little reminiscent of the agreement that was reached
poco recordando eh al acuerdo al que se
It arrived okay And you tell me what sense
llegó vale Y ustedes me decí qué sentido
I have to accept this, eh, you guys?
tiene que yo aceptase esto eh ustedes me
You say I want you to tell me
decís yo quiero que ustedes me digáis
What's the point of Jav Oliveira?
qué sentido tiene que jav oliveira
accept this [ __ ] [ __ ] and agree
aceptase esta [__] [__] de acuerdo y
is not yet respected and is not yet
todavía no se respete y todavía no se
respect But
respete Pero
no no I don't like Going Back in Time but the
no no me gusta Volver al pasado pero los
there are those who do not learn from the person who is shrunken
hay que no aprenden persona encogida de
shoulders Here I am I didn't want myself
hombros Aquí estoy yo no me quería
find Well here I am if one
encontrar Pues aquí estoy yoo si una
peseta gave each
peseta dier cada
Spanish but not to me where they have to
español pero no a m a donde tienen que
Javi Ignore the middays
Javi No hagas caso a medios días
having whole days for God's sake a kiss
habiendo días enteros por Dios un beso
zor Well zor you will pass by here
zor Bueno zor tú ya pasarás por aquí a
tell us about yours what happened to you this
contarnos lo tuyo lo que te pasó este
It was this horrible live that he did
fue el directo este horrible que hizo
insulting me, insulting my family
insultándome insultando a mi familia
Okay, with Amador threatening me, okay, with
vale con Amador amenazándome vale con
Amador threatening me that I put one on him
Amador amenazándome que le puse una
They couldn't notify the complaint in the end.
denuncia no la pudieron notificar en fin
You will give him a gift of good ham
le darás para el jamón de regalo bueno
Eh, I know I'm going to give it a shout.
Eh Yo sé que le voy a dar repercusión
With this I am going to give it notoriety
con esto que le voy a dar notoriedad
Okay, but I'm not going to keep quiet or
vale eh pero es que no me voy a callar o
I am answering you one by one.
sea le estoy contestando a una a una
Peppa I'm answering a Loli me
Peppa le estoy contestando a una Loli me
It doesn't matter to answer this one, I don't think so.
da lo mismo contestarle a este no creo
that I'm going to win a lot either
que vaya a ganar mucho tampoco me
you understand but man it is that it is
entiendes pero hombre es que está
Taking advantage of the videos
Aprovechando que están los vídeos
erased to continue lying and to
borrados para seguir mintiendo y para
lying is worth it, you listen and see everything
mentir vale ustedes escuchar y ver todo
This is worth it. This won't even be all of them.
esto vale Esto ni siquiera será todas
the times he has mentioned me and that I
las veces que me ha mencionado y que me
has been throwing [ __ ] for 2 years
ha estado tirando [__] durante 2 años
2 years two years the colleague made that my
2 años dos años el colega hecho que mi
next Antonia my next Joan flat
próxima Antonia mi próximo Joan plana
You are all the same. What do I give you? Do you like it?
todos sois iguales Qué os doy os gusta
I'll send you some samples of my perfume or something.
mi perfume os mando unas muestras o algo
This was the live one, worth watching this one
este fue el directo vale mirar este
direct and explain to me how I passed
directo y explicarme ustedes cómo pasé
I for this hoop and I think I am very
yo por este aro y creo que soy muy
generous 24 hours for you to delete the
generoso 24 horas para que borres los
videos you have from my channel on your
vídeos que tienes de mi canal en tu
channel a threat eh of try or in your
canal una amenaza eh de try o en tus
24-hour channels if not Iran strikes
canales 24 horas si no que Irán strikes
I'm going to delete the videos directly.
directamente yo voy a borrar los vídeos
that I have from your channel that we share
que tenga de tu canal que compartimos
a time when we both worked together
una época que trabajamos los dos juntos
It is worth a time that we work one
vale una época que trabajamos una
threat of strike here colleague two
amenaza de strike aquí el colega dos
together and I gave him permission to go up
juntos y yo le daba permiso para subir
my videos what happened that no
mis vídeos qué ha pasado que no
only has
solamente ha
uploaded but not to me where they have to
subido pero no a mí a donde tienen que
Your answering him is a gift for him
que tú le contestes es un regalo para él
He's looking for you every day and now
anda buscándote todos los días y ahora
attacks everything around you every day
ataca a todo tu alrededor todos los días
many handsome pesos every day when
muchos pesos guapo todos los días cuando
I gave him permission but he has uploaded them
le di permiso sino que los ha subido
when I was no longer talking to him and he continues
cuando ya no me hablaba con él y sigue
uploading it I give you 24 hours to
subiéndolo te doy 24 horas para que
Check out the videos that appeared on my channel
voles los vídeos surgidos en mi canal
because I take away the permission you had and
porque te quito el permiso que tenías y
If you keep it on your channel you
si lo sigues mantenendo en tu canal te
I put a strike there is nothing worse
pongo un strike no hay nada de ser peor
real youtuber So the topic of
youtuber de verdad O sea que el tema de
the strikes I mean you have no arguments eh
los strike O sea no tienes argumentos eh
you look bad, you make a fool of yourself
quedas mal se te pone quedas en ridículo
And then I put you
Y entonces te pongo
strike the censorship is going to be that no eh
strike la censura va a ser que no eh
but I don't have the caps at the end
pero no a m a tien al final el gorras
gets what he wants his channel is
consigue lo que quiere su canal está
dead and you're going to revive him, face of
muerto y se lo vas a revivir cara de
nausea I don't think I don't think I'll revive but
náuseas No creo no creo que reviva pero
If we act like this, let's not talk about it.
es que si nos ponemos así no hablemos de
LOL and let's not talk about Peppa and all this
LOL y no hablemos de Peppa y to esta
people who are on the same level as me
gente que está Al mismo nivel por mis
eggs and be careful because you have
huevos y ten cuidado porque tienes
videos from my three channels, that is, this one
vídeos de mis tres canales o sea este
uncle talks about everyone on his channel
tío habla de todo el mundo en su canal
Whoever he wants to mess with is fine.
de quien le da la gana vale se mete con
everyone insults whoever gives them the
todo el mundo insulta a quien le da la
win but be careful not to put it that
gana pero ten cuidado no lo pongas que
the one who closes your channels closes you
te cierra la que te cierra los canales
that closes your channels eh and you and you
que te cierra los canales eh y te y te
leaves very hard work out of work
deja sin trabajo trabajo muy arduo por
I'm here 24 hours if you don't delete the videos
estoy 24 horas Si no borras los vídeos
From my live shows I'm going to delete the ones that
de mis directos yo voy a borrar los que
have
tenga
suddenly where
tunto dónde
elero give it a go with the Chair flight Finally it is
elero dale con la Silla vuelo Por fin se
the lukewarmness ended the other day I got into
acabó la tibieza el otro día me metí a
see a live show of the incredible thing that happened
ver un directo del increíble que lo haya
left so long but you should
dejado tanto tiempo pero deberías
Do it in a salseria and we'll give you more.
hacerlo en salseria ya te damos más
members a kiss [ __ ] don't bite the
miembros un beso cabrón no piques a las
Ladies, you get three strikes.
señoras te caen los strikes tres strikes
You know they are C del Canal Ponte works
sabes que son C del Canal trabaja Ponte
to work, or rather, imagine, eh, a
a trabajar o sea imaginaros eh una
full-blown threat to close the
amenaza en toda regla con cerrar los
channels fraudulently of course I
canales de manera fraudulenta claro Yo
I don't know if he will be able to read very well or not.
no sé si él sabrá leer muy bien o no
will be able to read very well I don't know what course
sabrá leer muy bien No sé a qué curso
But he arrived
llegó Pero
Hey, YouTube's rules say it clearly.
eh las normas de YouTube lo dicen claro
and they speak clearly, use leg, do you understand, don't you?
y hablan claro uso leg entiendes tú no
you can threaten the first thing you can't
puedes amenazar lo primero que no puedes
To do is to threaten, that is the first thing
hacer es amenazar eso es lo primerísimo
Come on people, let's get the challenge, a kiss
vamos gente a conseguir el reto un beso
Pilar, gorgeous, the first thing you can't do is
Pilar guapísima lo primero que no puedes
to do is threaten people because
hacer es amenazar a la gente porque
because they shut you up because they
porque te callan la boca porque te
They expose not the first thing that the first thing that
exponen no lo primero que lo primero que
you can't do that second that use
no puedes hacer eso segundo que el uso
legitimate use is worth what you
legítimo vale el uso legítimo lo que te
is saying that you can use
está diciendo son que tú puedes utilizar
third-party content to give weight and
contenido de tercero para dar peso y
demonstrate illustrate
demostrar ilustrar
I don't know why you gave him a chance
no sé para qué le diste una oportunidad
Even if the monkey dresses in silk, the monkey will be
Aunque la mona se vista de seda mona se
You're going to freak out, but this is what
queda Vais a flipar pero es que esto que
I'm not even going to show you everything because
os voy a mostrar ni siquiera todo porque
I don't know what content this guy uploads.
yo este tío no sé el contenido que sube
I don't know what he does, I don't know anything.
No sé lo que hace no sé nada es
currently a Random literally with
actualmente un Random literalmente con
a thousand spectators some days
mil espectadores algunos días
Ok, but you have 24 hours to
vale pero es que 24 horas tienes para
delete how I ate this, dude
borrar los cómo me he comido Yo esto tío
direct from my channel that uploaded to your
directos de mi canal que subidos a tus
channels okay I mean the
canales vale me refiero a las
collaborations that at no time a
colaboraciones que en ningún momento una
collaboration means a contract of
colaboración significa un contrato de
work is over, good job is over
trabajo acabó el de buenas se acabó el
look the other way you have 24 hours
mirar para otro lado tienes 24 horas
to delete the live streams from my channel O
para borrar los directos de mi canal O
be this guy puts on his channel what
sea el tío este pone en su canal lo que
He doesn't want us to be what we are
le da la gana de ni que fuéramos lo que
Tele5 gives him the desire to do what he wants
le da la gana de tele5 lo que le da la
earn from the agencies you uploaded
gana de las agencias que tú subiste
Because at first they allowed you to
Porque al principio te los permitían
but 24 hours also on Twitch already makes me
pero 24 horas también en Twitch ya me
to search for a living, of course, this is one thing
rebuscar la vida claro esto es una cosa
under which it is allowed to you And this is a
bajo que te la permitido Y esto es una
something you have been threatening with
cosa con la que tú has ido amenazando
Twitter accounts also with
las cuentas de Twitter también con
close it and all that stuff that now
cerrarla y todo el rollo ese que ahora
We will also talk about your thing with the
también hablaremos de tu rollo con las
Twitter accounts but but it's over now
cuentas de Twitter pero pero ya se acabó
That is, you are not going to threaten anyone else anymore.
o sea ya no vas a amenazar a más nadie a
Anyone you click on, I'll go
cualquiera que le tires un click lo voy
to teach to
a enseñar a
peel it please express yourself in another way
pelarlo por favor exprésate de otra
way what you have of him and that he gets involved
manera lo que tengas de é y que se meta
the finger on it is erased Sister but if
el dedo en él está borrado Sor pero si
The worst thing is that it is erased.
es que lo peor es que está borrado se
reached an agreement after this
llegó a un acuerdo después de este
direct in which he insulted and got into
directo en el que insultó se metió con
My wife got involved now. You'll see.
mi mujer se metió ahora lo Vais a ver
anything goes an agreement was reached in the
todo vale se llegó a un acuerdo en el
that in which they did not mention us, they did not mention us
que en el que no nos mencionaban no nos
I gave him a strike, I think it was
yo le metí a él un strike creo que fue
When this started he put another one on me
cuando empezó esto él me puso otro a la
week or so and in the end it arrived
semana o por ahí no y al final se llegó
an agreement each on their own but not
un acuerdo cada uno por su lado pero no
has respected him, he is obsessed
lo ha respetado está obseso
He's obsessed with me. You'll see it here.
conmigo está obseso lo Vais a ver aquí
now in the
ahora en el
directly put you on strike or whatever in
directo ponerte strike o lo que sea en
Twitch also 24 hours on Twitch That is
Twitch también 24 horas en Twitch O sea
that the guy was going to Twitch but I don't know
que se iba a Twitch el tío pero yo no sé
that I, I, am that this thing about the
que yo yo es que de verdad esto de los
strike is one thing that he has as no
strike es una cosa que él tiene como no
as a move
como movida
e Here too, for example, he threatened to
e Aquí también por ejemplo amenazó a a
a Twitter kid is not the same
un chaval de Twitter no lo mismo
compose strike e when you are
componerle strike e cuando tú estás
making use of legitimate use to you
haciendo uso del uso legítimo a ti te
They can give you a strike and you appeal it and
pueden poner un strike y tú lo apelas y
You win it and YouTube recognizes it there
lo ganas y YouTube te lo reconoce hay
times that you even have a strike and you don't
veces que incluso tias un strike y no te
They admit it because it is legitimate use, don't you?
lo admiten porque es uso legítimo no os
I'm going to bore you here to tell you about the
voy a aburrir aquí para comentaros las
YouTube rules but what this does
normas de YouTube pero lo que hace este
man who censors Javi always has
hombre que censura Javi siempre tiene
reason a kiss
razón un beso
to Roberto Macarra Bueno among others
a a Roberto macarra bueno entre otros
okay threatened him because he uploaded a clip on
vale lo amenazó porque subió un clip en
Twitter Roberto uploaded a clip on Twitter
Twitter Roberto subió un clip en Twitter
that leaves it bad that leaves it bad because
que lo deja mal que lo deja mal porque
It is what it has done and what you are going to do
es lo que ha hecho ha sido y lo Vais a
see now You are going to see some examples
ver ahora Vais a ver algunos ejemplos
during these two years take advantage of the fact that
durante estos dos años aprovechar que
my videos where I was exposed
mis vídeos donde quedaba expuesto
were
estaban
eliminated for
eliminados para
lie saying that he didn't mess with
mentir diciendo que él no se metió con
Antonio David who didn't mess with Roco
Antonio David que no se metió con Rocío
flowers and has taken advantage of all this to
flores y ha aprovechado todo esto para
lie what is happening because the
mentir qué es lo que pasa pues que la
people who were there at the time, well, I don't know
gente que estaba en la época pues no se
forget So if you start lying
olvida Entonces si tú te pones a mentir
Well, people take out the clip, okay? And
pues la gente te saca el clip vale Y
so what he has done is with with
entonces lo que ha hecho es con con
Twitter accounts and with more channels
cuentas de Twitter y con canales más
small censor based on
pequeños censurar a base de
strike and you're not going to do that to me
strike y a mí eso no me lo vas a hacer
Juanjo, why do we have censorship here?
Juanjo porque la tenemos aquí la censura
No, man, censorship isn't going to help you here.
no tío aquí la censura no te va a servir
you're welcome because if you throw me a
de nada porque si tú me tiras a mí un
video I tell people here that
vídeo yo le digo aquí a la gente que lo
each upload to your social networks
suban cada uno a sus redes sociales
integers Twitter Facebook and it is the effect
enteros Twitter Facebook y es el efecto
trisan If you have no arguments
trisan Si tú no tienes argumentos
Shut up okay here he threatened Roberto
Cállate vale aquí amenazó a a Roberto
thug even for reporting for
macarra incluso por a denunciar por
to report for the civil for
a denunciar por lo por los civil por
Copyright The liar is worth it
derechos de autor El mentiroso vale que
If Roberto appealed the strike that was given to him
si Roberto apelaba el strike que le puso
On Twitter, people also appeal to you
en Twitter en Twitter también se apela
okay, that takes advantage of that because
vale que eso se aprovecha de eso porque
There are many people who do not know it, not in
hay mucha gente que no lo sabe no en
Twitter also appeals and said
Twitter también se apela vale y le dijo
to Roberto that he was going to report him for
a Roberto que lo iba a denunciar por
copyright that was a lie and
derechos de autor que fue mentira y
Roberto won, he won the appeal.
Roberto ganó eh ganó la apelación
measures again copyright Because it is
medidas otra vez de copyright Porque se
They are inventing things, well, as you wish.
están inventando fulas bueno como queris
call it I don't know specifically what it was
llamarlo no sé en concreto de que era el
Roberto's cli but come on it was a cli
cli de Roberto pero vamos era un cli
where he lied about something and they put him
donde él mintió sobre algo y le pusieron
the cli and he says that well I had to
el cli y él dice que bueno he tenido que
to strike because they are
meter un estrike Porque se están
inventing conspiracy theories with
inventando teorías conspirativas con
Regarding what I say, I do not say in my
respecto a a lo que digo no digo en mis
direct, what I say is what I want
directos yo lo que digo es lo que quiero
say there is no more, there are no more stories
decir no hay más no hay más historias
So when someone takes an extract
Entonces cuando coge alguien un extracto
my live and says that
mi directo y dice que
this but not to me where they have to
esto pero no a m a donde tienen que
wish me what you want but this challenge yes
deséame lo que quieras pero este reto sí
It's worth it, you've taken a lot away from me
merece la pena me has quitado muchas
a kiss, beautiful Josefina, a kiss, beautiful Josefina
un beso Josefina guapa un beso Josefina
well the live one
bueno el directo
this is it
este lo
we can react at another time
podemos reacionar en otro momento
We can talk about this live in another
podemos hablar de este directo en otro
moment Amador threatened me at this
momento Amador me amenazó en este
direct Amador muedano Amador moedano is
directo Amador muedano Amador moedano se
put there in his live with the
puso ahí en su directo con el
approval of the owner of the Canal
beneplácito del dueño del Canal el canal
familiar is to say that I that I
familiar vale a decir que que me que me
They wanted to wait behind a car with
querían esperar detrás de un coche con
a board to stick with a board and that
una tabla para pegar con una tabla y que
if I stepped on
si pisaba
chipiona that if I stepped on chipiona I would
chipiona que si pisaba chipiona me
Amador Moedano threw out the dogs that were already
echaba los perros Amador moedano que ya
He was sentenced because the dogs attacked
fue condenado porque los perros atacaron
a little girl threatened me that if
a una niña pequeña me amenazó con que si
I stepped on Chipiona and threw my
pisaba chipiona me echaba los
dogs with the owner's approval
perros con el beneplácito del dueño del
Channel that even the daughter called it
Canal que hasta la hija le llamó la
daily care
atención al día
next okay this is by phone
siguiente vale esto es por teléfono
with a guarantee that lives off insults and defame
con garán que vive de insultos difamar
to slander and it cannot be and then it goes to
de calumniar y no puede ser y luego va a
Amador comes who has seen some videos of
venir Amador que ha visto unos vídeos de
He will then come to Amador and I believe you that
él luego va a venir Amador y te creo que
He wants to give his opinion, he goes, I'll tell him to give his opinion.
quiere opinar él va ya le digo que opine
with peace of mind it's worth it Because also
con con tranquilidad vale Porque además
Javi said that I told him that I gave him
Javi ha dicho que yo le dije que le di
I never slammed the door on Javir Veira.
el portazo a javir veira yo nunca le
Amador said that Amador said several things
Amador dijo eso Amador dijo varias cosas
Several insults were also reported to him.
varios insultos adás se le denunció Lo
What happens is that the Chiclana court does not
que pasa que el juzgado de chiclana no
He notified it and it remained there as in the
lo notificó y por ahí quedó como en el
Limbo and there was a moment when he
Limbo y ya hubo un momento en el que le
I told Paul, let him be lost.
dije a Pablo déjalo déjalo que se pierda
There, what are you going to get out of that man?
ahí que que qué le vas sacar ese hombre
If it is embargoed then it is also released
si está embargados luego salió también
what Ricky got out of it, no ...
lo que sacó Ricky no eh de que no de que
He had no money and his house was seized.
no tenía dinero le embargaron la la casa
This is the sister's who goes
esta de la de la hermana que vaya
Shame on you for the debt and for not
vergüenza vale que por la deuda y por no
pay the treasury what you owe
pagar la hacienda lo que le debes te
take away your uncle's sister's inheritance
quiten la herencia de tu hermana tío la
house that your sister Roco Jurado leaves you
casa que te deja tu hermana Rocío Jurado
and they take it away from you, okay? And then why?
y te la quiten vale Y entonces para qué
You're going to continue with this if the guy doesn't go.
vas a continuar con esto si el tío no va
to pay a penny but they don't have to pay me
a pagar un duro pero no a m a tienen que
I have no idea who you are Juanjo but not like that.
ni idea de quién eres Juanjo pero así no
you will get more followers for sure
conseguirás más seguidores seguro que es
What you are looking for, I said who Javil Beila was
lo que buscas dije quién era javil beila
and he recently discovered that they happened to him
y lo descubrió hace poco que le pasaron
a video of these repetitions that makes
un vídeo de estas repeticiones que hace
annoying Well I'm going to ask you one
cansinas Bueno yo te voy a hacer una
question have you already received the complaint of
pregunta te ha llegado Ya la denuncia de
Roco Carrasco with this one she is with
Rocío Carrasco con esta con la que está
talking on the phone is avoid Dynamite
hablando por teléfono es evita Dinamita
Okay, there's Eva Dynamite saying
vale Ahí está evita Dinamita diciendo
It's good that you had received it
que bueno que si le había llegado la
complaint by Roso Carrasco because in his
denuncia de roso Carrasco porque en su
many many moments
momento muchos muchos
famous that now we are going to Let's go to
famosos que ahora vamos a Vamos a
reviewing a few is worth it
repasar unos cuantos vale
Many celebrities have already warned him about
muchos famosos le han advertido ya de
complaints and demands are worth it.
denuncias y de demanda vale Así de
Memory Amor Romeira released a statement
memoria amor romeira puso un comunicado
through his lawyers and he had to
a través de sus abogados y él tuvo que
remove a super nervous video to ask
retirar un vídeo super nervioso pedir
sorry okay love romeira I was going to
perdón vale amor romeira lo iba a
report Because he made fun of it, he mocked it
denunciar Porque hizo mofa hizo burla
About If love when I was little I had
sobre Si amor cuando pequeña tenía
tail or he looked at his tail in the in the
colita o se miraba la colita en la en la
bathtub something like that completely was
bañera algo así completamente fue
The comment was disgusting
asquerosísimo el comentario fue
disgusting comment and I understand that
asqueroso el comentario y entiendo que
love was going to take serious measures and
amor fuese a tomar medidas seria y
I completely understand why he was
entiendo perfectamente que él se pusiera
nervously deleted the video and asked
nervioso eliminara el vídeo y pidiera
Sorry
Perdón
Ok And who else Well Alexia riva to the
vale Y quién más Bueno Alexia riva a la
who told him that he was a scoundrel Anton Le
que le dijo que estaba golfe anton le
has warned of a
tiene advertido de una
demands several creators also Diego
demanda varios creadores también Diego
Diego's suburb, the suburb said that Diego
arrabal de Diego arrabal dijo que Diego
he disguised himself as
se disfrazó de
break into a hospital to steal
meterse en un hospital a robar
documentation well be it was tremendous yes
documentación bueno sea fue tremendo si
this
este
man does not have
hombre no tiene
sense doesn't make sense Vale and avoids it
sentido no tiene sentido Vale y la evita
Dynamite
Dinamita
You have respected for too long
esta demasiado tiempo has respetado a
You should have had this guy before
este tipo antes tenías que haberle
answered r face in love caror that a
contestado r cara enamorada caror que un
Random now You are going to see the numbers that
Random ahora Vais a ver los números que
has is a
tiene es un
Random come on people we have to do this
Random venga gente hay que hacer este
challenge and in a short time you will see the
reto y en poco tiempo que se vea la
Javi's community, a kiss, a kiss, handsome
comunidad de Javi un beso un beso guapos
em this one avoids Dynamite okay it is
em esta evita Dinamita vale que está
saying there you have already received the one
diciendo ahí te ha llegado Ya la de
avoid that you will surely see this
evita que seguro que vas a ver este
direct and you know what it hasn't
directo y la Tú sabes lo que no ha
arrived avoids the demand that you
llegado evita tampoco la demanda que tú
You were going to name Marta Riesco, but that one hasn't happened.
le ibas a poner a Marta riesco esa no ha
arrived nor has it been lost in the
llegado tampoco se ha perdido en el
path or
camino o
What I said at the time, do you remember it?
qué lo dije en su día os acordáis no lo
I said one day you know what hasn't happened
dije en su día sabes lo que no ha
The complaint that was going to come to me has not arrived either
llegado tampoco la denuncia que me iba a
arrive from Raquel Moreno Where is that
llegar de Raquel Moreno Dónde está que
I stayed
me quedé
Juanjo is not expecting her either today.
esperándola tampoco Juanjo a día de hoy
You don't talk to Eva Dinamita or you
ni te hablas con evita Dinamita ni te
You're talking to Raquel Moreno. Okay, so no.
hablas con Raquel Moreno Vale O sea no
I have commented on your fight with the
he comentado la pelea tuya con con la
Avoid Dynamite, which was cinema, okay?
evita Dinamita que fue cine vale
absolutely
absolutamente
cinema per
cine per
Didn't you just threaten again with
no acabos de amenazar de nuevo con
strike war
guerra de strikes
Take care of yourself. Look, she's not going to deny it.
Cuidate contigo Mira no va a desmentir
What is taken here is not a strike war
lo que se saque aquí no guerra de strike
That is the defense of the strike war
esa es la defensa de él guerra de strike
whatever you want and wherever you want Juanjo
la que tú quieras y donde quieras Juanjo
the one you want wherever you want it
la que tú quieres donde quiera la
censorship I'll tell you where you're going to go
censura ya te digo yo dónde te la vas a
strike war says the
meter guerra de strike dice la
creature is the but not to m a d have
criatura es lo pero no a m a d tienen
that he is angry with the numbers is
que que está amgad por los números está
bitter about the numbers now You'll see
amargo por los números ahora Vais a ver
the reality now You are going to see the reality
la realidad ahora Vais a ver la realidad
of the
de los
numbers They didn't want gossip from you. Well, here
números No a ti querían salseo Pues aquí
they have at
tienen al
King with heart eyes fought with
reyo con ojos de corazón se peleado con
Raquel Moreno, Olga Moreno's family
Raquel Moreno la familia de Olga moreno
doesn't want anything with him, it was cinema the t
no quiere nada con él sea fue cine los t
Raquel Moreno was cinema the tweets of
Raquel Moreno fue cine los tweet de
Raquel Moreno asking him not to come back
Raquel Moreno pidiéndole que no volviera
to mention that the sister has fought
a mencionar a la hermana se ha peleado
with the avoidance of Dynamite that also
con la evita Dinamita que tampoco
They want to know nothing about him, okay? Well then.
quieren saber nada de él vale Bueno pues
the obsessed colleague the colleague
el colega obsesionado el colega
obsessed with the dead channel
obsesionado vale con el canal muertxs
imo with the dead channel simo that I enjoyed
imo con el canal muert simo que disfrute
of these minutes of fame because it is
de estos minutos de fama porque está
dead tisimo Vale instead of taking and
muert tisimo Vale en vez de [__] y
leave things as they are now You are going to
dejar las cosas como están ahora Vais a
see that he has been screwing me for two years
ver que se ha pegado dos años tirándome
[ __ ] two years throwing [ __ ] at me 2s years
[__] dos años tirándome [__] 2s años
and here I have a little bit of what people
y aquí tengo un poco de lo que la gente
He was sending it to me and I have been saving it
me iba mandando y lo lo he ido guardando
Every time someone sent me something
cada vez que alguien me mandaba algo
but it will surely be much more
pero seguramente será muchísimo más
much more
muchísimo más
okay, the guy instead of [ __ ] and each one to
vale el tío en vez de [__] y cada uno a
his way Each one on his own is worth it
su camino Cada uno por su lado vale el
uncle was taking advantage of the videos
tío estaba Aprovechando que los vídeos
mine were
míos estaban
eliminated to lie or look at this
eliminados para mentir o sea mirar esto
Let me put it here, this is with Tania.
a ver te lo pongo esto es con Tania esto
It's a live show he did with Tania Vale
es un directo que hizo con Tania vale
because he has gone to join with everyone
porque se ha ido a juntar con con todos
I mean, with anyone I've been to
o sea con cualquiera que yo haya ido
arguing and so on with everyone
discutiendo y demás pues con todos ha
gone to look for everyone absolutely
ido a buscar a todos absolutamente a
Ok, so this is a live stream from him.
todos Vale pues esto es un directo de él
with Tania that Tania was supposed to
con Tania que la Tania se suponía que
She was moderator of Antonia VI but her
era moderadora de Antonia vi pero ya su
life is centered on Javi, okay, that is to say
vida se centra en Javi vale o sea se
talk to Juanjo, talk to Antonia
habla con Juanjo se habla con la Antonia
that his Twitter is dedicated to calling
que su Twitter está dedicado a llam
mistreated Antonio David is worth that much
maltratado a Antonio David vale eso
because I am more important than Antonio
porque yo soy más importante que Antonio
David Bueno is that I am the most
David Bueno es que yo soy el más
important of all why Because if you
importante de todos por qué Porque si tú
You are a fan of Antonio David, you have
eres una fan de Antonio David tú tienes
on Twitter in the blue tide flight then
en el Twitter en la avío marea azul pues
It is assumed that your opinion is focused on a
se supone que tú tu opinión se centra un
little in your principles Tania not in jav
poco en tus principios Tania no en jav
oliveira, that is, because by getting together with
oliveira o sea porque juntándote con
This meeting with Antonia and with
este juntándote con la Antonia y con
all of you who join together, well, what
todos los que te juntas pues lo que
you are proving that you do not have a single
estás demostrando es que no tienes ni un
just a good beginning for that and for
solo principio bueno por eso y por
many more things Tania that surely
muchas cosas más Tania que seguramente
We will also comment on this live stream.
también comentaremos en este directo
Okay, but you have no principles at all.
Vale pero no tienes principio ninguno
Tania, none is more important to you.
Tania ninguno es más importante para ti
Javi Oliveira, you are the moderator of the
Javi oliveira tú eres moderadora del
Antonio's channel you were looking forward to
canal de Antonio avid estabas deseando
being a collaborator on Antonio AB's channel
ser colaboradora del canal de Antonio AB
that Consuelo told the other day but
que lo contó el otro día Consuelo pero
Javi Oliveira gives you more than Antonio
te tira más Javi oliveira que Antonio
David because you don't care if it's a
David porque no te importa si es una
person who is against Antonio
persona que esté en contra de Antonio
David or in favor do you care that it is A
David o a favor te importa que esté A
for or against Javi Oliveira and it is
favor o en contra de Javi oliveira y es
What this kid was telling you
lo que os iba diciendo este este Chaval
instead of taking it and saying, "Well, I have."
en vez de [__] y decir Bueno pues he
reached a good agreement with Javi
llegado a un buen acuerdo con Javi
oliveira each one on his own path
oliveira cada uno por su camino
and I have my Game Over deleted and my
e y tengo mi Game Over eliminado y mis
deleted videos that no one knows the whole story
vídeos borrados que nadie sabe toda la
Hey, what mischief I've done without lying.
eh travesuras que he hecho no mintiendo
With things like this, let me see what you put here.
con cosas como estas a ver te lo pongo
to the comment Yes because I'm not watching
al comentario Sí porque no estoy viendo
Now this is a comment from Auri that
ahora esto es un comentario de Auri que
You know he's always around here
ya sabéis que está por aquí siempre no
Auri Auri chalde you know her what she says
Auri Auri chalde la conocéis que dice a
Roco Flores told her that she had to go to
Rocío flores Le dijo que tenía que ir a
older brother okay this is what Auri puts in
hermano mayor vale esto lo pone Auri en
the comment you see puts it in
el comentario lo veis lo pone en
screen and Juanjo who answers this
pantalla y Juanjo que responde a esto el
channel wait clear I think so too
canal espérate claro yo creo que también
explanations for me too because to me
explicaciones tamb para m porque a m
I also received that, but from Roco.
tamb me ha llegado eso pero de de Rocío
FL said that it is a lie. That never happened.
FL dijo que es es mentira Eso nunca lo
I said that is a lie I never said that
dije eso es mentira Eso nunca lo dije
There are many hoaxes too, that never happens
hay muchos bulos también eso nunca hay
many bu
muchos bu
we also hear it again
también lo volvemos a escuchar lo
we return to
volvemos a
listen you said you didn't say it guajo and
escuchar dijiste no lo dijiste guajo y
Tania knows this, Tania knows this
esto Tania lo sabe esto Tania lo sabe
Look here Auri posted it on Twitter
mira aquí Auri la se lo puso en Twitter
Okay, here Auris put it on Twitter to
vale aquí auris se lo puso en Twitter a
Tania, okay, eh, I tagged her, see you Tania?
Tania vale eh la etiquetó lo veis Tania
He said it, he didn't click this click
lo dijo no le puso el click este click
Of course the censor screwed him
por supuesto el censurador se lo tiró
Okay, and Auri also sent it to him via DM.
vale Y además Auri se lo mandó por md a
Tania, you see this, Auri published this.
Tania lo veis esto lo ha publicado Auri
On her Twitter she sends him the clip Tania
en su Twitter le manda el clip Tania lo
see you know Look you see here the seen you know
ve sabéis Mira veis aquí el visto sabéis
What is Tania's response when she
cuál es la respuesta de Tania cuando le
They send this to block Auri That was the
mandan esto bloquear a Auri Esa fue la
Tania's answer Vale now I
respuesta de Tania Vale ahora me
I would like to tell you a little about what is happening
gustaría comentaros un poco Qué pasa
Roman but he is not fighting with the
Román pero no está peleado con la
explosive I predict the future for you
explosiva les pronostico el futuro los
enemies of your enemies are going to become
enemigos de tus enemigos se van a volver
unite For the simple fact of going against
unir Por el simple hecho de ir contra
Javi suggestion for the next live
Javi sugerencia para el próximo directo
Avoid it, it's not like my enemy, okay?
evita no es como como enemiga mía vale
You see this These are the occasions in which
veis esto Estos son las ocasiones en las
that Juanjo has been kind enough to do for two
que Juanjo ha tenido a bien durante dos
years well these are some above
años bueno esto son algunas por encima
the ones that Juanjo has seen fit to do,
las que Juanjo ha tenido a bien pues
Well, talk about me live and
pues hablar de mí en su directo y
throw [ __ ] at me Yes yes the one that the one of the
tirarme [__] Sí sí el que el de los
strike the one of the
strike el de los
strike I speak what I want
strike yo hablo lo que me da la gana de
people but don't leave me alone
la gente pero a mí que no me dejen
Bad Yes of course they are going to get on Rodrigo
mal Sí claro que se van a subir Rodrigo
and let him throw it, let him throw it, we'll see
y que lo tire que lo tire que veremos
where necessary to throw them And if you
dónde haga falta que los tire Y si os
They throw a clip from Twitter, contact me, what do you think?
tiran clip de Twitter contactarme que os
I say where it is appealed as well as
digo dónde se apela al igual que
They started with the pimping when
empezaron con el chuleo cuando
They discovered the report by
descubrieron el el reporte por
defamation censorship not colleague
difamación la censura no colega la
censorship we are not all dedicated to speaking
censura no nos dedicamos todos a hablar
of things censorship does not son
de las cosas la censura no hijo la
censorship not instead of instead of trying
censura no en vez de en vez de intentar
censor would have let go of my arm
censurar me hubiera soltado el brazo
during these two years all this is
durante estos dos años todo esto son
some examples of you obsessed
algunos ejemplos de ti obsesionado
with me
conmigo
when they boycotted me in the
cuando me hicieron boicot en la
UNEP University this summer
universidad de la unep este verano
when I filed the lawsuit against Diego
cuando le puse la demanda a Diego
Doceta suburb
arrabal doceta
Hey, my exclusive from Antonio Tejado.
eh la exclusiva mía de Antonio tejado mi
Exclusive Olga and Agustn getting into it
exclusiva de Olga y Agustín metiéndote
with my wife for the bags that are
con mi mujer por los bolsos que se
buy that fabric eh about Fran costs
compra que eso tela eh sobre Fran cuesta
and every live show I've done with Fran
y cada directo que he hecho con Fran lo
has commented on whether or not I pay to
ha comentado sobre si pago o no pago a
my collaborators or the people who
mis colaboradores o a la gente que
interviewed about salary or no salary
entrevisto sobre el sueldo o no sueldo
Marina's about joining him with
de Marina sobre le le se juntarse con
Troy road with Loli Huerta and Tania
ard de Troya con Loli Huerta con Tania
with Peppa
con Peppa
and about nauter
e sobre nauter
Fay on the flat sentence on the
fay sobre la sentencia de plana sobre la
sentence of of
sentencia de de
Look what he caught in a
miare tío Mirad lo que se le pilló en un
direct Look what was caught in a
directo Mirad lo que se le pilló en un
live they have a call to a follower
directo tienen llamada a una seguidora
that the flame is bored like
que la llama está aburrido como
any of their live shows
cualquiera de sus directos no
very boring and look what's going on
aburridísimo y y mirar lo que está
fiddling with the computer and listening to it
toqueteando el ordenador y escuchar lo
that jumps out at him Eh This is not a
que le salta Eh Esto no es un
assembly sipro that each one the pain it
montaje sipro que cada uno el dolor lo
carries in a different way not even you
lleva de diferente manera no incluso tú
You can have moments when you go to a sanatorium
puedes tener ratos Sal un sanatorio
normal and when Marta Riesco wanted
normal y cuando Marta riesco ha querido
take advantage and there are times when
aprovechar y hay momentos se le
breaks his face and closes it running
descompone la cara lo cierra corriendo
the guy is live, he is not here
sea está el tío en directo no está
taking into account what he is talking about
echando cuenta lo que le está hablando
the follower and is touching and is
la seguidora y está toqueteando y se le
You open a tab and a video is filtered.
Abre una pestaña y se le filtra un vídeo
mine that I had open and when Marta
mío que tenía abierto y cuando Marta
Riesco wanted to take advantage of the guy, stop
riesco ha querido aprovechar tío deja de
seeing me is a desire to suffer, stop
verme son ganas de sufrir deja de
see me I don't even know what the hell you're doing
verme yo no sé ni qué [__] haces tú
because it is not of interest to
porque no le interesa a
no one stops
nadie deja de
see me Look at the insinuation about me
verme Mirad la insinuación sobre mi
Woman: Hey, I'm fine with how I am.
mujer Eh yo apte de cómo estoy
I'm putting up with the invitations because I have
aguantando los invites es porque tengo
a couple that gives me everything, there are others
una pareja que me lo da todo hay otas
people ask for more money have more
personas les pide más dinero tiene más
Deison bags or whatever it's called and well
bolsos de deison o como se diga y pues
They are like crazy people who don't know what
eso están como locos que no sabena Qué
do to earn more money and there are others
hacer para ganar más dinero y hay otros
who have a woman who asks for more
que tienen una mujer que le piden más
bags more I don't know what I don't know how much to what
bolsos más no sé qué no sé cuánto a que
I put here a goal to buy you a
pongo aquí un objetivo para comprarle un
bag for my wife juo that I buy her
bolso a mi mujer juo a que yo le compro
to my wife whatever I want and that
a mi mujer lo que me dé la gana y a que
when I bought it for my wife,
cuando yo se lo compré a mi mujer se lo
buy yours for these
compra tú a la tuya por estás
obsessed with me because you bought yourself
obsesionado conmigo Porque te compraste
a car when you got into my car
un coche cuando te montaste en mi coche
of
de
Malaga But what does this mean, huh?
Málaga Pero esto qué significado eh
family
familia
What is this? I'm telling you, I'm happy.
esto Qué es ya te digo yo soy feliz
because it is the best possible community
porque que es la mejor comunidad posible
and I have the best family you don't have
y tengo la mejor fam tú no tienes
community none Juanjo you have 800 900
comunidad ninguna Juanjo tienes 800 900
people like many 1000 live to
personas como muchos 1000 en directo a
You have no community left because of who you are.
ti no te queda comunidad por como eres
because you don't entertain the best community
porque no entretienes la mejor comunidad
the entire internet is here
de todo internet está aquí
Gentlemen, what are you going to get?
señoreros estás que que te va a dar
Don't look at me anymore, dude. It's just that I'm not me.
algo no me mires más tío es que yo no yo
with the people you my microphone says the
con la gente tú mis micrófono dice el
Indian no no same microphone no Indian
indio no no mismo micrófono no indio
same microphone as the other day
mismo micrófono no que el otro día se
Juanjo invented a challenge, did you think about cutting yourself?
inventó un reto Juanjo pensaste cortarte
the bar sometimes one that the other day
la barra alguna vez una que el otro día
he invented a challenge to shave his
se inventó un reto para afeitarse el
mustache that he has not done that in the
bigote que eso no lo ha hecho él en la
life says no no it's not that I'm thinking about
vida dice no no es que estoy pensando en
shave more around here and leave my mustache
afeitarme más por aquí dejarme El bigote
a little less than what is usually the case
un poco menos que es lo que se lleva
Now who has grown a mustache?
ahora quién quién se ha hecho el bigote
Now Juann, look, this was when I
ahora juanón mira Esto fue cuando me lo
They sent me, I said no, no fades, to cut my
mandaron dije no no fades cortarme la
beard Let's see, right now I'm in
barba A ver es que ahora mismo Estoy en
a time of changes that even I
una época ya de cambios que hasta me lo
said a person I know because
dijo una persona que conozco yo porque
now you are not Javi Oliveira Juanjo me
ahora no eres Javi oliveira Juanjo me
I left my beard at two before I left it longer
dejo la barba al dos antes lo dejaba más
The thicker the beard, the more the mustache
más tocho la barba me dejo más El bigote
as everyone is doing because
como está haciendo todo el mundo porque
Now on the street everyone goes to
ahora por la calle todo el mundo va a
The Grisons left my mustache as it is
los grison me dejo el bigote como está
doing all the
haciendo todo el
world you are not jav oliveira You are not going to
mundo no eres jav oliveira No lo vas a
you were a fan as we already saw in the script
ser eras un fan como ya vimos en el guin
that I admired that I drank the winds
que me admiraba que bebía los vientos
for me that you collaborated with me for a time
por mí que colaboraste una época conmigo
and that I stopped collaborating with you because
y que dejé de colaborar contigo porque
You did me a dirty trick by loving me
me hiciste una guarrerías queriéndome
get rid of an interview for two cents
quitar una entrevista por dos duros
dirty Juanjo and you stayed with me
guarros Juanjo y te quedaste conmigo con
the thing is not Jai Oliveira the
la cosa no eres Jai oliveira el
pending that maybe tomorrow is the
pendiente que a lo mejor mañana es el
last day of the pending maybe I
último día del pendiente a lo mejor me
I'm leaving because people have told me that
lo dejo porque la gente me han dicho que
They loved it, I'll leave it anyway. Yes, yes.
les ha encantado igual lo dejo Yo sí sí
Yes, your people have loved it.
sí la gente tuya le ha encantado al
earring
pendiente
oo a p each
oo una p cada
Spanish but not me where they have to
español pero no a mí a donde tienen que
Javi We have to talk about something in
Javi Tenemos que hablar una cosa en
private you will understand some things and in
privado entenderás algunas cosas y en
public we are also going to talk a few
público también vamos a hablar unas
Sor things we are going to do an interview
cosas Sor vamos a hacer una entrevis
Aunt in public we are also going to put
tita en público también vamos a poner
some examples are worth it for people
algunos ejemplos vale para que la gente
don't say no, they are just messy
no diga que no que son que son movidas
Mine okay boycott of the UNB okay This was
mías vale boicot a la unb vale Esto fue
We recently went to that gentleman's place. This was
hace poco vamos a ese señor estuvo Esto
It was recently, okay, recently and I had
fue hace poco vale hace poco e yo tuve
some problems with This was with
unos problemas con Esto fue con
some with whom it was that of the Well I
unas con quién fue lo de la Bueno yo
I had a conference because there are several
tenía una conferencia porque hay varias
occasions in which I have
ocasiones en las que me han
called to give lectures at the
llamado para dar conferencias en las
universities on media
universidades sobre medios de
communication about some things no Y
comunicación sobre algunas cosas no Y
There are times when I post it on Instagram
hay veces que lo publico en Instagram
There are others that are not worth it but I think that the
hay otras que no vale pero creo que los
that I followed a long time ago
que me seguí hace tiempo lo
you know but no to no no to that kind of
sabéis pero no a no no a ese tipo de
comments you can't make envy
comentarios no envidia puedes hacer
direct without a cap, eyes everyone
directo sin gorra ojos todo el mundo
You can do it live without a cap, anything goes
puede hacer directo sin gorra vale todo
the world has that freedom but
el mundo tiene esa libertad pero
try to avoid those kinds of comments
intentar evitar ese tipo de comentarios
Okay, it was viral, eh, it was viral, we were there.
vale fue viral eh fue viral lo estuvimos
commenting here there was some
comentando aquí hubo cierta
polemics
polemiques
Well, I don't know if it was summer or something like that.
Pues no sé si fue verano o algo así
you know what we are talking about
sabéis de lo que estamos hablando
You don't know what we're talking about, right?
no sabéis de lo que estamos hablando no
eh I had a chat with Triun and with
eh yo tenía una charla con triun y con
Joaqun Campos I think it was not with
Joaquín Campos creo que era no con
Joaqun Campos
Joaquín Campos
with Luis Garrido at a university in
con Luis Garrido en una universidad de
the unep who wants to be Javi is obsessed
la unep quio ser Javi es un obsesionado
kiss Clara okay I had a chat that
beso Clara vale Yo tenía una charla que
They canceled it because the community of
me la cancelaron porque la comunidad de
some youtubers started to contact and
unos youtubers se pusieron a contactar y
to bother the university do you remember
a molestar a la universidad os acordáis
not about that
de eso no
Ok then, listen to our colleague Olivera.
vale pues Escuchar al colega al Olivera
You were right, conera cap, you will never be like
Tena razón gorra conera nunca serás como
the king not even in your best dreams Kisses
el rey ni en tus mejores sueños Besos
Yara throwing a kiss and defending well
yara lanzando un beso y defend bueno
As many people are not like that of
Como tanta gente no es como lo de lo de
that you have an event and it is cancelled
que tienes un evento y te lo cancelen
because they talk more about
porque hablen más de
you are like what you have
ti es como que es como lo de que tienes
an event and they cancel it because they talk
un evento y te lo cancelen porque hablen
Bad things happened to me because of Paz Padilla
mal de ti a mí fueron por Paz Padilla
a play to be performed
una obra de teatro para para que se
Antonio designed to make enemies with me
enemistar conmigo diseñaron Antonio
David flowers to leave so that
David flores para que dejase para que
had a relationship with me saying
tuviese relación conmigo diciendo
erased from me that I also have
borradas de mí que además yo tengo
I don't know what evidence and witnesses were made
pruebas y testigos yo que sé se hicieron
a lot of nonsense and we already
muchísimas burradas y Nosotros ya nos
we climb on the back and forward
subimos a la espalda y para adelante
Juanjo, two have passed
Juanjo han pasado do
years the first thing that everything has its nuances
años lo primero que tod tiene su matices
has its things not in your fantasy but
tiene sus cosas no en Tu fantasía Pero
What does it have to do with you having a
qué tiene que ver que tú tengas un
paid work in a talk but of
trabajo pagado en una charla pero de
anyway, that is to say, it doesn't have
todas maneras o sea es que no tiene
sense not even that you are
sentido ni siquiera ni que estéis
informed of that topic
informado de ese tema
dude it doesn't make any sense
tío es que no tiene sentido ni
even if you are informed of
siquiera de que tú estés informado de
that topic stops
ese tema deja de
seeing me causes you a
verme te causa un
stop watching me but cute
deja de verme pero monar
worlds of Holy Hobs Mother
mundos de Santos hobs madre
mine is that you know what happens is like the
mía es que sabé lo que pas es como la
television that said it another day Basile
televisión que lo decía otro día basile
when three to Campos that people do not
cuando tres a Campos que la gente no
has memory, that is, he reaches a
tiene memoria o sea él se llega a un
agreement in which each one has his own path
acuerdo en el que cada uno su camino no
speak to each other they take off their
habla el uno del otro se quitan los
videos but he wants people to have
vídeos pero él quiere que la gente tenga
memory is that I don't understand it a bit
memoria es que no no lo entiendo un
second that I have to go to the bathroom no
segundo que tengo que ir al baño no
I take no time, I don't even wash my hands
tardo nada no me lavo ni las manos
if one
si una
but
pñ pero
Don't remember what I said about the members and
no Acuérdate que decía de los miembros y
bif now in the challenges they ask for bif because
bif ahora en los retos piden bif porque
It arrives before and he doesn't share it with you
le llega antes y no comparte con you
it makes no sense at all
no tiene sentido ninguno
family has no meaning whatsoever
familia no tiene sentido ninguno o sea
with a person with whom you have
con una persona con la que tú has
agreed not to
acordado no
mentioning makes sense to comment on this
mencionar sentido tiene comentar esto
dude okay that's the problem with people
tío vale es el problema que hay la gente
stays and to throw [ __ ] Eh for
se queda y para tirar [__] Eh por
supposedly the last thing
supuesto eh lo último
but that's the thing about it
pero eso es lo de la
unev demands Diego
unev demanda Diego
suburb I forgive myself for everything
arrabal a m mismo me perdono todo
Diego Arrabal demands not these last ones
demanda Diego arrabal no estos últimos
month has known that I put it last year
mes ha sabido que le puse el año pasado
a lawsuit against Diego Arrabal that has
una demanda a Diego arrabal que le ha
arrived now is worth it
llegado ahora vale
exo each one of us knows our own
exo cada uno nos conocemos nuestros
defects, some more than others, are true
defectos unos más otros menos de verdad
as
cómo
you are myself lost because the
estás a m mismo perdido porque el
minute less noci noes final we are the
minuto menos noci noes final estamos los
as always because the live shows always
de siempre porque los directos siempre
They have 25 20 on the person who is
tienen 25 20 sobre la persona que está
By saying that you are telling me that
diciendo eso me estás contando es que
we are my pore I have put it jokingly you go
estamos mis poro lo hab puesto coña vas
do
hacer
Good thing this isn't the one I thought it was.
que bueno este no es el que me creía yo
He has made several extracts even
él ha hecho varios extractos incluso
commenting on Diego Arrabal's lawsuit
comentando la demanda de Diego arrabal
saying that it made no sense for that
diciendo que no tenía sentido que esa
demand made no sense that demand
demanda no tenía sentido que esa demanda
I had put it there because they had told me
la había puesto yo porque como me habían
convicted in another lawsuit Well, I wanted
condenado en otra demanda Pues yo quería
that they condemned someone That said okay
que condenaran a alguien Eso dijo vale
which is like dude what the [ __ ] are you
que es como tío qué [__] estás
you commenting on something that we have
comentando tú de una cosa que hemos
agreed that we don't talk about each other
acordado que no hablamos el uno del otro
Well, Diego Arrabal's demand is not
pues la demanda de Diego arrabal no
not only commented on it but this is good
solamente la comentó sino que esto bueno
This is what everyone agreed on.
Esto se pusieron todos de acuerdo eh la
the night he gave Barbal that live show
noche que dio barbal hizo aquel directo
which seemed a little good to me XD
que a mí me pareció un poquito bueno XD
We're going to say XD not that Diego did like
vamos a decir XD no que Diego hizo como
a live show celebrating in style
un directo celebrando por todo lo alto
that they had accepted his appeal that
que le habían aceptado el recurso de que
We changed the court, okay?
lo cambiáramos de juzgado vale que por
Whatever it is, he celebrated it for everyone
lo que sea le le lo celebró por todos
the os while it was in
los os mientras que ello estaba en
Valencia he posted this tweet of the
Valencia él puso este tweet del
Roadrunner seems to catch him on the train
correcamino como que lo pilla el el tren
because he considers himself the roadrunner and
porque él se considera el correcamino y
that I am the Coyote and it rises every time
que yo soy el Coyote y sube cada vez de
from time to time drawings on Twitter that
vez en cuando dibujitos en Twitter eso
And well then the next day
e Bueno pues luego al día siguiente lo
He denied it, of course, people are calling him uncle.
negó claro la gente le está diciendo tío
that you are commenting on this too
que estás comentando esto también lo
denied okay No no I put it at random
negó vale No no lo puse al azar el
little drawing. On top of that, he's a coward, okay?
dibujito Per encima es cobarde vale
twelve twelve twelve and he is a boy
doceta doceta doceta e es un muchacho
and with whom I got along very well I had
e con el que yo me llevaba muy bien tuve
a good relationship is not that either
una relación bueno tampoco es que
We were close friends but these clips
fuéramos íntimos amigos pero estos clip
I'm new, eh? If you're looking at the Setup
soy nuevos eh si estáis viendo el Setup
These clips are not from him from three years ago.
de él estos clips no son de hace TR años
eh these clips are from now eh dosa is
eh estos clips son de ahora eh dosa es
a kid who was from you know okay
un chaval que era de you know vale se
He was with us and everything else was like that
llevaba con con nosotros y demás era así
As a big fan of mine and so on, too
como mu fan sillo mío y demás también e
I gave him the Partner in you know vale And dosa
le di el Partner en you know vale Y dosa
what happened was that
lo que pasó fue que
and people who were previously followers of mine and
e gente que antes era seguidora mía y
currently there is Antonia yare vale
actualmente es aí Antonia yare vale
because they are finally Antonio meare according to their
porque son a fin Antonio meare según sus
Twitter accounts
cuentas de Twitter
And some rather shady things came out about
e salió unas cosas un poco turbias sobre
Docetas is worth a girl.
docetas vale salió una chavala
being cancelled
cancelándose
that he also wants us to touch them
que él quiera también que las toquemos
that I have no problem touching them
que no tengo ningún problema de tocarlas
Okay, and remember that they are quite
vale Y recordarlas que están bastante
interesting no and and this girl who
interesantes no y y esta chica que
She was formerly a follower of mine for her
antiguamente eraa seguidora mía por su
has nothing to do with me Okay when
cuenta nada que ver conmigo Vale cuando
The teacher was canceled for that reason
a doceta lo cancelaron por eso que
many of you who are in the era
muchos de los que estáis en la época
You know what it was like, eh, doset ago?
sabéis que es lo que fue eh doset hacía
a series of things eh completely
una serie de cosas eh completamente
unfortunate enough to dedicate themselves to
desafortunadas para dedicarse a a a la
teaching I mean if I am a teacher already
docencia O sea si yo soy un profesor ya
be it drawing, math or whatever
sea de dibujo de matemáticas o de lo que
be in an institute Well, I don't do it
sea en un instituto Pues yo no hago
certain comments and certain attitudes
ciertos comentarios y ciertas actitudes
that I did have in you know I'm going to
que doceta sí tenía en you know lo voy a
react I'm going to summarize it like this okay no
reaccionar lo voy a resumir así vale no
I'm going to go in because that kid now
voy a entrar porque ese chaval ahora
He's not attacking me, okay?
mismo no me está atacando vale
And what ended up happening was that, eh
em lo que terminó pasando fue que eh
There were people who contacted the school where
hubo gente que contactó al colegio donde
Doc Z was working and sent the clips to someone
trabajaba doc Z le envió los clips a alg
a few clips of two and they kicked him out of the
unos clip de dosz y lo echaron del
institute where I worked is worth this
instituto donde trabajaba vale esto
people like Juanjo and other people are better
gente como Juanjo y otra gente más vale
They have dedicated themselves to selling it as if it were
se han dedicado a venderlo como que a
The teacher was fired from a job for
doceta lo echaron de un trabajo por
harassment
acoso
mine okay eh they repeated it in several
mío vale eh lo repitieron en varias
Occasionally they also did this with
ocasiones esto también lo hicieron con
Leol says that now we will go to
leol le que ahora iremos a
that already has what he wanted war with
eso ya tiene lo que quería guerra con
Javi to go up to wherever you want
Javi para subiras hasta donde quiera
as far as they want, eh
hasta donde quieran eh
They dedicated themselves to saying that series of
se dedicaron a decir esa serie de
mantras I don't know that the teacher
mantras no eh de que el doceta lo
They fired me from my job. Okay.
echaron del trabajo por culpa mía Vale
what the hell did I have to do with what he did?
qué [__] tuve que ver con lo que hiciera
That guy in you know was fired because of guilt
ese tío en you know lo echaron por culpa
yours from work you understand me If you are
suya del trabajo me entiendes Si tú eres
a teacher then don't do the things that
un profesor pues no hagas las cosas que
you do on the internet, okay, recently I was
haces en internet vale hace poco estaba
putting a thread bullying him
poniendo un hilo haciéndole bullying al
Dallas, by his physique, you understand me that
Dallas por su físico me entiendes que
I went to put something on it and they threw me away
fui yo a ponerle algo y se me echaron
above you understand me or
encima me entiendes o
be completely unfortunate things
sea cosas completamente desafortunadas
If you are dedicated to teaching, they fired you and
si te dedicas a la docencia lo echaron y
These people started selling the
esta gente empezaron a a vender el
mantra that the teacher was thrown out for
mantra de que a doceta lo lo echaron por
my
mi
guilt of course there was a moment in which
culpa claro hubo un momento ya en el que
I already heard it, heard it, I
yo ya de escucharlo de escucharlo se me
they burst the balls that was when they
reventaron las pelotas que fue cuando se
I heard Pepe Santos your minute of
lo escuché al Pepe Santos tu minuto de
sauce that is called Pepe today
salsa que se llama a día de hoy Pepe
Santos is a person from the Pepe era
Santos es una persona de la época Pepe
Saint on his day although now it is carried
Santo en su día aunque ahora se lleve
well with doc Z Pepe Santos was the
bien con doc Z Pepe Santos fue el
in charge of taking out all the doc's [ __ ]
encargado de sacar toda la [__] de doc
Z
Z
Pepe Santo was even banned from YouTube.
a Pepe Santo incluso lo banearon de you
know your minute of salsa because it put
know a tu minuto de salsa porque puso
third-party audios about two mushrooms and
audios de terceros sobre dos setas y
other people in which he was not
otras personas en las que él no era
sharer of all things and all things
partícipe todas las cosas y todas las
The [ __ ] that Doc Z put on was
[__] que se pusieron de doc Z fueron
Because Mr. Pepe Santos exposed them
Porque las expuso el señor Pepe Santos
They met with Juanjo, you know they're leaving
se reunieron con Juanjo tú sabes se van
uniting among themselves they are seeking Alliance
uniendo entre ellos van buscando Alianza
and it turns out that e
y resulta que e
[Music]
[Música]
They started selling that mantra until
se pusieron a vender ese mantra hasta
that my balls were blown out
que a mí me reventaron las pelotas de
that they lie about me as they always do
que se mienta sobre mí como hago siempre
No, then Pepe Santo came to my channel.
no entonces Pepe Santo vino a mi canal
You saw him ask me for forgiveness
ustedes lo visteis me pidió Perdón
also from his own and docet called to the
también desde el suyo y doceta llamó al
Pepe Santos' Channel and explained the truth
Canal de Pepe Santos y explicó la verdad
Okay, what is Juanjo doing? What is it?
Vale qué es lo que hace Juanjo qué es lo
What does Juanjo do about this when he doesn't
que hace Juanjo ante esto cuando él no
has nothing to do
tiene nada que
see worth with a person with whom you are
ver vale con una persona con la que se
assumes that he doesn't want to
supone que no quiere
problems no ca is a good kid eh but
problemas no ca es buen chaval eh pero
One day I have to talk to him because in
un día tengo que hablar con él porque en
private says one thing and then when
privado dice una cosa y luego cuando
When you give him a tap he says it
cuando le dan un toque dice lo
On the contrary, what does this have to do with you?
contrario qué tiene que ver esto contigo
Uncle, I think that in life you have to be
tío creo que en la vida hay que ser
brave and say the same thing in both
valientes y decir lo mismo en los dos
sides are worth or rather the
lados vale o sea el
uncle contacting people so that I
tío contactando con gente para que me
defame me, well there are several who have
difame bueno son varios los que me han
Having said that, a kiss Marilu, but not to
dicho esto eh un beso marilu pero no a
me where they have to Javi in the end
mí a donde tienen que Javi al final le
you have given what I wanted you will do it
has dado lo que quería lo vas a
resurrect I would continue ignoring it all
resucitar yo seguiría ignorándolo todos
would ignore and Juanjo Why does he get into
ignoraría y Juanjo Por qué se mete en
Everything about Javi. Well, explain it to me, Anika.
todo lo de Javi Pues explícame anika
Because if you meet a person in
Porque si tú quedas con una persona en
not mentioning you What's up? I mean, if I
no mencionarte Qué pinta O sea si yo
I deny what Doc Z and Doc Z and Pepe said.
desmiento lo de doc Z y doc Z y Pepe
Saints ask me for forgiveness why you go out
Santos me piden Perdón por qué sales tú
to contradict him when the subject
a llevarle la contraria cuando el tema
it doesn't go
no va
with you dear Javi during the
contigo querido Javi durante la
Roco Carrasco's docuseries is now complete
docuserie de Rocío Carrasco ya quedó
Of course you made some content
claro que tú hiciste un contenido
excellent and this character that did not do
excelente y este personaje que no hacía
nothing is worth it and above all say why
nada vale Y sobre todo decir por qué
lost his job and who was who
perdió su trabajo y quién fue quien
called where he worked
llamó a dónde trabajó
and you are listening to it, that is, docetist
y lo estáis escuchando o sea doceta
enter Pepe Santos' Channel to
entra en el Canal de Pepe Santos para
to say that his dismissal had nothing to do with
decir que su despido no tuvo nada que
see with me but it was completely
ver conmigo sino que fue completamente
It was his fault and in any case Pepe was the one
culpa suya y en todo caso Pepe fue el
who put it and this one comes out to say that
que lo puso y sale este a decir que que
that that no that has to tell the
que que no que tiene que contar la
true to say who that was
verdad decir que de quién era esa
person will have those little things one day
persona esas cositas algún día tendrá
that saying them is worth it I don't know what I don't know
que decirlas él vale Yo no lo que no se
may be saying different things in
puede estar diciendo cosas distintas en
different
diferentes
sides that will surely be what is
lados que seguramente será lo que está
also saying that doz says one thing
diciendo también que doz diga una cosa
from behind And another from the front But you
por detrás Y otra por delante Pero tú
what do you have to
qué tienes que
see what you have to do with what I've gotten into
ver tú qué tienes que ver me he metido
me in your fight with evita
yo en tu pelea con evita
Dynamite, I got into your fight with
Dinamita me he metido yo en tu pelea con
Raquel Moreno and with Olga that you do not
Raquel Moreno y con Olga que no te
they want
quieren
see what you have to do with a
ver tú que tienes que ver con un
with what you have taught me that you
con lo que tenga doceta conmigo que tú
You can join him if you want
te puedes juntar con él si te da la gana
and with all the people I get along with
y con toda la gente con la que me llevo
Bad Of course if it is your mission in the
mal Claro que sí si es tu misión en la
life and and it makes you not to hang out with
vida y y te pone te pone no juntarte con
each one that I fight with
cada uno que me peleo
Do it, everyone dedicates their life to what they
Hazlo cada uno dedica la vida a lo que
can but come out in
puede pero salir en
public for what to complain about
público para para qué para quejarte de
that they are not defaming me
que no me estén difamando a
I'm fine, I say it with affection because it's a
mí vale lo digo con cariño porque es una
person who has suffered a lot and I have
persona que ha sufrido mucho y yo lo
I understand but we have to go straight ahead and
entiendo pero que hay que ir de frente y
don't be afraid and even if you don't take legal
no tener miedo y aunque no tome legales
I think that people should know what he suffered.
que la gente sepa lo que sufrió creo yo
we continue ok or so what do you want for
seguimos vale o sea que quiere por
balls [ __ ] for me ok pay attention to
[__] [__] para mí vale atentos a
Pay attention to this because this is strong
esto atentos a esto que esto es fuerte
Pay attention to this, tell me one thing that is true
atentos a esto di una cosa que es verdad
that in the end what they achieve is to unite us
que al final lo que consiguen es unirnos
even more so this is when I was going to
aún más esto es cuando cuando lo iba a
sue Alexia Rivas who also said
demandar Alexia Rivas que también dijo
that he was going to sue him for telling him that
que lo iba a demandar por decirle que
It was a shame, it's worth looking at the
estaba golfe vale mirar el
comment I honestly think that
comentario yo Honestamente creo que
You are right to expose this. There is nothing.
haces bien en exponer esto No hay cosa
better for A Gang of Friends than
mejor para Una Pandilla de amigos que
have an enemy
tener un enemigo
common for a gang to hear this
común para Una Pandilla de escuchar Esto
Okay, do you remember when Troy burned?
vale os acordáis cuando ard de Troya
He said the other day that they had to
dijo el otro día que tuvieron que
expel the pppa from the unions and from
expulsar a la pppa de las uniones y de
the alliances because every time they
las alianzas porque cada vez que se
they all united and that they had something not
unían todos no y que tenían algo no
Host, a nonsense came out of
[__] salía una una tontería de
Javi's sentence or they were
Sentencia de Javi o lo estaban
canceling because Marina said I don't know what
cancelando porque Marina dijo no sé qué
of Dana or that every time they had
de la Dana o que cada vez que tenían
Something Peppa screwed up, okay? Listen
algo la Peppa la cagaba vale Escuchar
These friends who have a common enemy do not
esto amigos que tener enemigo común no
There is nothing better for a Gang of
hay nada mejor para Una Pandilla de
friends who have an enemy in
amigos que tener un enemigo en
common This is what unites them
común Esto es lo que les une
family is not love it is called
familia no es amor se llama
I have an obsession, for example.
obsesión ties la yo por ejemplo
They will surely want to make contacts with
seguramente querrán hacer contactos con
youtubers I'm convinced but no no no
youtubers estoy convencido pero no no no
because I have worked all my life
porque yo me he trabajado toda mi vida
in my audience, it's worth giving it away
en mi público como para regalárselo vale
Here's what he's always said okay
aquí es lo que él siempre ha dicho vale
that had its channel closed to
que tenía su canal cerrado a
collaborations for not giving publicity to
colaboraciones por no darle publicidad a
Small youtubers Okay, that's it.
youtubers Pequeños Vale que eso es lo
What happened to you with Mik Vasco and me?
que le ha pasado con mik Vasco y me
glad it's worth it obviously mik Vasco he
alegro vale evidentemente mik Vasco él
He took Mik Vasco to his channel and what if
se llevaba mik Vasco a su canal y Y si
You see Mika, I mean, it's that the one from El de
veis la Mika O sea ya es que el de El de
TV Top no longer publishes statistics.
TV top ya no publica las estadísticas
But this is something he knows. This is
Pero esto es algo que él lo sabe Esto es
something he knows And if he denies it
algo que él lo sabe Y si lo niega lo
we can teach it too, okay
podemos enseñar también vale
and the statistics of Mik Vasco during
e las estadísticas de mik Vasco durante
the whole live show is worth it, imagine these are
todo el directo vale imagínate Estos son
9 o'clock okay These are 10 and These are
las 9 vale Estos son las 10 y Estos son
the 23 that when mica ends, well then
las 23 que cuando termina mica Vale pues
This is Juanjo Vale's channel.
la Este es el canal de Juanjo vale Este
It's Juanjo's channel and it goes like this.
es el canal de Juanjo va así sus
live shows go like this and when the 10 o'clock arrives
directos van así y cuando llegan las 10
men1 of the night ago
men1 de la noche hace
This is why because it has been made known
esto por qué Porque la ha dado a conocer
to his audience and he has taken it
a su público a mik y se la ha llevado
Obviously, who is going to see you for
evidentemente Quién va a verte a ti para
sleeping is fine but let's say it doesn't have
dormir está bien pero vamos que no tiene
sense you know mik is the one who is
sentido sabes la mik es la que lo está
exploding the live shows that is the
reventando los directos que es la el
most-watched live heart channel
canal más visto de directo del corazón
mik Vasco who is still following
mik Vasco que todavía se sigue
Urdangarn keeps talking with 5 or
manteniendo hablando urdangarín con 5 o
6000 viewers don't see you
6000 espectadores no tú a ti no te ve
Nobody You have a channel with 600,000
nadie Tú tienes un canal con 600000
subscribers who have 6000 visits in
suscriptores que tiene 6000 visitas en
the
los
Mik Avio videos right away, you have to go
vídeos mik avio enseguida que hay que ir
alone and snuggle
sola y acurrar
exactly he was collaborating here okay
exactamente estuvo colaborando aquí vale
and at the moment how such people left
y en el momento que tal la gente se fue
and he knows it He changed his schedule from the
y él lo sabe Él cambió su horario de las
10 to 9 to start an hour earlier
10 a las 9 para empezar una hora antes
that mik and he starts starts no And when
que mik y él empieza empieza no Y cuando
over here when it's already at 900,000
por aquí cuando ya va por 900000
spectators at the moment that mik
espectadores en el momento que mik se
connects makes people boom because they know
conecta hace la gente pum porque sabe
that mica has its enemy on its side
que mica tiene su horilla enemigo en
common Common enemy Common enemy
común Enemigo en común Enemigo en común
Hey, I collaborate with small and medium-sized people.
eh yo colaboro con gente pequeña mediana
and big but what I have learned is
y grande pero lo que sí he aprendido es
that many people who are the only ones but not me
que mucha gente que lo único pero no a m
where they have to go too far
a donde tienen que demasiado has
endured Javi your community always
aguantado Javi tu comunidad siempre
The king bangs on the table and
contigo El rey da un golpe en la mesa y
the mice run away a kiss a
los ratones salen corriendo un beso un
I don't kiss you, but I want it to be direct.
beso no pero yo quiero que este directo
It will be so that you can tell me if it is
va a ser para que me digáis si está
justified or not that they return to
justificado o no que se vuelvan a
publish the videos and get answers
publicar los vídeos y que se conteste
Of course, it's not like you want out of nowhere.
claro no es como de la nada vale quieres
Your audience is worth what I have. Of course.
tu público vale lo que s tengo Claro que
I will collaborate on other channels
yo colaborar en otros canales voy a
take a long time, that is, it has to be a thing
tardar mucho o sea tiene que es una cosa
very rare I think the last time was to t
muy rara creo que la última vez fue a t
in plan
en plan
Tania who has a husband convicted of
Tania que tiene un marido condenado por
sexual abuse of a minor during
abuso sexual a una menor durante
Tania, moderator of the channel, years old
años Tania moderadora del canal de
Antonio David Flores who is dedicated to
Antonio David flores que se dedica a
insult everyone and just
insultar a todo el mundo y solamente se
He knows her because he spent 8 months reading one
la conoce por estar 8 meses leyendo una
nonsense sentence for insults in the
chorrada de Sentencia por insultos en la
that I fought with another youtuber who
que yo me peleé con otro youtuber que me
He insulted before and I put him in his place
insultaba antes y yo lo puse en su sitio
with a gin and they sentenced me to 0 euros okay
con un gin y me condenaron a 0 eur vale
8 months Tania reading that sentence that
8 meses Tania leyendo esa sentencia que
I think she is a girl with potential and
creo que es una chica con potencial y
that Tania is a girl with potential
que Tania es una chica con potencial
can do well if you want it to be
puede hacer bien Si quiere que ha
worked very well some direct and
funcionado muy bien algunos directos y
which shows that it has potential
que demuestra que tiene potencial
potential to scream will be no Juan
potencial para chillar será no Juan
potential in the throat no In what does it have
potencial en la garganta no En qué tiene
potential the
potencial la
Tania potentially slum neighborhood
Tania potencialmente barrio bajera no
what else I don't know what but I am
que otra cosa no no sé cuál pero yo es
very rare since I go to your channels and
muy raro Ya que vaya aotus canales y
especially since I'm not going to give away
sobre todo porque yo no voy a regalar a
my audience to no one because then I'm not going to
mi público a nadie porque luego no voy a
give away my audience nobody channel and and
regalar mi público nadie canal y y
notify your cell phones of your
notifican a los móviles de tu de
someone else's community Then no
comunidad de otra persona Entonces no
Here he is snitching because he is very
aquí se está chivando porque es muy
clumsy and leaves all the cards on the
torpi y deja todas las cartas sobre la
table is telling what he feels
mesa se está chivando de lo que siente
With Mik Vasco he starts the live show and
con mik Vasco él empieza el directo y
as it is notified
tal y como se tal y como se notifica el
Direct from Mik Vasco, boom, you can do it
directo de mik Vasco hace pum lo podéis
see I don't know if someone can send me by
ver no sé si alguien me puede mandar por
WhatsApp Lili some of the graphics of
WhatsApp Lili alguna de las gráficas de
TV top and you see it very clearly so that the
TV top y lo veis clarísimo para que la
people see it okay do you remember that I left
gente lo vea vale os acordáis que me fui
a a la or so this was guys this that
a a la o sea esto fue chicos esto que
You're watching this, it's a tweet of mine, okay?
estáis viendo esto es un twit mío vale
This was the first image that was
esta fue la primera imagen que se
published by Antonio Tejado arriving at
publicó de Antonio tejado llegando a
detained arriving at the court in Seville
detenido llegando al juzgado de Sevilla
And tonight I was live on
e esta noche estuve en directo en
telesalseo then I went to the salseria and
telesalseo luego me fui a la salsería y
at 4 in the morning when I finished in
a las 4 de la mañana cuando terminé en
the salsera How I like to work and
la salsería Como me gusta trabajar y
cure them
curármelas
He got dressed and went to the court in Seville
se vistió y se fue al juzgado de Sevilla
to wait for Antonio Tejado to arrive
a esperar que llegase Antonio tejado
I got this picture there was a
conseguí esta imagen allí había un
a lot of people from the press and others to the
montón de gente de prensa y demás a los
that I already know because I have thrown many
que ya conozco porque he echado muchas
hours with them I am not a journalist nor
horas con ellos no soy periodista ni
papari but I have spent many hours with
papari pero he echado muchas horas con
people have to that I would just like
gente a tienen que yo solo me gustaría
that he should stop cheating but I think that
que dejase de engañar pero creo que eso
It will never be. Well, if he is denying you that
nunca será Pues si te está negando que
he has messed with Roco Flores
se haya metido con Rocío flores
eh this image clear while they
eh esta imagen claro mientras que ellos
They passed it on to the agency and such was the
la pasaban a la agencia y tal fue la
first image of Antonio to be published
primera imagen en publicarse de Antonio
roof stopped okay Look what he did
tejado detenido vale Mirad lo que hizo
Juanjo when he opened live that day Here
Juanjo cuando abrió directo ese día Aquí
we see the face of ant I left tomorrow
vemos el rostro de ant he dejado mañana
The singer's nephew enters
el sobrino de la cantante ingresa en
provisional prison that window of the
prisión provisional esa ventana de la
van makes me laugh Because many
furgoneta me hace gracia Porque muchos
media say first
medios dicen primera
image that window of the van to me
imagen esa ventana de la furgoneta me
It's funny because in many media
hace gracia porque en Muchos medios
They say the first image of the old roof and
dicen primera imagen de antoño tejado y
All you see are metal circles and
lo único que ves son círculos de metal y
a background stain And where is the face
una mancha de fondo Y dónde está la cara
which is not the first image because it is not
que no es la primera imagen porque no se
see all the cameras there are
ve bien todas las cámaras que hay de
photos there are all things that need to be done
fotos ahí todas hay cosas que hay que
laugh there are things that you have to laugh or that is
reírse hay cosas que hay que re o sea
Can any of you here help me?
alguien de los que estáis aquí me podéis
explain what it has to do with him that I
explicar qué tiene que ver con él que yo
do a job and get one
haga un trabajo y saque una
exclusive I mean if he has done it in
exclusiva O sea si él lo ha hecho en
sometime during these two years I
algún momento durante estos dos años yo
I have no [ __ ] idea because I don't see His
no tengo ni [__] idea porque no veo Su
content like almost no one else
contenido al igual que casi nadie
already or rather they fixed what Comment or rather
ya o sea fijaron lo que Comenta o sea
but this is something to watch from my live shows
pero esto es de verse los directos míos
integers from p to pa and from all the
enteros de p pa y de de todas las
In the morning when you wake up, check
mañanas cuando se levanta revisar
How many numbers have I had that
Cuántos números he tenido que lo
recognized the other day and check my
reconoció el otro día y revisar mi
account of
cuenta de
Twitter belittles the work like this
Twitter desmerecer el trabajo así
completely
totalmente
FJ but he's like a person with whom
FJ pero es como una persona con la que
you have agreed not to not to not to not to talk about
has quedado en no en no en no hablar de
She is worth exclusive about Olga and Agustn
ella vale exclusiva sobre Olga y Agustín
I got an exclusive that I was
conseguí una exclusiva que la estuve
saying for weeks about a first
diciendo durante semanas de una primera
Well first a breakup of Olga with
bueno primero una ruptura de Olga con
Augustine and then a Reconciliation
Agustín y luego una Reconciliación
Ok, Olga Moreno, as you know, has fulfilled her promise.
vale Olga Moreno como sabéis ha cumplido
48 years old this week Antonio David Flores
48 años esta semana Antonio David flores
has liked it and of course now
le ha puesto me gusta y claro que ahora
remember Olga Moreno who has her
se acuerde de Olga Moreno que tiene su
life made and has her boyfriend and and
vida hecha y que tiene su novio y y
He has his happiness, this is him groping
tiene su felicidad esto es él tanteando
the land because I was commenting
el terreno porque yo estaba comentando
the exclusive even there are people who
la exclusiva inclus hay gente que
try to say that if things go wrong
intenta decir que si l va mal la
Olga's relationship with her Agustn de tien
relación de Olga con su Agustín de tien
I'm telling you that this is false.
que ya os digo que eso es falso que ya
I tell you that this is false because he
os digo que eso es falso porque él le
I would ask Raquel Moreno if she
preguntaría a Raquel Moreno si se
I was talking to her still there now I don't know
hablaba con ella todavía ahí ahora no se
Speak okay But why do you have to deny
habla vale Pero por qué tienes que negar
an exclusive of mine uncle passes by
una exclusiva mía tío pasa de
They ignore me but they try to give
mí pasa de mí pero intentan dar
hopes to the public for I don't know
esperanzas al público para no sé
reconnect a little there something eh The thing
reenganchar un poco ahí algo eh La cosa
It is that Mrs. David has put one
está en que Doña David ha puesto una
news that I think talks about him but
noticia que yo creo que habla de él pero
people try to turn it around and
la gente intenta darle la vuelta y
It means that he talks about and then he came out
quiere decir que habla de y luego salió
that they had seen had been
que se habían visto habían estado
taking something clearly so I say no From
tomando algo clamente así lo digo no De
anyway there are already people who are
todas maneras ya hay gente que está
seeing Olga with Agustina on the street
viendo a Olga con Agustina en la calle
This was when I uploaded a video I remember
Esto fue que yo subí un vídeo me acuerdo
perfectly with the mobile from the
perfectamente con el móvil desde el
my sister's room because someone in
cuarto de mi hermana porque alguien en
Seville told me that they had seen
Sevilla me avisó que habían visto
Agustn and Olga on the street in the middle
Agustín y a Olga por la calle a la media
hour to the half hour
hora a la media hora
uploaded a video clearly so I say
subió un vídeo clamente así lo lo digo
No. Anyway, there are already people who
no De todas maneras ya hay gente que
He's seeing Olga with Agust Ti in the
está viendo a Olga con agustí ti en la
street do not hide because they have never
calle no se esconden porque nunca ha
nothing happened and they don't hide because
pasado nada y no se esconden porque
Nothing has ever happened and now these rumors
nunca ha pasado nada y ya estos rumores
They are dismantling time alone
están desmontando solos el tiempo
always puts everything in its place and there is
siempre coloca todo en su sitio y hay
times when the public is foolish in a way
veces que el público es necio en plan de
that if you tell them that there is nothing
que si se les dice que no hay nada de
problems and this was him throughout the
problemas y esto era él durante toda la
week denying the news that was
semana negando la noticia que estaba
I was saying that it was an exclusive that I gave her
dando yo que fue una exclusiva que la di
I remember perfectly that I go out with
me acuerdo perfectamente que salgo con
the glasses in the car I don't know what about that
la gafa de en el coche no sé qué de que
they had had a Cris vale And he
habían tenido una Cris vale Y él
denying it uncle don't look at me don't look at me
negándolo tío que no me mires que no me
Look very good guys welcome
mires muy buenas chavales bienvenidos
Finally, what did you have to do? Very good
finalmente Qué tuvo que hacer muy buenas
Guys, welcome to a new video of
chavales Bienvenidos a un nuevo vídeo de
Very good guys, dude, they don't follow you.
ju muy buenas chavales tío no te siguen
Juanjo guys don't follow you
chavales Juanjo no te siguen
kids special final breakup
chavales especial ruptura final de
Moreno and Agustn or so they say
Moreno y Agustín o eso es lo que dicen
the networks have been erased for the moment How
la redes de momento se han borrado Cómo
Juanjo, hello guys, welcome to
Juanjo muy buenas chavales Bienvenidos a
a new special from Juan final breakup
un nuevo de Juan especial ruptura final
of Olga Moreno and Agustn eti breakup
de Olga Moreno y Agustín eti ruptura
end of Agustn and Olga, well that's it
final de Agustín y de Olga pu eso es lo
What the networks say at the moment has been
que dicen las redes de momento se han
have mutually deleted each other from Instagram
borrado mutuamente de Instagram han
deleted photos and make you understand the thing
borrado fotos y da entender la cosa de
that this time yes, yes, I am
que de que esta vez sí que sí yo Esta
once yes yes no what I was saying
vez sí que sí no lo que estaba diciendo
I
Yo
practically a
prácticamente hace un
A month later Olga and Agustn returned
mes después volvieron Olga y Agustín
Okay, then Olga and Agustn came back.
vale después volvieron Olga y Agustín
totally on that topic at least I am
totalmente de ese tema al menos yo e
Well, who knows, whether it's for or not?
Pues quién sabe No si es para como para
provoke or simply because it does good
provocar o simplemente porque bueno hace
A month later rumors began that remained
un mes se inicion rumores que quedaron
denials very quickly
desmentidos muy rápido
No
no
How to see that rumor started at the
Cómo a ver ese rumor se inició a lo
better bet on certain means than
mejor aposta por determinados medios que
there was no news
no había noticias
How also because there were little things that
Cómo también porque había cositas que
They saw the people who didn't fit in, they didn't
veían la gente que no encajaba no la
bracelet that suddenly joined it
pulsera que lo unía de repente la
removed what I said in the videos
quitaba lo que yo decía en los vídeos
Juanjo doesn't
Juanjo no me
look at me completely every time
mires deja de verme completamente cada
straight
directo
mine don't look at me it's suffering it's desire
mío no me mires es sufrir son ganas de
suffer Look at what I have told you about the
sufrir Mirad lo que os he dicho de las
statistics
estadísticas
Okay, well, it's not that shameless here, Lili.
vale Bueno aquí no es tan descarado Lili
Here they are not shameless, there are some who
aquí no están descarados hay algunos que
They are more shameless. Look at the graphs of
son más descarados Mira las gráficas de
tubet okay they are going up it's time
tubet vale van subiendo es la hora
It starts at 9 but Pam joins at 10
inicia a las 9 pero a las 10 Pam se pega
a slap down because Open mica
una [__] para abajo porque Abre mica
which at the same time presented to him
que a la vez le presentado a su
Mica audience because it was looted with its
audiencia mica pues se m saqueado con su
community as It is logical because mica
comunidad como Es lógico porque mica
Okay, and you're not to my liking, huh? To me.
vale Y tú no para mi gusto eh Para mi
opinion
opinión
[Music]
[Música]
Eh Eh Eh Eh Eh
Eh Eh Eh Eh Eh
Franc
Franco
I am that with
estáa Yo es que con
this look at this there is with this I have one
esto mira de esto hay con esto tengo una
thing with Fran. I'm just saying
movida con lo de Fran Yo es que
when they mess with my friends or
cuando cuando se meten con mis amigos o
they use my friends, people who
utilizan a mis amigos a gente a la que
I want for your moves or your obsessions
quiero para sus movidas o sus obsesiones
So you have with me I don't know the truth
Así que tiene conmigo No sé la verdad
Look at this, this beginning, very good.
Mira este este este comienzo muy buenas
guys, this start of live
chavales este inicio de directo
belongs to em do you remember is that me
pertenece a em os acordáis es que me
I agree perfectly because I was
acuerdo perfectamente porque yo estaba
on the beach with the kids and with Lorena and
en la playa con los niños y con Lorena y
my name is
me llamó
Fran had something happened with Daniel Sancho
Fran había pasado algo con Daniel Sancho
that you already know that it is a topic that eh
que ya sabéis que es un tema que eh
We are the ones who have had the most audience
somos los que más audiencia ha tenido
with the theme Daniel
con el tema Daniel
Sancho And then Fran called me
Sancho Y entonces me llamó Fran yo
I was in Huelva in Punt Umbra I was And
estaba en huelva en punt umbría estaba Y
Then Fran called me so that
entonces me llamó Fran para que
we did a live show at night And if
hiciéramos un directo por la noche Y si
We're doing a live show tonight with Trium.
hacemos un directo esta noche con trium
I don't know what
no sé qué
and I say clearly
e digo claro
I got up at night and came here to Seville
cogí por la noche me vine aquí a Sevilla
You may remember that I did a live show for the
lo recordaréis e hice un directo por la
night with Fran and with Trium do you remember?
noche con Fran y con trium os acordáis
that Fran messed up a bit at the end and I had
que Fran la lió un poco al final y tuve
that cut a little at the end do you remember
que cortar un poco al final os acordáis
I left that live show at night.
de ese directo me vine por la noche dejé
to the family on the beach to come to
a la familia en la playa para venir a
Seville to do the
Sevilla a hacer el
direct do you remember that direct but
directo os acordáis de ese directo pero
no to you come on let's go we have to
no a a tien venga vamos que hay que
It costs more to reach five than it does for us to reach
cuesta más llegar a cinco que nosotros a
50 a kiss a
50 un beso un
kiss do you remember that live? Not that one
beso os acordáis de ese directo No ese
live had 17,000
directo tuvo 17.000
spectators okay then we will play a
espectadores vale que luego tocaremos un
little he who said that he does not speak of
poco el que ha dicho que no habla de
Daniel Sancho but he does speak but not
Daniel Sancho pero si habla pero no
He speaks but he doesn't clarify, okay. No, it wasn't.
habla pero no se aclara vale No no era
the Jos Luis fair Ah well yes maybe
la feria José Luis Ah bueno sí puede que
outside the fair it is true it may have been
fuera la feria es verdad puede que fuera
I know that I went to Punt Umbra at the fair
la feria yo sé que me fui a punt umbría
with the family that did not do much
con la familia que no hacía no hacía muy
good
buen
time but not to me they have to not you
tiempo pero no a m ae tienen que no te
will respond is allied with Rafael and
va a responder está Aliado con Rafael y
his sad end remember the
su triste final acuérdate de los
members were begging
miembros era de pedigueñeria
It's very bad, very bad. Okay, then look at it.
es muy mala mu mala Vale pues mirar lo
Look how it opens directly. This is what I
que Mirad Cómo Abre directo Esto me lo
They send because I don't see anything of this
mandan porque yo no veo nada de este
man evidently like him if he sees it
hombre evidentemente como el si lo ve
I don't give a [ __ ] about what comes up
mío me interesa una [__] lo que suba
This man, but this is sent to me
este hombre pero que esto me lo mandan
the next day is worth the next day
al día siguiente vale al día siguiente
Please listen to it carefully and
escucharlo Atentamente por favor y
tell me why what need
decirme que por qué Qué necesidad
Welcome to a new video from juanjus
Bienvenidos a un nuevo vídeo de juanjus
How are you tonight, gentlemen? Hello.
Cómo estáis esta noche señores Hola
Patricia ypes Hello Pili Hello ngeles
Patricia ypes Hola Pili Hola Ángeles
Domnguez Hello from the fresh Isabel Villar
Domínguez Hola del fresca Isabel Villar
Notorius or Notorius these days of football
notorius o notorius estos dí de fútbol
We've seen you less. Hello Patti, let's go.
te hemos visto menos Hola patti ue vamos
to start little by little before anything else
a empezar poco a poco antes de nada
tell you that it is a real blast
deciros que es una auténtica pasada los
yesterday's data from this channel despite
datazos de ayer de este canal a pesar de
that everyone broadcasts live despite
que todo el mundo emita directos a pesar
that everyone has stars
de que todo el mundo tenga estrellas
famous television
famosos televisión
all that despite the fact that everyone
todo que a pesar de que todo el mundo
broadcast live and even though the whole
emita directos y a pesar de que todo el
world has television stars
mundo tenga estrellas de televisión
who who
quién quién
had those who opened directly that day
tuvo Quiénes abrieron directo ese día
with whom they opened live that night
con quiénes abrieron directo esa noche
with television stars only me
con estrellas de la televisión solo yo
so I make some allusion here
por o sea yo hago aquí alguna alusión
from the live that he has had the
de El directo que haya tenido él la
night before I have no idea what
noche antes que no tengo ni idea de lo
what does this man do? This
que haga este hombre Este
Random than the numbers we have had
Random que los números que hemos tenido
even though uncle we had 17000
a pesar de que tío tuvimos 17000
spectators you are not a competition
espectadores no eres una competencia
for me Put it in the
para mí Métetelo en la
head I'm not competing with you
cabeza no estoy competiendo contigo lo
What I do is not what you do
que hago yo no es lo que haces
You don't know the competition that
tú no es que no sé la competencia que
has with me compare yourself with Mika yes Mika
tiene conmigo compárate con Mika si Mika
has Look, I have twice as much as you.
tiene Mira yo tengo el doble que tú
Juanjo every night of spectators
Juanjo todas las noches de espectadores
but Mika has twice as much
pero es que Mika tiene el doble que
I compare you with
yo compárate con
Mika compate Mike Marina I don't know if he wants to
Mika compate Mike Marina No sé si querrá
come up one day to answer what you
subir un día para contestar lo que a lo
that he dedicated to her a month ago
que le dedicó a ella hace un mes que se
He also started to get involved against Marina for
puso a meterse contra Marina también por
face to face now we will go to
la cara por la cara ahora iremos a
Marina tambaku do not understand each other and it is the
Marina tambaku no se entienden y es el
Odok's love has you, you're great, Javi.
amor odok te tiene eres grande Javi
My darling, a kiss, thank you queen for that
bonito mío un beso gracias reina por eso
people have stayed
la gente se ha quedado
Well if it were just this comment
aquí Bueno si fuera solo este comentario
but listen now uncle we
pero es que escuchar ahora tío nosotros
We didn't get off the boat and almost 300,000
no nos bajamos del barco y casi 300.000
visits on this channel and that we follow
visitas en este canal y que seguimos
being the heart channel of Mercado
siendo el canal del corazón de Mercado
most viewed Spanish heart
español más visto el corazón
that then we are going to review the
que no luego vamos aí a repasar los
numbers so that you know the reality of
números para que sepáis la realidad de
the numbers in case there are people who don't know
los números por si hay gente que no se
pay attention to that, it's worth it from the heart live
fija en eso vale del corazón en directo
The one who has the most viewers is Mica
quien más espectadores tiene es mica
Vasco is worth after between Antonio David and
Vasco vale después entre Antonio David y
I have times when I have times when
yo que hay veces que tengo yo hay veces
that he has Vale and then they are
que tiene él Vale y ya después e están
Well, these channels Juanjo la la
Pues los canales estos Juanjo la la
Tania, Peppa, the Trojan horse and others
Tania la Peppa el ar de Troya y demás
okay Not on visit on visit
vale No en visita en visita
and Okay if you don't want to count my channel
e Bueno si no quiere contar mi canal
main if you don't want to count my channel
principal si no quiere contar mi canal
that my channel is not telesalseo my channel
que mi canal no es telesalseo mi canal
It's Javi Oliveira But well if not
es Javi oliveira Pero bueno si no lo
They want to count if only we
quieren contar si solamente nos
we focus on the heart on TV, I don't know
centramos en el corazón la tele no sé
What Javid Speaking clearly is the one who most
qué javid Hablando claro es el que más
visits have neither short nor direct
visitas tiene adás ni short ni directo
Javi is okay, well, I'm sure I'll add up.
Javi vale bueno Seguramente yo si sumo
the three channels that are mine, all three
los tres canales que son míos los tres
channels But well Javi I don't know I don't
canales Pero bueno Javi No lo sé no me
I have compared nor wish the best to
he Comparado ni le deseo lo mejor a
everyone I'm not competing But it's that
todos no estoy compitiendo Pero es que
I don't, I don't do the same thing they do
yo no yo no hago lo mismo que hacen
all the others I will do you one day
todos los demás yo un día te hago un
report one day I become a gossip of
reportaje yo un día me hago salseo de
the youtuber another day I'll do it for you but it's
los youtuber otro día te hago pero es
What do I care? But well, not you.
que qué me importa Pero bueno tú no tú
Tania type, Peppa type, and those Juanjo people
tipo Tania tipo Peppa Y esa gente Juanjo
Nobody can take it away from you Nobody can take it away from you
noos lo quita nadie Si os lo quita nadie
He takes it away from you, he takes it away from you for 24 hours, my love
os lo quita os lo quita 24 horas corazón
Diego Arrabal takes it from you, he has more
os lo quita Diego arrabal tiene más
visits that Juanjo Albero Men has
visitas que que Juanjo albero mené tiene
more visits than
más visitas que
Juanjo and last piece of information, last piece of information that is not
Juanjo y último datoo último dato que no
I have seen it nor am I going to see it in
lo he visto ni yo vamos a verlo en
direct okay we are now very close very
directo vale estamos ya muy cerquita muy
close to those who are interested in how this is going
cerquita de los que esto interet como va
Pando we are very close to the
Pando estamos muy cerquita de los
594,000 was you teaching the social
594,000 fuite tú enseñando el social
Blade subscribers of crazy crazy it
Blade suscriptores de locos de locos lo
that is happening this crazy month and is
que está pasando este mes de loco y está
with 1000 spectators But well, which one?
con 1000 espectadores Pero bueno ha cuál
If he wants to celebrate that, no, I don't have to.
si él quiere celebrar eso No no tengo
nothing against that 17,000 subscribers
nada en contra de eso 17000 suscriptores
17,000 subscribers in the last 30
17000 suscriptores en los últimos 30
crazy days what's happening and that
días de locos lo que está pasando y eso
that we are returning again to
que estamos vuelto volviendo otra vez a
the horizontal direct ones because there are
los directos horizontales porque hab
a lot of claim and we are making two
mucho reclamo y estamos haciend dos
live at night Well I don't know if
directos por la noche Bueno no sé si
This remains so if we do it others
esto queda así si lo haremos otras
ways but at times the data of
maneras pero de momentos los datazos de
yesterday from this channel even though everything
ayer de este canal a pesar de que todo
the world directly even though the whole
el mundo directos a pesar de que todo el
world has famous television stars
mundo tenga estrellas famosos televisión
We didn't download anything on bco and
todo nosotros no lo bajamos en bco y
almost 300,000 visits in this part of your
casi 300.000 visitas en esente de tu
reflection is really cool because
reflexión es una auténtica pasada porque
We are client Our goal Our
estamos cliendo Nuestro objetivo Nuestro
way It was to make entertainment without
camino Era hacer entretenimiento sin
kill no one to get those hoes to
matar a nadie conseguir que esos hos de
internet fores disappear that you
internet fores desaparezcan que se te
put the internet name does not come out
pone el nombre de internet no salga
no nonsense, no thing that you
ninguna tontería ninguna cosa que te
you can embarrass yourself in life
puedas avergonzar en la vida
either
o
sea Listen to this eh again Eh This is
sea Escuchar esto eh otra vez Eh Esto es
all because I did a live show with Fran
todo porque yo hice un directo con Fran
and we swept it away okay Listen
y arrasamos vale Escuchar
This without any comments other than that
esto sin comentarios más que que la
people waiting for your reflection is
gente pendiente de tu reflexión es
really cool because we are
auténtica pasada porque estamos ciendo
Our goal Our path Was
Nuestro objetivo Nuestro camino Era
make entertainment without killing anyone
hacer entretenimiento sin matar a nadie
get those that we are doing
conseguir que esos que estamos haciendo
entertainment without killing anyone good
entretenimiento sin matar a nadie bueno
Okay, okay, yes, the titles a little bit.
bueno vale Sí los títulos un poco
regulinchi fores that disappear that are
regulinchi fores que desaparezcan que se
put the internet name and nothing comes out
pone el nom internet no sale ninguna
nonsense no thing that you can
tontería ninguna cosa que te puedas
embarrass in life that if they put your
avergonzar en la vida que si te ponen tu
name on the internet does not appear at all
nombre en internet no sale ninguna
nonsense or anything you can
tontería ni ninguna cosa que te puedas
embarrass this has already been done on several occasions
avergonzar esto ya lo ha hecho en varias
occasions that refer to the articles
ocasiones que se refiere a los artículos
that appear in my press about faca al
que salen en prensa míos sobre faca al
stalker I had who posted a
acosador que tuve no que publicó un
pile of [ __ ] on me My address
montón de mierd sobre m Mi dirección
calling my family pedophiles all
llamando pedófilo a mi familia todas
those things no
esas cosas no
and yes, these press articles of
e sí los artículos de prensa estos de de
[ __ ] no
[__] no
and I [ __ ] on press articles
e que me cago en los artículos de prensa
because I have more impact than
porque yo tengo más repercusión que
any article that they take from me
cualquier artículo de que me saquen
Okay, and the guy starts throwing [ __ ] at me.
vale Y el tío se pone a tirarme [__]
So if you search my name on Google
con que si buscan mi nombre en Google
appears
aparece
What is more important is everything fulfilling the
qué más importante todo cumpliendo la
law and complying above all with everything
ley y cumpliendo sobre todo todo
fulfilling the moral law of each one
cumpliendo la ley moral de cada uno el
feeling well I saw is a good one
sentimiento bien vi es una hacas bien
never passes anyone, no one more than anyone
nunca pasa de nadie nadie más que nadie
and we are fulfilling that, that is to say this
y eso lo estamos cumpiendo o sea este
speech of this speech
discurso de este discurso
[Music]
[Música]
of us here we do not have Stars of
de nosotros aquí no tenemos Estrellas de
the TV Well if I have them what is it
la tele Bueno si las tengo qué cuál es
the problem
el problema
It's something negative, that is, it's supposed to be
es algo negativo o sea se supone que es
a problem I think is a good thing no
un problema Yo creo que es algo bueno no
This speech is not about starting the live show
este discurso no de empezar el directo
Here are 100 Stars of the
aquí 100 Estrellas de la
TV and if you search for our name on
tele y si buscan nuestro nombre en
Google doesn't show anything strange
Google no sale nada raro por
why do you have to throw [ __ ] at me
qué por qué me tienes que tirar [__]
What have I done to you today?
qué es lo que te he hecho yo el día
before to
antes a
This is what someone can explain to me what
esto o sea Alguien me puede explicar qué
It's what I had done the night before
es lo que había hecho la noche antes
so that this man has to me
para que este hombre me tenga que
remember the press articles that I
recordar los artículos de prensa que me
take out or the harassment they do to me or the
saquen o el acoso que me hagan o las
defamation or [ __ ] why what is it
difamaciones o la [__] por qué qué es
what he had done to her
lo que le qué es lo que le había hecho
I the night before this
yo las noche antes a este
uncle to have
tío tener
audience But you don't have Amador in
audiencia Pero tú no tienes Amador en
your
tus
direct But you do not have the Yahwe
directos Pero tú no tienes a la yahwe
So he's throwing [ __ ] at me because I've
O sea me está tirando [__] porque he
had 17000
tenido 17000
spectators a kiss Salome where
espectadores un beso Salomé dónde
you were walking and you have all my support
andabas m ae tienen que todo mi apoyo
Javi, patience has a limit, no no.
Javi la paciencia tiene un límite no no
I have been silent all this time
yo todo esto he estado callado esto
Obviously you are telling me that this is
evidente me estáis diciendo que esto es
by fair yes it would be one of the
por feria sí la sería una de las
seasons of Daniel Sancho I imagine
temporadas de Daniel Sancho me imagino
that of the
que la del
trial I mean if I'm not telling you
juicio O sea si yo no te estoy diciendo
nothing I have your videos
nada tengo tus vídeos
lined What for
forrados A qué
comes to What does a person come to be?
viene A qué viene que una persona O sea
what is it that what is it that what is it that
qué es lo que le qué es lo que qué es lo
what I did the night before to this
que le hice yo la noche antes a este
man I don't think it contains the
hombre Yo no creo que lo contene la
death I would not die because I would be
muerte yo a muerte no porque le estaría
The press is very bad, but I don't know.
muy mal la prensa pero es que no sé cen
After this one I don't think so either, Fran. I'm with Fran.
despu esta tampoco creo Fran yo con Fran
a person who I have always said no
una persona que siempre lo he dicho no
I like it, he doesn't like it, Fran, I like it, I know.
me gusta no le gusta Fran me gusta Yo sé
which is very loved by the people but
que es muy querido por la gente pero a
I don't like it but he doesn't like it he doesn't like it
mí no me gusta pero no le gusta no le
I like Fran, I like him since the time of
gusta Fran me gusta ya desde la época de
TV, that is, I'm into documentaries
la tele o sea yo soy de los documentales
De la Fuente is truly the best Felix.
de verdad de de la Fuente el mejor Félix
Rodrguez de la Fuente The documentaries
Rodríguez de la Fuente Los documentales
Fran's are really fake
de verdad los de Fran son de mentira
Okay
vale
collaborators this is commenting on
colaboradores esto es comentando sobre
that I have collaborators, okay?
que yo tengo colaboradores vale Ya sea
Marina or the Corrillo
Marina ya sea el Corrillo
Azucena Santos A giant kiss too
Azucena Santos Un beso gigantón también
and giving likes, okay, we are there 200
y dando likes vale estamos ahí 200
people we got 200 this is a day
personas conseguimos 200 esto es un día
after the
después al
Corrillo and this is what we were doing.
Corrillo y y esto pues lo que estábamos
talking when all this started
hablando cuando empezó todo todo este
direct that what is tiring is
directo que que lo que cansa es
Check the news Search for what
verificar las noticias Buscar de qué
talk
hablar
to to
al al
They are watching TV and have put themselves in A
están viendo la tele se han puesto A
scream How are you family are you okay
chillar Cómo estáis familia estáis bien
either
o
what What are you doing are you okay or
qué Qué hacéis estáis bien o
what everything when there are no topics like that
qué todo cuando no hay temas así
important Teresa yes Also I think that
importantes Teresa sí Además creo que
to be thankful that he is alone Because it is
que agradecer que esté solo Porque es
the more the channel grows, the more
cuando más el canal crece cu los
most viewed live shows I have also seen
directos más vistos a ver también he
said that this year I will not go to the ascend
dicho que este año no no voy aut acens
last me
durarme
here criticizing the issue of having
aquí criticando el tema de que se tenga
collaborators, for example, client
colaboradores yo por ejemplo clente
They will want to make contacts with YouTubers
querrán hacer contactos con youtubers
I am convinced it shows that it has
estoy convencido demuestra que tiene
potential but I am very rare since
potencial pero yo es muy raro Ya que
go to your channels and especially because
vaya a tus canales y sobre todo porque
I'm not going to give my audience many
yo no voy a regalar a mi público muchas
times when you see someone collaborating with
veces cuando veáis alguien colaborar con
many people many times when you see
mucha gente muchas veces cuando veáis a
people collaborate with other people is because
gente colaborar con otra gente es porque
wants the public of that person Okay and
quiere el público de esa persona Vale y
Many people who collaborate so much is because
mucha gente que colabora tanto es porque
on their own they are not worth it and many people who
por sí solos no valen y mucha gente que
He collaborates so much because he doesn't do it alone.
colabora tanto es porque por sí solo no
you are in the audience no we do not depend on nor
vales en audiencia no no dependemos ni
of topics, fashions, or other things. Oh no.
de temas ni de modas ni de otros Ah no
It depends neither on topics nor on fashions nor on
depend ni de temas ni de modas ni de
another is the only youtuber who has
otro es el único youtuber que tiene
60,000 viewers just talking about him
60.000 espectadores él solo hablando de
what you have done during the day is worth it
lo que ha hecho durante el día vale vale
I have mentioned to you before on the subject of
antes os he mencionado sobre el tema de
okay le le this is strong or so this is
vale le le esto es fuerte o sea esto es
strong this is strong this is strong
fuerte esto es fuerte esto es fuerte
such as what we have seen
como como por ejemplo lo que hemos visto
before with
antes con
he is obsessed with you he likes you
do está obsesionado contigo le gusta
compare yourself and try to imitate him
compararse e intentar imitarte a su
community will be able to deceive us not
comunidad podrá engañarla a nosotros no
we love you King has no community if
te queremos Rey no tiene comunidad si
wants it now
quiere ya
and but I want you to have all this
e pero todo esto quiero que que tengáis
always present that this is with a
siempre presente que esto es con un
agreement not to mention each other
acuerdo de no mencionarnos
Eh This is with a no-contest agreement.
Eh Esto es con un acuerdo de no
mention us eh I want you to have it
mencionarnos eh quiero que lo tengáis
present all the time but not to me
presente todo el tiempo pero no a mí a
where they have to and it will be
donde tienen que y ya estará
dusting off the expensive movie suit
desempolvando el traje de cinero cara
crying with laughter face crying with laughter
llorando de risa cara llorando de ris
I understand that joke, all this is with a
entiendo ese chiste todo esto es con un
agreement of each one on his side and I
acuerdo de cada uno por su lado y yo
ignoring him, eh?
pasando de él eh
I've told you before about Doc Z and
hab os he contado antes lo de doc Z y
you have seen here you can see the Setup
habéis visto aquí podéis ver el Setup
Okay, this is not old, this is from now.
vale Esto no es Antiguo esto es de ahora
I have given you before the example of
os he puesto antes El ejemplo de lo de
Doceta is worth it and the guy is no longer that I don't
doceta vale e el tío ya no es que yo no
I mess with him or that he and I are not
me meta con él o que él y yo no estemos
in war he is the one who gets involved in defending
en guerra él es que se mete a defender a
the people I'm with
la gente de la que yo me estoy
defending okay or so this was because
defendiendo vale o sea esto fue porque
They used the entire eastern group of channels
utilizaron todo el grupo este de canales
affected by Javi oliveira cara
afectados por Javi oliveira cara
in love face throws kiss Rosita les
enamorada cara lanza beso Rosita les
they assumed that he did a thing to him
dieron por de hecho el le le hizo un
super pathetic video on the beach as if
vídeo super patético en la playa como si
whether he was a preacher or as if he were a
fuera un predicador o como si fuera un
God that had come down that uncle I mean you
Dios que había bajado que tío O sea tú
you had a channel Leon Lee was a guy who
tenías un canal Leon Lee era un tío que
I had a channel dedicated to me but it's just that
tenía un canal dedicado a mí pero es que
There was a time when it was the channel
tenía una época en la que era el canal
dedicated to me because I visited him
dedicado a mí porque le daba visita
Then he started to suck up to me and
Luego me empezó a hacer la pelota y se
I messed with everyone I had a problem with
metía con todos los que yo tenía un
problem in fact There was a time when
problema de hecho Tuvo una época el
channel dedicated to messing with Juanjo
canal dedicado a meterse con Juanjo a
mess with Joan Plana with everyone who
meterse con Joan plana con todo el que
I used to fight. He had a time in Leol Le.
yo me peleaba Tuvo una época en leol le
in which he was dedicated and I have The
en la que se dedicaba y tengo Las
captures or so we already denied this in
capturas o sea esto ya lo desmentimos en
your day is not the direct one now if it does
su día no es el directo ahora si hace
It is missing again and is denied again
falta otra vez se vuelve a desmentir
Leon was once again an uncle who first
otra vez Leon le fue un tío que primero
he dedicated himself to throwing me then he dedicated himself to
se dedicó a tirarme luego se dedicó a
eat my ass and then in time
comerme el culo y luego al tiempo se
dedicated to eh again to dedicate the channel
dedicó a eh otra vez a dedicar el canal
to me until there was a good day
a mí hasta que hubo un día que bueno
making me some disgusting thumbnails
haciéndome unas miniaturas asquerosas
with disgusting insinuations defam
con unas insinuaciones asquerosas difam
send me insults and there was a day in which
mándame insultándome y hubo un día en el
that I'm already bored and tired
que yo me aburrí ya y me cansé
and I say right now we have a debate
y digo ahora mismo hacemos un debate lo
You have it in the salsera over there
tenéis en el en la salsería por ahí por
the chat will put Lili
el chat va a poner Lili
the name of the live show is Okay, what is it?
el el nombre del directo Vale qué es lo
What happened when he faced a
que pasó pues cuando se enfrentó a un
debate with me in which I said nothing
debate conmigo en el que no le dije nada
eh, I mean, I was calm, Chilto.
eh o sea estuve tranquilo chilto el
debate but it remained
debate pero quedó
humiliated, the debate ended
humillado terminó el debate
crying ended the debate crying
llorando terminó el debate llorando
He couldn't stand a debate, that is, a guy
no pudo soportar un debate o sea un tío
who dedicated his channel to me to touch my
que dedicaba su canal a mí a tocarme los
eggs to me when I finally say why
huevos a mí cuando por fin digo porque
He also dedicated himself to that, which is something
además se dedicaba que eso es una cosa
that don't count The guy was dedicated to
que no cuentan El tipo se dedicaba a
send your audience to spam arm here
mandar a su audiencia a spame arme aquí
in the chat to have a debate with him
en el chat que hiciera un debate con él
He wanted fame for balls, he climbed
por huevos quería fama el trepa por
eggs for eggs for eggs and when I
huevos por huevos por huevos y cuando me
I came back and did the debate, it ended.
volví y le hice el debate terminó el
debate
debate
crying like everyone else, always what happens
llorando como todos siempre lo que pasa
always what always happens Well then
siempre lo que pasa siempre Bueno pues
Now all the channels are allies
ahora todos los canales estos aliados
Association of those affected by Jav Oliveira
asociación de afectados por jav oliveira
They decided to take Leon Lee as well.
le dieron por [__] a Leon lee al igual
that two sets say that he was a guy that I
que dos set decir que era un tío que yo
I kicked out of the internet Poor Leon Lee Leon
eché de internet Pobrecito Leon Lee Leon
read what happened to Leon
lee lo que pasó con Leon
Then read in one of the live broadcasts that
Lee entonces en uno de los directos que
We played Freaky Tuber, eh? Alanne Elena
hicimos de Freaky tuber eh alanne Elena
There we were that night, those of us who knew
el estábamos esa noche los que sabíamos
the story Elena who was alanne who
la historia Elena que estuvo alanne que
was and those of us who are here
estuvo y los que estamos los que
we were okay And he was too and it
estabamos vale Y él también estaba y lo
It's worth it and there you have the debate there.
sabe vale Y ahí tenéis el debate ahí
you have the debate put the title there
tenéis el debate poner por ahí el título
in the debate chat with leol le para
en el chat del debate con leol le para
that people see it in its entirety and know what it is
que la gente lo vea entero y sepa qué es
What happened to Leon Lee watching the debate
lo que pasó con Leon Lee mirar el debate
watch the debate and put it there in the chat
mirar el debate ponerlo ahí en el chat
okay what happened because the debate
vale qué es lo que pasó porque el debate
He ended up crying and tried to throw me away.
terminó Llorando me intentó tirar el
debate with a strike that then
debate con un strike que luego lo
Okay, sure, now he was embarrassed later.
vale claro ahora luego se avergonzaba
Well, don't get involved.
Pues no te metas
with me, I mean you mess with me and if you
conmigo o sea te metes conmigo y si te
I answer you cry then if I don't
respondo lloras pues entonces si yo no
I'm messing with you. Well then, in
me estoy metiendo contigo Bueno pues en
a Freaky tubers as they caught it all
un Freaky tubers como lo cogieron toda
These people are dedicated to Ay Leon Lee was
esta gente se dedicar Ay Leon Lee era
like a soul in pain that we had cast out
como un alma en pena que habíamos echado
poor internet Leon Lee Well in a
internet pobre Leon Lee Pues en un
Freaky tubers we caught and explained the
Freaky tubers cogimos y explicamos la
history of le le with screenshots with
historia de le le con capturas con
tests and we deny it
pruebas y y lo desmentimos
Look what Juanjo did that day
Mirad lo que hizo Juanjo al día
next and also from here send a
siguiente y también desde aquí mandar un
I kiss le of le because these 24 hours
beso a le of le porque estas 24 horas
I'm listening to a lot
Estoy escuchando muchas
nonsense these 24 hours I am
tonterias estas 24 horas Estoy
listening to a lot of nonsense why
escuchando muchas tonterías por qué
because you are seeing why you put yourself to
porque estás viendo por qué te pones a
watch my live shows Juanjo, it's just that I don't no
ver mis directos Juanjo es que yo no no
I understand that I don't see your thing
lo entiendo es que yo no veo lo suyo por
what everyone is doing to see me
qué se ponen todo el mundo a verme son
desire to
ganas de
suffer I have to say that everything
sufrir yo tengo que decir que todo lo
that he said about me at the time he asked me
que dijo de mí en su momento me pidió
apologies
disculpas
and I talked to him for a long time afterwards
y hablé después mucho tiempo con él
say that he did leave the networks because
decir que él sí dejó las redes porque
He was harassed so much that he left the networks because
estaba acosado que dejó las redes porque
I was harassed, well, the networks did not have them
estaba acosado bueno las redes no las ha
left because I was recently
dejado porque hace poco estuve
investigating some things and I was
investigando unas cosas y estuve
talking to people around me and
hablando con gente de su entorno y me
They said they know it's on the networks
dijeron que saben que está en las redes
in some way but they don't know
de alguna forma pero que no saben
exactly how it is worth but that
exactamente de qué forma vale pero que
He left here harassed that I have
se fue de aquí acosado que tengo
audio messages for whoever needs them
mensajes audios para quien los necesite
whoever wants them if I have to be
quien los quiera si tengo que ser
witness I am anywhere Here I am
testigo Yo en cualquier sitio Aquí estoy
Where are you going to be a witness, dude? And what?
yo dónde vas a ser testigo guajo Y qué
you have validity as a witness if you are
validez tienes tú como testigo si eres
a liar You are a liar who is
un mentiroso Eres un mentiroso que está
obsessed with me or rather you don't
obsesionado conmigo o sea a ti no te
could be brought as a witness to a trial
podrían llevar de testigo a un juicio
against me Here I am as a witness but
contra mí Aquí estoy yo de testigo pero
I am that this is really Someone
yo es que esto de verdad O sea Alguien
Can you explain this to me the same as with
me puede explicar esto lo mismo que con
teaches the same as what we have seen
doceta lo mismo que lo que hemos visto
before Fran if he doesn't go with her
antes de Fran si con él no va la
thing if it doesn't go with him, that is, the guy
vaina si con él no va o sea el tío
agree with me that a pact of no
acuerda conmigo en que un pacto de no
aggression between the two of us but
agresión entre nosotros dos pero
Hey, they attack Javi and he gets involved.
eh que agredan a Javi y se mete a
get angry that I defend myself
enfadarse con que yo me defienda de
aggressions or an aggression pact of
agresiones o sea un pacto de agresión de
no aggression between us
no agresión entre nosotros
two in which he gets involved in denying
dos en el que él se mete a desmentir de
that I defend myself from
que yo yo me defienda de
aggressions what does this have to do with him
agresiones qué tiene que ver esto con él
because he has to go out, let's go
porque él tiene que salir vamos si
wants to get out, come out face to face, let's go out
quiere salir sal de cara vamos sal de
face come out face
cara vente sal de cara
Guajo but if you have an agreement with
guajo pero si tú tienes un acuerdo con
someone is not that a strike It is not that no
alguien no es que un strike No es que no
get out of
sal de
face or this is a day
cara o sea esto al día
next this is new Eh This is not from
siguiente esto es nuevo Eh Esto no es de
the time this This is from now eh This
la época esto Esto es de ahora eh Esto
It was that a Freaky tuber went out to
fue que un Freaky tuber salimos a
You can deny it there. Search for the day
desmentirlo por ahí podéis Buscar el día
I don't know if the day will come and he goes out
no sé si al anes saá el día y sale él a
deny us but with you what
desmentir noos de pero contigo qué
So we have a pact of one
va O sea que tenemos un pacto de una
aggression but you get involved in that I don't
agresión pero tú te metes en que yo no
I can defend myself from being attacked by you.
me pueda defender de que me agredan Tú
what are you going on about
de qué vas
obsessed and the tests Well here and in
obseso y las pruebas Bueno aquí y en
another one that no nonsense is said and that
otro mó que no se digan tonterías y que
Don't treat people like idiots
no se trate la gente como idiota que la
people have eyes and people know what
gente tiene ojos y la gente sabe lo que
is to do things well and do the
es hacer las cosas bien y hacer las
bad things Ah you are the one who does it very
cosas mal Ah tú eres el que la hace muy
divinely well so you
bien divinamente así te
Now we'll talk about Loli Nauf.
va ahora hablaremos de lo de Loli nauf
It is a Twitter account that used to be
es una cuenta de Twitter que antes era
hate against me many people know her from
hate contra mí mucha gente la conoce de
the youth is worth it
la chavalería vale
And I currently have peace with it
em Y actualmente tengo una paz con ella
I don't know if it's a cordiality, let's see.
No no sé si una cordialidad una a ver
a peace no we don't have war okay Okay
una paz no no tenemos guerra vale Bueno
Well, pay attention to this, eh, Nauter Flay?
pues atentos a esto eh nauter flay que
It is an account like Javiel Canino Javiel
es una cuenta como javiel canino javiel
wigs that kind of beads this is like
pelucas ese tipo de cuentas esto es como
The naut thing does not take away its exclusivity from the
lo de naut no quita su exclusiva de lo
from the breakup of
de la ruptura de
Play This was because I was in all of them
Play Esto fue porque yo salí en todos
the
los
media because I gave the exclusive of the
medios porque di la exclusiva de la
Auron and Villin breakup
ruptura de auron y villin
auron and vin
auron y vin
come my friend and
vin colega mía y
auron colleague also To the only channel that
auron colega también Al único canal que
has gone to Uron Play to give an interview
ha ido a uron Play a dar una entrevista
It was Javi Oliveira and IB didn't go.
ha sido a Javi oliveira y a IB no ha ido
neither to the Wild
ni ni a the Wild
project I give an exclusive okay I give one
project doy una exclusiva vale doy una
exclusive about their breakup and
exclusiva sobre la ruptura de ellos y a
Juanjo Juanjo seems to you
Juanjo Juanjo le parece
well go out the same night to say that
bien salir la misma noche para decir que
the Nauter exclusive
la exclusiva de nauter
flay this is like nter flay no su
flay esto es como lo de nter flay no su
exclusive on the Play Pues breakup
exclusiva de lo de ruptura de Play Pues
the same eh I have not been first but
lo mismo eh yo no he sido primero pero
I have been
he sido
second
segundo
not just in case
no por si
just in case
acaso por si
perhaps he will mention it again in his
acaso lo vuelve a comentar en su en su
another channel uploading an excerpt on its
otro canal subiendo un extracto en su
The San TV channel uploads an extract that
canal a la San TV sube un extracto que
It's called the split of Auron and Villin and
se llama la ruptura de auron y villin y
his sad
su triste
reason to say that the exclusive is of
motivo para decir que la exclusiva es de
nauter
nauter
flay because I gave it to her because that is
flay porque la he dado yo porque o sea
When you talk about
Cuándo hablas tú de
youtubers if you don't even know the names, it's that
youtubers si no sabes ni los nom es que
We are not like Lafay Naturf, it is an account
no somos como lafay naturf es una cuenta
Hey, the credits for when
Oye los créditos para cuándo los
credits But this is very important
créditos Pero esto es muy importante
because he has an impressive stripe
porque él tiene una rayada impresionante
with the Indian's account or the account of
con la cuenta del Indio o la cuenta de
Joe
Joe
Hunter this is mind-blowing
Hunter esto es alucinante
Not because I don't see the stripe he has
No porque no vea la rayada que tiene él
with the account of Joe Hunter that Joe
con la cuenta del Joe Hunter que Joe
Hunter only puts the data
Hunter lo único que hace poner los datos
of the numbers for when eh that we are
de los números para cuándo eh que somos
always the first to touch all the
los primeros siempre en tocar todos los
sticks we are like eh naturf is an account
palos somos como eh naturf es una cuenta
from Twitter that is brutal is an account
de Twitter que es brutal es una cuenta
that has at that time was a time in
que tiene en esa época era una época en
the one who doesn't even know how to say the name
la que que no sabe ni decir el nombre se
dedicated to that account
dedicaba a esa cuenta a
throw all the gossip at me
tirarme todos los cotillos de de de
youtubers before anyone else and no one wants
youtubers antes que nadie y nadie quiere
mention it until
mencionarlo hasta
this until this because they did not want it to be
esto hasta esto porque no querían que se
knew we were talking about what I had done
supiese hablamos de que yo había hecho
a video a while ago talking about Hasta
un vídeo hace tiempo hablando de Hasta
that's these are This is another one eh This is
eso estos son Este es otro eh Este es
Another live stream from Auronplay's girlfriend
otro directo de la novia de auronplay
auronplay is one of the most popular youtubers
auronplay es un youtuber de los más
important from here in Spain and now
importantes de aquí de España y ahora
It turns out that all the media say everything
resulta que dicen todos los medios todo
I think it started with a tweet, I don't know if
creo que empezó con un tweet no sé si
was
era
Nauf I don't know if it was Nauter Flay or something like that
nauf no sé si era nauter flay o algo así
uncle you are
tío estás
obsessed obsessed was an exclusive of mine
obseso obseso era una exclusiva mía
Javi Oliveira appeared in all the media
salió en todos los medios Javi oliveira
Release it
Suelta la
exclusive auron Play broken sad vingan
exclusiva auron Play vingan roto triste
final face rolling with laughter face
final cara revolviéndose de la risa cara
I turned from laughing face throwing a
revolvi de la risa cara lanzando un
kiss is worth obsessed
beso vale obsesionado
here we are speaking in outer
em aquí que estamos hablando en outer
flap because this is clearly important
flap porque esto claro es importante
to then remember the
para luego recordar el
eh the obsession he has
eh la obsesión que tiene él
with these accounts
con con las cuentas estas del
Indian I don't know if I have one here
Indio No sé si tengo yo aquí una
capture but there was a
captura pero hubo un
day Ah I don't have it
día Ah no la tengo
Uncle, there was a day when I said,
tío es que hubo un día tío que digo
mother of
madre de
God there was a day this is the day Look man
Dios hubo un día este es el día Mira tío
When they sent me this I was
yo cuando me mandaron esto yo estaba
doing somersaults eh
dando voltereta eh
This is a screenshot of a video that uploads
esto es una captura de un vídeo que sube
It's in the morning but well, like no
é por la mañana pero bueno como No
I would know how to take coffee that day or whatever
sabría tomar el café ese día o lo que
be a kiss
sea un beso
Roman and I recorded this video with this in the
Román y grabo Este vídeo con esto en la
screen I can't do
pantalla no puedo hacer
zoom Ah I can't do it
zoom Ah no puedo hacer
zoom
zoom
here he recorded a video with this in the
aquí grabó un vídeo con esto en la
screen uncle this is an account too
pantalla tío esto es una cuenta también
dedicated to jav oliveira vale In fact
dedicada a jav oliveira vale De hecho
Look at the recommendations that appear to you
Mira los recomendados que le aparecen a
Juanjo, well, those are the Wilson accounts.
Juanjo pues son el Wilson Esas cuentas
Okay
vale
Uncle This was the day this is strong eh
tío Esto fue el día esto es fuerte eh
also eh for the obsession eh
también eh para la obsesión eh
once again Javi is right And Javi
una vez más Javi tiene razón Y Javi
always strong eat me kiss face
siempre fuerte la me comid beso cara
blowing a kiss face blowing a kiss
lanzando un beso cara lanzando un beso
the best community we are going to finish
la mejor comunidad ya vamos a acabar
This first objective now if you want
Este primer objetivo ahora si queréis
I put another voucher
pongo otro vale
Hey, I can do mysteries. This is a
Eh ican doid mysteries Esto es una
Twitter account that was dedicated to
cuenta de Twitter que se dedicaba a
take out a clip of me turning green too
sacar clip mío poniéndome verde también
and in the end the same as always, no things
y en fin lo mismo de siempre no e cosas
that he can't stand. That is, if he can't stand
que él no soporta O sea si él no soporta
the caricatures of the Indian, that is, he is not
las caricaturas del Indio o sea él no
supports the caricatures of the Indian and the
soporta las caricaturas del indio y del
Joe Hunter and all this and it goes with
Joe Hunter y todo esto y se lleva con
all these accounts because Gan outer
todas las cuentas estas porque Gan outer
flay also spoke What happens is that
flay también habló Lo que pasa que eso
we'll leave it for later
lo vamos a dejar para más adelante
True Juanjo, what you said
verdad Juanjo lo de
Nafay Cotilla and others, we're going to leave it
nafay Cotilla y demás lo vamos a dejar
for later ok Juanjo eh it's put
para más adelante vale Juanjo eh se pone
This was the
Esto fue el
day This was the day I changed him
día Esto fue el día que yo le cambié de
I named Javi the puny and I gave him the
nombre a Javi el canijo y le puse la
sauce shop
salsería
Okay, so he starts talking to a
Vale pues él se pone a hablar con una
account of these hatred towards
cuenta de estas de odio hacia
Thank you so much in the end I didn't put the videos up.
mí gracias al final no puse los vídeos
I'll do it tomorrow. Javi's thing smells like it's
lo haré Mañana lo de Javi huele que es
by the time the sentence is published, no
para cuando se publique la sentencia no
they run into the Canal or something like that you know that
se topen al Canal o algo así sabe que
can
puede
sink his jump to television
hundir su salto a la tele
Juanjo recommend me whatever
Juanjo recomiéndame lo que sea que
you ate tonight
comieras esta noche
Juanjo starts talking, the first thing is the
Juanjo se pone a hablar lo primero es la
importance and the F so they have with
importancia y la F asía que tienen con
These sentences are so stupid, man, what are they?
las sentencias estas chorras tío que son
silly sentences that if everyone
sentencias chorras que si todos
we had the time and the money and the
tuviéramos el tiempo y el dinero y la
bitterness of sending everyone to Kiki. Well
amargura de de mandar a todo kiki Pues
we would all be doomed with that
todos estaríamos condenados con esa
nonsense a sentence for insult and the
chorrada una sentencia por insulto y el
colleague believed that if I had to
colega se creía que si yo tuviera que
that going on TV would ruin it for me
que ir a la tele me lo hundiría una
sentence in which I 6 years ago
sentencia en la que yo hace 6 años le
I said hair flattery to a YouTuber, trust yourself
dije pelos coba a una youtuber fíate tú
what you start talking about with an account
lo que se pone a hablar con una cuenta
of
de
hate Why do you even have to
odio Por qué tienes ni siquiera que
to know and be aware of whether I have
saber y estar pendiente de si de si he
changed my channel name
cambiado el nombre de mi canal
secondary Juanjo I changed the name of
secundario Juanjo yo cambié el nombre de
my secondary channel because it seemed to me
mi canal secundario porque me parecía
the salsa bar is more commercial than Javier
más comercial la salsería que Javier
canine or the puny one okay you changed the
canino o el canijo vale tú cambiaste el
name of your secondary channel because you
nombre de tu canal secundario porque te
you pointed out that you were
pusiste a señalar de que tú estabas
registering your company so that no one
registrando tu empresa para que nadie
I could put your name on your title that
pudiera poner tu nombre en tu título que
You thought you could strike for
te creías que podías poner strike por
to put the name of your channel in the
que pusieran el nombre de tu canal en el
title and it turns out that you had a
título y resulta ser que tú tenías un
YouTube channel with a name that
canal de YouTube con un nombre que
It was registered by Mediaset that it was
estaba registrado por mediaset que era
couch potatoes I changed my name from my
teleadictos yo cambié mi nombre de mi
channel because I felt like it you do it
canal porque me dio la gana tú lo
you changed because you took a name that
cambiaste porque cogiste un nombre que
was registered
estaba registrado la
marks and begins to speculate as if Juanjo
marca y se pone especular como si Juanjo
you have more
tenéis ustedes más
worry and you live the sentences more
preocupación y vivís más las sentencias
These are mine and my God that I, I, do not
estas mías y los Dios mío que yo yo no
I don't give it any importance, I don't know
le doy ninguna importancia a mí no se me
I don't spend my life on this.
da a mí no se me va la vida en esto me
They seem like nonsense. Well, if I have to
parecen chorradas Pues si tengo que
pay a fine to someone or do I have to
pagarle una multa a alguien o tengo que
pay someone something for having done it
pagarle algo a alguien por haberle he
said four things then I will pay it
dicho cuatro cosas pues la pagaré Me
I will do
haré
responsible because I have told him so because I
responsable pues se lo he dicho pues me
They have said whatever I have answered
han dicho lo que sea le he respondido
Well, well, if justice says that
Pues bueno Pues si la justicia dice que
I have to pay you how much was it 0 euros
le tengo que pagar Cuánto fue 0 eur lo
of flats Well, my thing is
de planas Bueno pues lo de mi está
obviously resorting to it because it is not
recurriendo evidentemente porque no
I do not agree with that at all
estoy nada de acuerdo con esa
Sentence but you start talking
Sentencia pero que tú te pongas a hablar
with multi-account what do you think it is?
con multicuenta que te crees que es que
the problem they have had and what
el problema que han tenido y lo
frustrated that they are is that they
frustrados que están es que ellos
They expected that if a sentence came out
esperaban que si salía una sentencia
where I am
donde me
they condemned it okay if one came out
condenaran vale que si salía una
sentence where they condemned me
sentencia donde me condenaran que a mí
People were going to stop seeing me Juanjo
me iban a dejar de ver la gente Juanjo a
People don't care if I get 25
la gente no le importa si me ponen 25
Stupid sentences like that are not
sentencias estúpidas de esas no son
criminal sentences such as those they have
sentencias penales como las que tienen
some of your collaborators who now do it
algunos colaboradores tuyos que ahora lo
we will try you also have
trataremos también tú tienes
collaborators with sentences
colaboradores con sentencias
very
muy
serious and those sentences don't matter to you
serias y esas sentencias no te importan
Juanjo a sentence for insult of
Juanjo una sentencia por insulto de
right to honor does not matter to the
derecho al honor no le importa a la
People, if they give me 40 this year
gente si me ponen 40 este año
Juanjo, people will continue to see me.
Juanjo la gente me va a seguir viendo a
me and not to
mí y no a
you and I will continue to have the best
ti y voy a seguir teniendo la mejor
community of the world and of everything
comunidad del mundo y de todo
internet and you will continue to suffer for it
internet y tú vas a segir sufriendo por
Don't look at me, man, you're having a bad time.
eso no me mires tío que lo pasas mal no
be aware of whether I change the name
estés pendiente de Si cambio el nombre
to the
al
Channel that is not a desire to suffer
Canal que son ganas de sufrir no es
good for you
bueno para ti
Juanjo tot
Juanjo tot
eh before continuing with the topic of
eh antes de seguir con lo del tema de
the multi-accounts Well yes I connect with
las multicuentas Bueno sí empalmo con
We are going to comment on the accounts
las cuentas vamos a comentar una
little thing It turns out that Juanjo
cosilla Resulta ser que Juanjo
He has seen fit not only to insult me
ha tenido a bien no solamente insultarme
during these two
durante estos dos
years excusing himself no longer that I
años excusándose ya no en que yo lo
mention it because he knows perfectly well
mencione porque él sabe perfectamente
that I don't talk about him and that I deleted the
que yo no hablo de él y que borré los
videos about him but he has had to
vídeos sobre él sino que ha tenido a
Well insult me because well he says that
bien insultarme porque bueno él dice que
that since I don't mess with him, well
que que como yo no me meto con él pues
that people on Twitter are messing with him
que se meten con él la gente de Twitter
and the FJ and the I don't know who because I
y el FJ y el no sé quién porque yo los
I command because I command them attentively
mando porque yo los mando atento
They do not lie and deceive and it must be reported
no mienten y engañan y hay que denunciar
These things are worth it, let's act as if
estas cosas vale vamos a hacer como si
out the documentary of Rocio Carasco with
fuera el documental de Rocio carasco con
a 3-minute video that goes on
un vídeo de 3 minutos que anda en
internet that is made by
internet que es hecho por
German wait a moment for the announcer
Germán esperar un momento el locutor de
salami who has made a video of the song
salame que ha hecho un vídeo del tema de
Antonio Tejado as if he were Save Me
Antonio tejado como si fuera sálvame
Okay, in homage to them this is like
vale en homenaje a ellos esto es como
when you trust what you compare, eh, or rather
cuando fíate tú lo que compara eh o sea
He is remembering Germn and Slvame
se está acordando de Germán y de sálvame
and he thinks about his obsession
y él piensa en su obsesión
A person cannot attack because he is already
una persona no puede atacar porque ya un
judge has said that it cannot be as
juez ha dicho que no se puede como
when a person has said that he cannot
cuando una persona ha dicho que no puede
attack because a judge has said not to
atacar porque un juez ha dicho que no se
can but orders someone else to do it But
puede pero manda a otro hacerlo Pero
send someone else to do it, I say because I
manda a otro hacerlo digo porque a mí
When I saw it, it seemed to me
cuando lo he visto me ha parecido
disgusting and I like my German as
asqueroso y mi Germán a mí me gusta como
What this would surely be is that the day
lo c esto sería seguramente que el día
before then I would do some live shows for him
antes pues le haría algún directo
Juanjo, how do you interpret life?
Juanjo tú cómo interpretas la vida
colleague, how do you interpret life?
colega tú cómo interpretas la vida
Juanjo Do you think so? Of course.
Juanjo Tú crees que si a ti pues claro
I think that's what you believe
creo que es eso lo que ustedes os creéis
Hey, I do love you.
eh yo sí que te quiero
glo I think that's it. Like you.
glo yo creo que es eso Como tú lo
they interpret no. So if I am in a
interpretan no O sea que si a mí en una
in the lawsuit of Joan Plana that I
en la demanda de Joan plana que a mí me
Please let me refrain from violating your
pongan que me abstengan de vulnerar su
honor of course what you think is
honor claro lo que ustedes pensáis es
that I can't talk about Joan Plana anymore
que yo no puedo hablar más de Joan plana
That's what you interpret in your
eso es lo que tú interpretas en tu
little head no take off your cap and read it
cabecita no po Quítate la gorra y Léelo
again because that is not what it says
otra vez porque eso no es lo que pone la
Joan plan sentence is a person who
sentencia Joan plan es una persona que
has been since the sentence was issued and a
lleva desde que salió la sentencia y un
just a little while before insulting me by calling me
poquito antes insultándome llamándome
dog calling me a clown calling me a
perro llamándome payaso llamándome un
a lot of things that I have here in one
montón de cosas que la tengo aquí en una
folder for another day You think that if I
carpeta para otro día Tú crees que si yo
I'll answer Jan right now.
ahora mismo le contesto a Jan
flat they would condemn me or they would say to me eh No
plana me condenarían o me diría eh No
You can talk about Johan Plana, about you, yes.
puedes hablar de Johan plana el de ti sí
that's what your head interprets
eso es lo que tu cabeza interpreta
Juanjo Do you think that if I have to
Juanjo Tú crees que si yo te tengo que
answer
responder a
a guy like you you a guy like you whatever you are
un como tú tú un tío como tú lo que seas
Hey
eh
to you, to a Tania, to a flat You think that
a ti a una Tania a un plana Tú crees que
I need to send a FJ Juanjo T
yo necesito mandar a un FJ Juanjo Tú
Do you think I need to call an Indian?
crees que yo necesito Llamar a un indio
to a FJ a Jo Hunter You think I
a un FJ un Jo Hunter Tú crees que yo me
I'm talking and looking for allies on the base
voy hablando y buscando aliados en base
to people who fight with you like
a la gente que se pelee contigo como
you do
haces
You You know who I am Juanjo You know
tú Tú sabes quién soy yo Juanjo Tú sabes
that you can come in a row one by one here
que podéis venir en fila uno a uno aquí
right now to this live and I'll chew you up
ahora mismo a este directo y os mastico
You think I need Ali to arm with
Tú crees que yo necesito Ali arme con
someone Juanjo I just that what you do not
alguien Juanjo yo solo que lo que no os
a click that Salom posted on Twitter
un click que puso Salomé en Twitter de
that I said something like another fool
que yo dije algo así como un tonto más
A fool is two fools, says Salome.
un tonto son dos tontos m lo pone Salomé
Please click on your Twitter
el click por favor en su Twitter
look for it and send me the link that
búscamelo y mándame el enlace que le
I want to tell people something. Okay.
quiero contar a la gente una cosa Vale
Well all these clips are from him
bueno todos estos clips son de él
saying that every time they mess with
diciendo que cada vez que se meten con
he in these two years that I am through
él en estos dos años que soy yo a través
from other people you know that it is like me
de otras personas sabes que es como yo
need
necesito
That's what few have learned.
Eso de od cre contados han aprendido la
lesson with the justice of not being able to
lección con la justi de no se pueden
involve they have learned with the
implicar ellos han aprendido con la
justice that they cannot be involved
justicia de que no se pueden implicar
What they do is send others
ellos lo que hacen es mandar a otros
smaller satellite channels which
canales satélites más pequeñitos lo que
They do is send to other channels
hacen es mandar a otros canales
satellites smaller Juanjo if I
satélites más pequeñito Juanjo si yo le
I want to say something aan flat I'm going to tell you
quiero decir algo aan plana se lo voy a
say if I want to tell you something to me
decir si yo le quiero decir algo a mi se
I'm going to say it and we'll go to Antonia's now.
lo voy a decir y a la Antonia vamos ya
I tell you that if I told him, it would be the last straw
te digo que si se lo digo solo faltaba
What do you think is a sentence?
Tú queé te crees que es una sentencia
Juanjo, a censorship like the one you are trying to
Juanjo una censura como la que intentas
execute
ejecutar
you and me as long as I don't use the same ones
tú yo mientras que no utilice las mismas
expression
expresion
that for example you use I can
que por ejemplo utilizas tú yo puedo
answer whoever wants to eh
contestarle a quien quiera eh el
The problem is when I answer that they are coming
problema es cuando contesto que vienen
the
los
cries Why me
lloros Por qué me
you look for us because
buscáis porque nos
we lay down
acostamos
not a tremendous direct hit I many
no de un directazo tremendo Yo muchas
I sometimes tell my people that
veces se lo comento a mi gente que
when we make a tremendous direct hit
cuando hacemos un directazo tremendo
Well, this is very long, I'll summarize it.
bueno Esto es muy largo lo voy a resumir
a little bit worth the next one who comes back
un poco vale el próximo que vuelva a
say that I am defaming someone already
decir que estoy difamando a alguien ya a
take action because this is what he gets
tomar medidas porque esto es él se pone
to talk to the chat is that we are
a hablar con el chat es que eh estamos
seeing how lately it is
viendo como últimamente Se está
warming up x people are warming up
calentando x personas están calentando a
different people their I don't know what about
diferentes personas su No sé lo que del
famous to try to boycott our
famoso para intentar boicotear nuestro
channel we didn't see that they are boycotting
canal no lo vimos que están boicoteando
We saw your channel with Alexia Rivas with
su canal con Alexia Rivas lo vimos con
We saw it with Alexia Rivas, she said that
lo vimos con Alexia Rivas dijo que
I was golfed
estaba golfeado
risk the same with more people than
riesgo lo mismo con más personas que
They say they have seen things they have not seen
dicen haber visto cosas que no han
past on the channel that is have seen
pasado en el canal que es han visto
things that haven't happened Then you're going to
cosas que no han pasado Entonces vas a
look and it is always the Indian the ane the
mirar y siempre es el indio la ane el
other are always the same No whether in
otro siempre son los mismos No ya sea en
direct in private or whatever but
directo en privado o lo que sea pero
we're always high and all that
siempre estamos altos y todo eso
So what? So what I say is
Entonces qué Entonces yo lo que digo es
that sometimes and I have been raising
que a veces y yo he estado planteando
today with the lawyer who is with me
hoy con con el abogado que me está
carrying my father's things and everything
llevando cositas de mi padre y todo yo
I am a very honest person with you
soy una persona muy honesta con vosotros
You already know that's why I speak from the heart
ya lo sabéis por eso lo hablo de corazón
To what extent is a youtuber
Hasta qué punto un youtuber es
responsible for what he does
responsable de de lo que hace su
community I think we have to start
comunidad yo creo que hay que empezar a
open melon And to what extent because
abrirse melón Y hasta qué punto porque
clear when you go to To what extent a
claro cuando vas a Hasta qué punto un
YouTuber is responsible for what he does
youtuber es responsable de lo que haga
your community I not I
su comunidad Yo no yo
I, I look at the profiles, they are all the
yo yo mira los perfiles son todos el
same bias hating people who have been
mismo sesgo gente odiadora que ha sido
cultivated with great care week after week
cultivada con mucha atención semana tras
week for them to hate you and then a week comes
semana para que te odien y llega un
moment when I am not allowed
momento que cuando no se me permite
work when they say authentic things
trabajar cuando se dicen auténticas
fallacies of me and a lawsuit would not come
falacias de mí e una demanda no vendría
then we must break the pattern of
entonces hay que romper el esquema de
work of these people and that you know that
trabajo de esta gente y que sepáis que
I'm studying that's what it is
estoy estudiando ese es qué está
studying that he is studying to report
estudiando que está estudiando denunciar
to the youtubers for what they gave their
a los youtubers por lo que dian su
community It turns out that Juanjo me
comunidad Resulta ser que Juanjo me
dedicated to me Marina for the face a while ago
dedicó a mí a Marina por la cara hace un
month a direct screaming failed I have
mes un directo gritando fracasado Tengo
six times your audience eh was a
seis veces tu público eh fue un
quite a shameful spectacle
espectáculo bastante bochornoso bastante
regrettable
lamentable
and according to him answering that I the day
e según él contestando a que yo el día
He had said something before about him having
antes había dicho algo de que él tiene
alliances that have them are worth what they have
alianzas que las tiene vale lo lo ha
recognized in any of the clicks seen
reconocido en alguno de los clic visto
Okay
vale
And do you know what happened?
e sabéis De qué se dio por
alluded to Of course because when I met the two
aludido Claro porque yo cuando a los dos
or three days ago they told me that this man
o tres días me contaron que este hombre
I had made a super altered live
Me había hecho un directo super alterado
Okay, I'm yelling at the camera on a Saturday.
vale eh gritando a la cámara un sábado
At noon I was with Enrique
al mediodía Yo estaba con el Enrique
eating is fine and they notified me the next day
comiendo vale Y me avisaron al día
next to the other I don't remember No it's not
siguiente al otro no me acuerdo No no es
that this live is for you and it gets in
que este directo es para ti y se mete
with Marina saying that he had one
con Marina diciendo que él tenía una
relationship with sea of speaking all the
relación con mar de hablar todas las
Night, well Marina will answer that later. Yes.
noches bueno eso ya contestará Marina si
She wants to but come on, what a show
ella quiere pero vamos qué espectáculo
further
más
embarrassing what a spectacle
bochornoso qué espectáculo más
embarrassing day Well then I get to work
bochornoso dio Bueno pues me pongo a
look to see what had happened
mirar a ver qué era lo que se había dado
by alluded to and had taken it as alluded to
por aludido y se había dado por aludido
that I said the night before
de que yo la noche antes dije
each one of you has not done this
estoo cada uno no habéis
been able together is the same or so to me that
podido juntos es lo mismo o sea a mí que
I don't care if I fight with a fool or
más me da pelearme con un tonto que
fight with another fool than fight with
pelearme con otro tonto que pelearme con
another fool to get together all the
otro tonto a que se junten todos los
fools a fool joins another fool and
tontos un tonto se une a otro tonto y
there are two
son dos
Fools, I was checking the live stream to see
tontos estuve revisando el directo a ver
what had been given to him and it was that
qué era lo que le había dado y fue que
He had taken it personally because I said
se había dado por aludido porque yo dije
this
esto
really let others work
de verdad dejar trabajar a los demás
It costs so much if my family wants to do it
tanto cuesta si mi familia qui hacer
We make our normal life on the Internet and
vida normal en internet la hacemos y
period and I will not tolerate anyone judging
punto y no voy a tolerar que nadie juz
What I do, I'm not a YouTuber
lo que hago yo yo no soy un youtuber
controversial I am not a channel of a channel
polémico yo no soy un canal de un canal
white Juano a white channel
blanco Juano un canal blanquito
I'm ashamed of you. You're welcome, quite the opposite.
avergonzarme De nada todo lo contrario
This channel will be cleaner and more
este canal va ser más limpio y más
familiar and increasingly cleaner and more
familiar y cada vez más limpio y más
Familiar I don't know if it is Let's see I don't know if each
Familiar no sé si es A ver no sé si cada
cleaner and more familiar because
vez más limpio es más familiar porque
Of course if you take it to your channel
Claro si te te pones a llevar a tu canal
to the air of
a ar de
Troy if you start taking your channel to
Troya si te pones a llevar a tu canal a
Loli Huertas if you start taking her to
la Loli huertas si te pones a llevar a
Tania and if you start taking her to the
la Tania y ya si te pones a llevar a la
Peppa who doesn't even clean the kitchen will get you
Peppa que no limpie ni la cocina te va a
clean you up
limpiar a ti el
my style channel, that is, those who suffer from
canal mi estilo o sea los que sufran de
Jito Sauda is going to blow his brains out
jito sauda van a reventar por los sesos
because you will see that this profile of
porque van a ver que ese perfil de
hater of people without feelings who
odiador de personas sin sentimientos que
They always mean that they have said that
quieren decir siempre que han dicho que
I am falling apart
soy se les cae a cachos
and last month I was exploding I don't know
y el mes pasado estaba explotando no sé
because as I just told you with the
por qué como os acabo de decir con el
time that has to comply with the
tiempo qui tiene que cumplir con la
justice and who is not and who is
justicia y quién no y quién está
doing things right on YouTube and
haciendo las cosas bien en YouTube y
Who doesn't because I'm not a pain
quién no porque Qué pesado yo no soy
Nobody, not even you, a Twitter person
nadie ni tú tampoco persona de Twitter
That is what justice is going to say.
eso es la justicia lo que lo va a decir
Little by little it's worth it And it's enough of being
poco a poco vale Y ya está bien de estar
saying and judging as if others
diciendo y juzgando como si los demás
were judges time puts everyone
fueran jueces el tiempo pone a todo el
world in its place Yes and that's what
mundo en su sitio Sí y eso es lo que
this
está
passing yes, time is passing
pasando sí que el tiempo lo está
putting everything in its place that's why you are
poniendo todo en su sitio por eso estás
with 900 spectators and you can invent
con 900 espectadores y podéis inventar
fake audience graphs
gráficas de audiencias falsas
defamations insults posting photos of me
difamaciones insultos poner fotos de mi
my son's wife my father's do it
mujer de mi hijo de mi padre hacer lo
Whatever you want, but there will be everything
que os de la gana pero todo va a haber
consequences I have to certify
consecuencias he tengo que certificar
almost 300 tweets from one person
casi 300 tweets de una persona
bandaging siqua you have balls make a face
vendando siqua tené [__] Pon cara
Okay, good night.
Vale Buenas noches
handsome a kiss car throwing a kiss my
guap un beso car lanzando un beso mi
Crown crown
Corona coronan
If I tell you who has me
si os digo quién me ha
called If I tell you who called me
llamado Si os digo quién me ha llamado
today someone just sent me a WhatsApp
hoy qui me acaba de mandar un WhatsApp
for a project we are doing
para un proyecto que estamos haciendo
Come on, we've already finished the objective
venga que ya terminamos el objetivo
Diana and give it a thumbs up
Diana y dale a pulgar hacia arriba
that does not lie How much envy they have
que no miente Cuánta envidia tienen a
This wonderful community there is only one
esta maravillosa comunidad solo hay un
Raider sauce and that's you
Raider salseo y ese eres tú
Javi When you know the project I'm working on
Javi Cuando sepáis el proyecto que estoy
messing around when you know what I'm messing around
liando cuando sepáis la que estoy liando
dune a
duna un
kiss Well what do you want, don't you
beso Bueno qué quies gu vosotras no os
work hideout to defame for
escondiso de trabajo para difamar para
invent two and a half years already missing
inventar dos años y medio ya faltando
respect, no one is making up hoaxes
respeto inventándose bulos nadie le está
taking into account that is to say that nobody
echando cuenta o sea es que nadie le
He's doing the math and has a thing going on there
está echando cuenta y tiene un rollo ahí
objective achieved
objetivo cumplido
one p each
una p cada
Spain but they don't have to dagger me.
españ pero no a m ae tienen que 50 puñal
I don't understand what we just gave him.
itas que le acabamos de dar no entiendo
Isabel a kiss Well then having
Isabel un beso Bueno pues habiendo
Having achieved this objective, I propose to you
cumplido este objetivo yo os propongo
something a deal between you and me still
algo un trato entre ustedes y yo todavía
I still have a few things to comment on
me faltan algunas cosas que comentar
here it is worth it then I looked at the kids who
aquí vale luego Miré a la chavalería que
I have some salt around here, okay? And I have
tengo por ahí algún salillo vale Y tengo
to also record a video for the
que grabar también un vídeo para el
main channel but there is one thing that is not
canal principal pero hay una cosa que no
I know if people want it or not
sé si la gente lo quiere o no lo
people want a
quiere la gente quiere un
Game Over, people want a gin over.
gameover la gente quiere un gin over
updated
actualizado
tell me a number tell me a number that
decidme un número decidme un número que
I'm going to tell you one
os voy a decir una
thing a number that this community is
cosa un número que esta comunidad sea
able to fulfill 1 5 10 15 20 30 other
capaz de de cumplir 1 5 10 15 20 30 otro
50 No way, not another 50 I don't think so.
50 Ni de coña no otro 50 no creo
not another 50 No way
no otro 50 Ni de coña
No, that's not the case, we won't break the internet like that.
no eso no así no romperemos internet no
another 50 yes yes let me write
otro 50 sí que sí dejarme que escriba
a
una
thing yes
cosa si
we arrived I don't know what time
llegamos no sé qué tiempo
I don't know what time I put but yes
no sé qué tiempo he puesto pero si
we make another 50 if this community is
hacemos otros 50 si esta comunidad es
able to do another 50 worth
capaz de hacer otros 50 vale
and game over is going to be released
e se va a estrenar el game over
updated that is not asked Jai La
actualizado eso no se pregunta Jai La
The answer is yes, it is a video that is not missing.
respuesta es sí es un vídeo que no falta
Respect It is a video that tells the truth
el respeto Es un vídeo que dice verdades
It's a video that is a video that gave me
es un vídeo que es un vídeo que me dio
so much pity
muchísima pena
It's a video that made me feel very sad.
es un vídeo que me dio muchísima pena
delete and here we have a person
eliminar y aquí tenemos a una persona
that has stuck to me for two years
que me está se ha pegado dos años
Disrespecting almost three times is enough
faltando al respeto casi tres ya vale
Roman a handsome kiss Roman no 50 members
Roman un beso guapo Roman no 50 miembros
Roman has given me, it's going to be playing
me ha regalado Roman va a estar sonando
50 members all the time Roman is a
50 miembros todo el tiempo Román es un
video that I felt very sorry to delete
vídeo que me dio muchísima pena eliminar
and I think this person has not complied
y creo que esta persona no ha cumplido
the agreement is valid, the pact has not been fulfilled
el acuerdo vale no ha cumplido el pacto
It will no longer be removed in the
ya no se va a volver a eliminar en la
life is worth it
vida vale
eh I already believe that the time to be
eh Ya yo creo que que la época de ser
silly, the time has clearly passed. SIM
tonto ya pasó evident SIM la época de
Being an idiot is over for me, eh all this
ser idiota ya pasó para mí eh todo esto
that I am putting to you and more that remains
que os estoy poniendo y más que queda
Okay, I've been swallowing it, I've been swallowing it
vale me lo he ido tragando me lo he ido
I've been swallowing it, I don't think so.
tragando me lo he ido tragando No creo
to upload all the videos that were in
que suba todos los vídeos que había en
the time obviously because they are already
la época evidentemente porque ya están
outdated and such I do not rule out uploading
desactualizado y tal no descarto subir
some more worth it will depend but I have
alguno más vale dependerá pero yo he
I've been removing these videos by keeping quiet
estado quitando estos vídeos callándome
and this guy throwing [ __ ] at me all the time
y este tío tirándome [__] todo el
time uncle or so why do i have to
tiempo tío o sea Por qué tengo que
I put up with a guy throwing [ __ ] at me
aguantar yo un tío tirándome [__]
every day one day because I have
todos los días un día porque tengo
17,000 viewers another day because
17,000 espectadores otro día porque
I'll collaborate with Fran another day because I don't know
colaboro con Fran otro día porque no sé
What? Or any day, any excuse
qué O sea cualquier día cualquier excusa
She's good at throwing [ __ ] at me all day long
es buena todo el día tirándome [__]
Okay, no, they're not little shots. Pilar is shooting.
vale No no son tiritos Pilar es tirando
[ __ ] that you take the next day and
[__] que tú cojas al día siguiente y
open the live stream
abras el directo
saying that there is nothing about you on Google
diciendo que de ti no hay nada en Google
I don't know, I don't know how much, simply because I
no sé no sé cuánto Simplemente porque yo
I had a great program with
he tenido un pedazo de programa con
Frank is not a joke, it's throwing me away.
Frank no es una pullita es tirarme
[ __ ] on the face okay eh you open
[__] por la cara vale eh que tú abras
a live one day giving Doc a kiss
un directo un día dándole un beso a Doc
Z saying that that no that that why
Z diciendo que que no que que por
[ __ ] what you say is the story
[__] lo que tú digas es la historia
from do Z is throwing [ __ ] at me you are
de do Z es tirarme [__] estás
implying that I have harassed a person
insinuando que yo he acosado una persona
until he kicked her off the internet with l
hasta que la ha echado de internet con l
I read the same They are not
Li lo mismo No son
pullit are not pullit okay Now the one who is
pullit no son pullit vale Ya el que se
It's boring, he kicks and whatnot, but I'm
aburre que patalea y que tal pero yo de
moment I have that video, that video
momento ese vídeo lo tengo yo ese vídeo
I'm going to have it because it's a video of mine.
lo voy a tener porque es un vídeo mío un
video with a lot of work, okay And it is
vídeo con mucho curro vale Y está
updated we have it updated okay
actualizado lo tenemos actualizado vale
So if we get to 50 members,
Entonces si llegamos a 50 miembros lo
I put yes no no
pongo si no no
Okay, two and a half years of missing
Okay dos años y medio de faltando
respect is enough is enough I know that
respeto ya está bien ya está bien sé que
there is no content I know you have nothing
no hay contenido sé que no tenéis nada
what to talk about because you don't know how to work
de que hablar porque no sabéis trabajar
It's hard to work at this time of year.
cuesta mucho trabajar por esta época no
I know what I would be talking about but I
sé de qué estaría hablando yo pero yo
I think I don't lack content, I think.
creo que a mí contenido no me falta creo
that I am a person who is doing
que soy una persona que está haciendo
many things you cannot even imagine
muchísimas cosas no os imagináis ni
not even what is coming next week
siquiera lo que se viene la semana que
comes or the other one is worth it you can't even imagine
viene o la otra vale ni os lo imagináis
It's going to be something that's going to give a lot
va a ser una cosa Que que va a dar mucho
that talking is worth it, eh? You can't even imagine it.
que hablar vale eh Ni os lo imagináis de
true what is coming eh I have triumphed
verdad lo que se viene eh he triunfado
with the case of Daniel Sancho I have
con el caso de Daniel Sancho he
triumphed with the Didi case eh with
triunfado con el caso de Didi eh con
all with a lot of lores that I have
todo con un montón de lores que he
treated in the main channel which is my
tratado en el canal principal que es mi
channel
canal
worth in
vale en
the easiest thing is to defame
fin lo que es más fácil es difamar
constantly insulting and disrespecting
insultar y faltar respeto continuamente
You are a bunch of lazy people, you are all good
sois una panda de vagos sois bueno todos
adjectives It crosses your mind
calificativos Se os pasa por la cabeza
It goes without saying and you know it very well.
no hace falta ni decirlo y lo sabéis muy
Well, it's that everyone thinks that
bien Es que cada uno piensa que
I insult her
la insulto
You look into a person's eyes and realize
V los ojos de una persona y das cuenta
the amount of problems that you and we have
la cantidad de problemas que ti nosotros
We are not to blame because we always
no tenemos culpa porque siempre las
things well That's why we are calm and
cosas bien Por eso estamos tranquilos y
enjoying we enjoy youtuber me
disfrutando disfrutamos de youtuber yo
I have been enjoying this platform
llevo en esta plataforma disfrutando se
you see him enjoying a great time you have
le ve disfrutando un disfrutón you tiene
to serve as a mirror of those greats
que servir como espejo de esos grandes
moments not as a mirror of things I go
momentos no como un espejo de cosas voy
Let's see what they're putting on Twitter like
a ver que están poniendo en Twitter como
that I have done something that I have not done
que yo he hecho una cosa que no he hecho
I have said nothing, I have never said anything because
he dicho nada jamás he dicho nada porque
I don't want to give promotion But there are each
no quiero dar promoción Pero hay cada
thing in each channel and they have double
cosa en cada canal y que tienen el doble
or triple the audience but for me
o triple de audiencia pero que para mí
These channels do not exist because they
esos canales no existen porque se
They invent things that have the channels
inventan las cosas canales que tienen el
double or triple the audience than me but
doble o el triple audiencia que yo pero
It does not exist because things are invented
no existe porque se inventan las cosas
I'm not going to compare myself with channels that are
no voy a compararme con canales que se
they invent things there is one there
inventan las cosas hay uno ahí
inventing that he was dying of giving
inventándose que se muerto de dar
moral lessons to no one is fine anymore
leciones de moral a nadie ya está bien
Enough of making up stories
de inventaras historias ya está bien de
stories with private everyone
cuentos chos con privado todo el mundo
You know the profile, you are a lazy person and
sabe el perfil tú si que eres un vago y
you are a [ __ ] stirrer this is the
tú eres un revuelve [__] esto es al
Indian okay, he thinks it's fine to avoid
indio vale a él le parece bien evita
Dynamite
Dinamita
Wilson has that account with which he
Wilson la cuenta esa con la que se
He spoke privately that he was caught
hablaba por privado que se le pilló la
conversation
conversación
private naf is worth all those but the
privada naf vale todas esas pero el
Indian is all this, eh, you're a nobody
indio es todo esto eh eres un don nadie
a walking mem, a son of a [ __ ] who only
un mem andante un hijo de [__] que solo
invents a son of a [ __ ] invents and that
inventa un hijo de [__] inventa y que
works for I don't know who and what he works for
trabaja para no sé quién y que trabaja
for I don't know who and in the end everything is in
para no sé quién y al final todo está en
your site everyone knows the
su sitio todo el mundo sabe el
profile have tried actively and by
perfil han intentado por activa y por
passive put me Fear I have messages from
pasiva meterme Miedo tengo mensajes de
If you don't do this, we'll take away your channel and
si no haces esto te quitamos el canal y
all
todo
That's for you to know the interpretation.
eso vete tú a saber la interpretación
real heo What will it be if you have to go to
real de heo Cuál será si tiene que ir a
Wherever I have to go I'll take it and I'll go
donde tenga que ir Voy a llevarlo y voy
to say I don't know, your honor, but this is
a decir yo no sé señor juez Pero esto es
of this person in
de esta persona en
end this What is it
fin esto Qué es
again the Indian who is sent by me
otra vez el indio que es mandado por mí
the Indian is a
del el indio es un
offender
delincuente
trying to only work for one
intentando com solo trabaja para una
community a community that has been
comunidad una comunidad que ha sido
condemned Okay, so to this point
condenada Vale pues a esta parte
We wanted to get to this part right now.
queríamos llegar vale a esta parte
We wanted to reach a community that has
queríamos llegar una comunidad que ha
a community has been condemned
sido condenada una comunidad una
community that has been condemned
comunidad que ha sido condenada
Is this worth the condemnation he wants?
t vale esto de la condena que él quiere
use okay we have to talk about this
utilizar vale esto lo tenemos que hablar
obviously
evidentemente
Okay, we have to do this.
vale esto lo tenemos que ha
Obviously I really This is not
evidentemente yo de verdad Esto no es
for throwing anything in his face
por tirarle nada en cara a
No one for a well-done gameover that doesn't
nadie por un gameover bien hecho que no
leave doubts about what kind of character he is
deje dudas de qué clase de personaje es
this
este
sir yes yes Ed you want it it it
señor si si Ed queréis lo lo lo
We're releasing it now, okay, that's already in
estrenamos ahora vale eso ya está en
your hand is worth it I think it's a
vuestra mano vale Yo creo que es una
madness that this community suddenly
locura que esta comunidad de repente
Now we would do 100 superchats in this
ahora hiciéramos 100 superchat en este
Same direct okay But well I'll leave it there
mismo directo vale Pero bueno ahí dejo
the option is valid
la opción vale
and the Indian is a criminal who works
e el indio es un delincuente que trabaja
for a condemned community you can me
para una comunidad condenada me podéis
Please pay the lawyer together.
pagar el abogado entre todos porfa
I ask, eh, can you pay me at
pregunto eh Me podéis pagar al
Lawyer asked, "Hey, I paid for it."
abogado pregunto eh Oye el lo he pagado
I'm alone
yo eh solo
eh Let's see the 0 euro sentence, not the
eh A ver la condena de 0 eurito no la
we can share it among everyone but I
podemos repartir entre todos pero yo
I think the lawyer too
creo que el abogado también
Hey Auri, how are you? I haven't told you yet.
eh Auri qué tal no te había
seen
visto
Eh, this thing about the condemned community and that
Eh Esto de la comunidad condenada y que
You defend a convicted person, it's something
defiendes a un condenado es algo
very common in Juanjo's words
muy habitual en las palabras de Juanjo
to refer to me okay eh In fact
para referirse a mí vale eh De hecho
Well, from the sentence of Planas no
Bueno de la sentencia de planas no
It's just that he spoke, it's okay.
solamente es que haya hablado vale ha
talked about Miare's sentence before
hablado de la sentencia de miare antes
I have put for example the capture that
he puesto por ejemplo la captura esa que
the flat sentence voucher was leaked
se filtró vale de la sentencia de plana
Well here I have some examples I don't know
Bueno aquí tengo algunos ejemplos no sé
what to wear is fine
qué poneros vale
[Music]
[Música]
and Johan's sentence
e sentencia de Johan
flat you're going to burn what you do is
plana te vas a abrasar lo que haces es
I remind you that there are illegal sentences
ilegal te recuerdo que hay condenas
recent YouTube videos I remind you that there are
recientes de YouTube te recuerdo que hay
recent convictions in which when not
condenas recientes en los que cuando no
There is proportionality, there is a crime, I am of you
hay proporcionalidad hay delito yo de ti
I think it has been spoken two or three times
creo que se hablado dos tres veces los
that when there is no proportionality there is
que cuando no hay proporcionalidad ha
good crime is not a crime because it is a
delito bueno delito no es porque es una
civil judgment is valid are claims for the
sentencia civil vale son demandas por el
honor these who come out Here with the hat
honor estas que salen Aquí con el gorro
You see what he's doing here with the hat.
veis esto que hace aquí con el gorro
You see this that comes out here with the hat
veis esto que sale aquí con el gorro
I'm not going to put this thumbnail here.
esta miniatura esto no lo voy a poner
because it's very long okay this is very
porque es muy largo vale esto es muy
long But this is a live that he did
largo Pero esto es un directo que hizo
I explain Joan Plana's lawyers to you
os explico los abogados de Joan plana
They made an article on their website
hicieron un artículo en su página web
Ok so Juanjo came to
Vale pues Juanjo vino a
He saw fit to give it a vertical direct shot.
bien vio bien darle un directo vertical
to that article a person with whom
a ese artículo una persona con la que
I have a non-aggression pact that is
tengo un pacto de no agresión que se
It means that we don't have to talk to each other
supone que no tenemos que hablar el uno
of the other one that I am supposed to have removed
del otro que se supone que yo he quitado
those videos we agreed on
esos vídeos en los que hemos acordado
Well this person saw
Pues esta persona vio a
It's good to dedicate an afternoon to that article.
bien dedicarle una tarde a ese artículo
Okay
vale
we could put several clips
podríamos podríamos poner varios clips
but it is very long
pero es que es muy largo
Look, send us audios s610
Mira mandaros audios s610
4666 I stopped working and could live less than
4666 dej trabajar pued vivir medos que
comes to subscribers who own in
viene a los suscriptores que posean en
Their respective channels are the
sus respectivos canales son los
well-known youtubers frequently
conocidos youtubers con frecuencia el
ecosystem this is about getting along
ecosistema esto de é ponerse a llevarse
with Joan Planas to agree on a
con Joan planas para acordar como una
kind of boycott me or throw me like that
especie de boic contra mí o tirarme tal
has done it more times Okay now let's
lo ha hecho más veces Vale ahora vamos a
see some examples but I think that with
ver algunos ejemplos pero creo que con
You understand this, right? I mean, he's like
esto lo entendéis no O sea él está como
super motivated with this sentence worth it
super motivado con esta sentencia vale
clean my channel is a channel in which
limpio mi canal es un canal en el que
we just talk about good vibes
solo hablamos de buen rollo de las cosas
but he is seen talking all the time
pero se se le ve todo el tiempo hablando
in good spirits with the way things are
de buen rollo de las cosas como estáis
checking it's over it's over it's over
comprobando se acabó se acabó se acabó
The movie of messing with
Ya se acabó la película de meterse con
juanjus ended a long time ago but why
juanjus se acabó hace tiempo pero porque
There are already rulings that it cannot be done
ya hay sentencias de que no se puede
to do and there are sentences that say no
hacer y hay sentencias que dicen que no
People can mess with Juanjus.
se puede meter la gente con juanjus lo
It says eh in a sentence with juanjus no
pone eh en una sentencia con juanjus no
eh it is forbidden with juanjus there is no
eh está prohibido con juanjus no hay
sentences that prohibit it and you think
sentencias eh que lo prohíben y pensáis
that on Twitter it is different will be more
que en Twitter es distinto será más
long and tedious but each profile has
largo y tedioso pero cada perfil tiene
an IP each IP is the license plate each IP
una IP cada ip es la matrícula cada ip
It's a license plate, okay?
es una matrícula vale
and with the soul everything that is truly
e con el alma todo lo que de verdad
Thank you all for being there with me
gracias a todos porque estáis ahí con
the red hearts I am speechless and
los corazones rojos estoy sin palabras y
Lis the chat that I don't see anything but color
Lis el chat que no no veo más que color
red without eating or drinking it is worth it, that's what it is
rojo sin comerlo ni beberlo vale es lo
What touches is reality and I, as I have already
que toca es la realidad y yo como ya he
Having lived through this, they are now looking to see masks
vivido esto buscan ya a ver caretas
outside we know what they are looking for
fuera sabemos lo que están buscando
They have been provoking me for a long time
llevan mucho tiempo provocándome para
get things that are not going to happen
conseguir cosas que no lo van a
It takes a long time to get
conseguir llevan mucho tiempo
provoking him
provocándole
He who does not speak and so much time
el que no habla y tantoo el tiempo
provoking him because there is a difference
provocándole porque hay una diferencia
between me and others I will never be
entre yo y otros yo no voy a ser nunca
condemned to nothing because I know very well
condenado a nada porque yo sé muy bien
what I do there is a difference between
lo que hago yo hay una diferencia entre
he and others that he will never be
él y otros que él nunca va a ser
damn okay Okay, I can get bored
condenado vale Bueno me puedo aburrir
All this is worth talking about the sentence
vale todo esto hablando de la sentencia
of
de
flat Eh I'm fed up with us
planas Eh Yo estoy harto ya de que nos
send people who insult us
manden personas que nos afrentan las
face things and me since he is tired
cosas de cara y yo ya que está cansado
that people who do not know how to send you
de que le manden personas que no se
I am insulting things head on
afrentan las cosas de cara estoy infando
that I send to someone as if to me
que yo le mando a alguien como si a mí
he matters to me I will go there, don't have
él me importase voy a acudir no tenga
that you should go to this person if you want
que acudir con esta persona si quiere
sue me, sue me, eh? There's one.
demandarme que me demande eh Hay una
something that a person who is told me
cosa que me dijo una persona que es
It's true that there comes a time in life that, eh?
verdad lleg un momento en la vida que eh
He called me condemned in
lo de llamarme condenado lo ha hecho en
many occasions worth In fact this
montón de ocasiones vale De hecho este
I have done it directly because they have
directo lo he hecho porque me han
sent this afternoon
mandado esta tarde
eh a clip where once again last night
eh un clip donde una vez más anoche
He again alluded to the fact that this is a
volvió a hacer alusión a que esta es una
community of a convicted person is worth it. In fact
comunidad de un condenado vale De hecho
Every time he messes with Carmen with
cada vez que se mete con Carmen con
teleindiscreta here the friend tells him that
teleindiscreta aquí el amigo le dice que
Well Carmen, what are you doing with a
bueno Carmen Y tú qué que estás con un
condemned that you collaborate with a
condenado que colaboras con un
condemned Juanjo for the next time he
condenado Juanjo para la próxima vez que
you refer to someone in my environment as
te refieras a alguien de mi entorno como
who joins a convict or who
que se junta con un condenado o que
collaborates with a convicted person Look at you, I'll see you
colabora con un condenado Mira te vo te
I'm going to explain something, dude.
voy explicar una cosa guajo
Look at Amador Moedano, your collaborator.
Mira Amador moedano tu colaborador
main the star of your channel
principal la estrella de tu canal
convicted of attacking his dogs
condenado por la agresión de sus perros
to a girl the brother of the deceased
a una niña el hermano de la fallecida
Roco Jurado and Rosa Benito's ex-husband
Rocío Jurado y ex marido de Rosa Benito
He has been sentenced to 2000 which is already more
ha sido condenado a 2000 que ya es más
greater than mine of compensation to a
grande que la mía de indemnización a una
13-year-old girl
niña de 13
years after an attack by his dogs
años tras una agresión de sus perros a
The young lady seems to me that this is more
la joven me parece a mí que esto es más
serious than some insults eh Because also
grave que unos insultos eh Porque además
It's that this You know It seems to me that that
Es que esto Sabes Me parece a mí que que
an assault is much more is much more
una agresión es mucho más es mucho más
Okay, this sentence from Amador is not valid for you.
vale no te vale esta condena de Amador
Well, nothing happens. Look, Amador Mohedano.
bueno no pasa nada Mira Amador mohedano
on the edge due to a large debt of
al límite por una gran deuda de
247,000 with
247,000 con
Treasury, that is a collaborator of yours.
Hacienda ese es un colaborador tuyo la
this star I really hope that
la estrella este De verdad espero que
Francisco, don't take it as an attack.
Francisco no se lo tome como un ataque
because it is not okay it is news that
porque no lo es vale es una noticia que
It came out recently, I have nothing in it
salió hace poco yo no tengo nada en
against him this morning he sent me a
contra de él esta mañana me mandó un
WhatsApp I answer each one well
WhatsApp yo le contesto bien cada uno
will know the things that
sabrá las cosas que
I think people have teete
tiene yo creo que la gente tiene teete
a kiss I believe that there are things and there are
un beso yo creo que hay cosas y hay
crimes that have reintegration there are others
delitos que tienen reinserción hay otras
that are more serious like that of the husband of
que son más graves como lo del marido de
Tania is worth it, well, every single thing, no, but
Tania vale bueno cada cosas no pero
Well Francisco, your main collaborator
bueno Francisco tu colaborador principal
also
también
p Game Over Game Over Game Over Gamer
p Game Over Game Over Game Over Gamer
over smiling face smiling face with
over cara sonriendo cara sonriendo con
Gaf spends two years in prison for simulating
gaf pasa dos años de cárcel por simular
a transfer well This is another one
una transferencia bueno Esto es una otra
sentence was valid for 4 years and he spent 2
condena vale que era de 4 años y pasó 2
years to remove it I have nothing
años para para quitarlo tengo nada
against Francisco and I get along well with
contra de Francisco y me llevo bien con
He collaborates here too, okay. But oh well.
él colabora aquí también vale Pero bueno
It's that Juanjo is very offended that
es que Juanjo está muy ofendido con que
one is civilly condemned Then
uno esté condenado civilmente Entonces
I remind you
le recuerdo
Okay, Conchita, with whom you collaborated
vale que Conchita con la que colaboraste
also recently Okay now I'm going to read
también hace poco Vale ahora voy a leer
Conchita's thing is fine but it makes me feel that
lo de Conchita vale pero me pone que
This is private, I can't click on it myself.
esta es privada no puedo pinchar t mismo
yourself Juanjo, let's see, put Conchita on it
tú mismo Juanjo a ver pone Conchita la
deluxe polygraph examiner a life of
poligrafista de deluxe una vida de
scandals police arrests for
escándalos detenciones policiales por
false threats and accusations against her
falsas amenazas y denuncias sobre ella
This according to the exclusive media
esto según el medio exclusivo
digital gives Conchita Prez the polygraph
digital pone Conchita Pérez la polígrafa
del delux loses again to the
del delux vuelve a perder ante la
justice its requirements on
justicia sus requerimientos sobre
digital is also
digital es también
damned okay Juanjo Then all of them
condenada vale Juanjo Entonces ya todas
the times you refer to me as a
las veces que te refieres a mí como una
convicted person I want to see the game
persona condenada Yo quiero ver el game
over and they are already giving me a hard time for
over y ya me están poniendo a caldo por
the theme that supports the worst of the worst
el tema que apoyan a lo peor de lo peor
and let the [ __ ] come together not that person
y que la [__] se junte no esa persona
is supporting a person who has been
está apoyando una persona que ha sido
condemned that person referring to
condenada esa persona refiriéndote a
Carmen de T indiscreet every time
Carmen de T indiscreta cada vez que
you argue with her
discutes con ella
Let's go for the gameover, a Maleficent kiss
vamos a por el gameover un besa Maléfica
Too Sanch is also putting it on me.
Toño sanch también me lo están poniendo
in the chat that Too Sanch owes him money
en el chat que Toño sanch le debe pasta
Beln Esteban was also not sentenced
a Belén Esteban no también fue condenado
We have not interviewed both you and I
no hemos entrevistado tanto tú como yo a
Coto Matamoro I think also had some
Coto matamoro creo que también tuvo Unos
little problems, not just some other ones
problemillas no algún que otro
little problem demands for the right to
problemilla demandas por derecho al
honor A kiss maril demands by right
honor Un beso maril demandas por derecho
to honor Well, I think we have also
al honor Pues creo que también hemos
interviewed the two agents who have
entrevistado los dos agentes que ha
lost lawsuits for the right to honor
perdido demandas por derecho al honor
So Ju when you refer to me from
entonces Ju cuando te refieras a m de
this
esta
however you want to mess with people who
forma te quieras meter con gente que se
join me this way
junte conmigo de esta for
Don't do it, he'll become a victim of it.
no lo hagas se va a victimizar de eso
He knows a lot that haters are going to attack him.
sabe mucho los odiadores se le van a
add up and they will give you visits is what
sumar y le van a dar visitas es lo que
wants
quiere
No, that game never happened. It should have happened.
No ese game nunca se Tendría que haber
eliminated has earned every FR
eliminado se ha ganado a pulso cada FR
2.0 has held you back for too long
del 2.0 demasiado tiempo te frenado ante
so much attack
tanto ataque
cowardly one
cobarde una
Spanish but not
españ pero no
Game Over
Game Over
return a kiss yuka How
return un beso yuka Cómo
Coto has been in jail and
anda Coto ha estado en la cárcel y
Do everything hands in prayer hands
todo Hazlo manos en oración manos
clapping face in love face throwing
aplaudiendo cara enamorada cara lanzando
a
un
kiss to see if
beso a ver si
finish host I'm going to have to
termina [__] voy a tener que
silence it sorry but I'm going to have
silenciarlo perdonad pero voy a tener
that silencing it is worth it, we arrive at the challenge Ok
que silenciarlo vale llegamos al reto Ok
If you want the gameover, we get to the challenge.
si queréis el gameover llegamos al reto
but I'm going to have to keep that quiet
pero voy a tener que silenciar eso
Juanjo, the next time you go to
Juanjo la próxima vez que te vayas a
refer to me or you're going to mess with me
referir a mí o te vayas a meter con
someone in my environment in this way
alguien de mi entorno de esta forma
Of course, people deserve it
desde luego que se merece que la gente
know what he is like and how he acts that he has been
sepa Cómo es y cómo actúa que ha sido
condemned that
condenada esa
person that person is putting a
persona esa persona está poniendo una
person who has been convicted, you remain silent
persona que ha sido condenada te callas
the
la
mouth is worth the
boca vale la
ris carando deis carando de ris cara
ris carando deis carando de ris cara
throwing a kiss throwing a kiss
lanzando un beso lanzando un beso
throwing a
lanzando un
kiss don't cry lawyer
beso no llores abogado
per
per
no what
no Qué
you win The time of silence has passed
ganas Ya pasó el tiempo del Silencio se
sink your puddle game cap with visor
hunde tu charquito game gorra con visera
cap with
gorra con
visor Now we are condemned community B
visera Ahora somos comunidad condenada B
flexed spicy chili pepper perd Queen
flexionado chile picante perd Queen
Okay, it looks really ugly, but yes
vale hace mu feo per que si
Ok, but they have the gin
vale pemos el gin a tienen
If you want, we can add the gin over, but
que si queréis ponemos el gin over pero
I have to silence this because if not,
tengo que silenciar esto porque si no no
I can speak okay
puedo hablar vale
Hey, this Juanjo who to everyone who
eh este Juanjo que a todo el mundo que
He comes up to me and says this, no, that
se acerca a mí le dice esto no que
defends a condemned man that I am a
defiende a un condenado que yo soy un
condemned a community even
condenado una comunidad incluso
This man was condemned and saw fit to no longer
condenada este hombre tuvo a bien ya no
only collaborate and interview
solamente colaborar y entrevistar a
people convicted of more serious things
gente condenada por cosas más graves
but you are going to defend Tania and
sino que tu va bien defender a a Tania y
to your
a su
husband invited saying something out loud
marido invito diciendo salido una cosa
what things and victim people
que cosas y de personas vítimas
okay, we are talking about
vale que se está hablando de
victims there are victims for a long time
víctimas hay vítimas hace mucha gra ha
There are victims who are not amused.
ell hay víctimas que no les hace gracia
that it is being talked about already
que se esté hablando de ella ya han
talked about things or with people and
hablado las cosas o con las personasen y
that maybe they have already talked things over
que a lo mejor ya han hablado las cosas
with the person who is in the sentence
con la persona que está en la sentencia
see how far you can go
fíjate hasta dónde eres capaz de llegar
Juanjo with
Juanjo con
session I condemned my community
sesión yo condenado mi comunidad
convicted TV insider collaborates with
condenada teleindiscreta colabora con
a person
una persona
Tania's husband and her sentenced
condenada el marido de Tania y su
victim may have to fix things
víctima a lo mejor han arreglar las
tremendous tremendous things did not come out
cosas tremendo tremendo no salió a
defend Tania Today is a strange day
defender a Tania Hoy es un día raro un
I kiss Tania because you already know that it is true
beso Tania porque ya sabéis que cierto
very pretty, we'll talk about it later
muy guapa que vamos a comentar después
But tell him that I am sending him once again a
Pero decirle que le mando una vez más un
Tania kiss and well this did it during
beso Tania y bueno Esto lo hizo durante
every day is worth it you know that I am
todos los días vale sabéis que yo soy
This was for every day
una Esto fue durante todos los días
defending Tania a kiss Tania
defendiendo a Tania un beso Tania
eh And something happened also worth it
eh Y pasó una cosa también vale la
nonsense of the report
mamarrachada del reporte
eh the nonsense of sport
eh la mamarrachada del deporte el
report for defamation I don't know if it
reporte por difamación no sé si lo
You will remember but Tania gave me a
recordaréis pero Tania me puso un
report by
reporte por
defamation that is a tool that
difamación eso es una herramienta que
discovered
descubrió
wajo that existed on YouTube that doesn't work
wajo que existía en YouTube que no sirve
for censorship he believes that the
para la censura él se cree que los
Copyright reports are for the
reportes para copyright son para la
censorship and he believes that the reports of
censura y él se cree que los reportes de
defamation are for censorship
difamación son para la censura el
copyright report Juanjo is for
reporte de copyright Juanjo es para
copyright in case someone takes a live
copyright por si alguien coge un directo
yours and monetize it and upload it or a video
tuyo y lo monetiza y lo sube o un vídeo
yours that you have worked hard, that is what it is
tuyo que tú te hayas currado que eso es
complicated and upload it and monetize it, okay
complicado y lo sube y lo monetiza vale
in
em
[Music]
[Música]
the defamation report is a report
el reporte de difamación es un reporte
that you put on YouTube and they block you
que tú le pones a YouTube y te bloquean
the video in the country is worth it But
el vídeo en el país vale Pero
Obviously if they report to you, you
evidentemente si a ti te reportan Tú
You respond by arguing and showing the
respondes alegando y enseñando las
proof that what you are saying is true
pruebas de lo que estás diciendo verdad
and you answer No at the moment in which
y y contestas No en el momento en el que
Juanjo put me or rather Juanjo has put him
Juanjo me puso o sea Juanjo le ha puesto
That report, for example, on the fly is worth it.
ese reporte por ejemplo al vuelo vale es
a habitual thing in him is censorship
una cosa habitual en él la censura no
and when it comes to
e cuando lo de
Tania when what about Tania eh Juanjo
Tania cuando lo de Tania eh Juanjo le
explained to Tania how to put that
explicó a Tania cómo poner ese
report not what Remen did to Antonia
reporte no lo que remen le hizo Antonia
David is not another type of report, okay?
David no es es otro tipo de reporte vale
that he recently discovered he put it to
que él descubrió hace poco se lo puso al
flight and what it does is put that report
vuelo y lo que hace es poner ese reporte
so that this appears on the screen
para que en la pantalla aparezca Este
video has been reported for defamation AND
vídeo ha sido reportado por difamación Y
then he Johan flat Tania and all
entonces él Johan plana Tania y todos
those affected do not
los afectados no
He and all those affected began to
él y todos los afectados se pusieron a
to say that YouTube had taken action
decir que YouTube había tomado medidas
It is worth it when a person makes a
Vale cuando una persona hace una
we all see the barbarity
barbaridad lo vemos todos
Okay, he started saying that YouTube had
vale se puso a decir que YouTube había
taken measures they began to say that
tomado medidas se pusieron a decir que
YouTube was starting to take action
YouTube estaba empezando a tomar medidas
and that precautionary measures were going to be requested
y que se iban a pedir medidas cautelares
Ok, Juanjo made this video.
vale el Juanjo hizo este vídeo
uncle first measures of the case
tío primeras medidas del caso
Tania, the person who had met me
Tania persona que había quedado conmigo
in which each one on his own I am
en que cada uno por su lado me estoy
Me fighting with Tania because Tania has
peleando Yo con Tania porque Tania tiene
your channel dedicated to me dedicated to
su canal dedicado a mí dedicado a
me and also
mí y también se
get into something that is not even worth it
mete vale se mete en una cosa que ni
Even I had to see why
siquiera yo tenía que ver porque lo de
the husband's sentence of not so much
la sentencia del marido de tan no lo
I took it out, they took it out on Twitter under
saqué yo lo sacaron en Twitter bajo
movements that Tania herself made
movimientos que hizo la propia Tania de
give no clues and that Tania had
dar pistas no y que la Tania lo había
published on their networks no Well then
publicado en sus redes no Bueno pues
Juanjo also got involved in this
esto Juanjo también se metió para
defend of course the other party
defender por supuesto a a la contraparte
no first measures of the Tania case
no primeras medidas del caso Tania la
things get very
cosa se pone muy
It would be I don't know what day this came up.
seria yo no sé a qué día subió Este
video but at the moment that I that I
vídeo pero en el momento que yo que yo
I appealed because I think he didn't know that
apel porque yo creo que él no sabía que
This could also be appealed in the
eso se podía apelar también en el
The moment I appealed, YouTube took it away from me.
momento que apele YouTube me quitó el el
report
reporte
Why don't you delete this video Juanjo in
Por qué no borras Este vídeo Juanjo en
the one who starts inventing laws and
el que te pones a inventarte leyes y las
blocks like you
cuadras como a ti te
It seems pitiful this, this gives
apetece lamentable esto esto da
Shame on you, man. Look at Johan Plana.
vergüenza tío mira con el Johan plana es
very beastly what is happening in
muy bestia lo que está sucediendo en
YouTube and example of evil people
YouTube y ejemplo de la gente malvada
Johan plans that there is camping YouTube it
Johan plana que hay campando YouTube lo
I explain in this thread and share the video
explico en este hilo y Comparto el vídeo
from Juanjo who explains very well the
de Juanjo que explica muy bien las
legal implications what a shame what
implicaciones legales qué vergüenza qué
shameful
vergüencita
eh what a shame this eh what a shame
eh qué verg esta eh qué verguen
Uncle also got involved in Tania's thing
tío también se metió en lo de la Tania
when YouTube returned the video to me yes
cuando YouTube me devolvió el vídeo sí
who said something because of course
que dijo algo porque é por supuesto
You also know that YouTube gave me back the
también sabe que YouTube me devolvió el
video when a person makes a
vídeo cuando una persona hace una
barbarity we all see it We don't need
barbaridad lo vemos todos No necesitamos
that he tells us or notifies us
que nos lo diga o nos notifique la
platform when a person makes a
plataforma cuando una persona hace una
barbarity we all see it We don't need
barbaridad lo vemos todos No necesitamos
Whether the platform says it or not, then
que lo diga o no la plataforma Entonces
Guajo why when you put the
guajo por qué cuando pusisteis el
report you put in all your
reporte pusisteis en todas vuestras
accounts that YouTube had taken action on
cuentas que YouTube había tomado medida
if we don't need it, don't say it
si no necesitamos que no lo diga la
platform Then we need it that
plataforma Entonces lo necesitamos que
tell us
nos lo diga la
platform the platform gives more entity
plataforma la plataforma da más entidad
or it does not give more entity because the platform
o no da más entidad porque la plataforma
when I win the report what he did
cuando yo gane el reporte lo que hizo
it was eh
fue eh
give me back the video
devolverme el vídeo
Ju therefore who applauds in the air of
Ju por lo tanto quien aplaude al aire de
that has taken away something who knows how who
que ha quitado algo a saber cómo quien
He who applauds the air applauds
aplaude al aire quien aplaude al
air that has removed something to know
aire de que ha quitado algo a saber
how appealing Juanjo for example
cómo apelando Juanjo por ejemplo
teaching the public articles of the Pania
enseñando los artículos públicos pania
that this was a public issue teaching
de que eso era un tema público enseñando
the sentence that it is a real issue
la sentencia de que es un tema real
teaching the media
enseñando los medios de comunicación
talking about that topic for example
hablando ese tema por ejemplo
Juanjo, I repeat it to you again.
Juanjo te lo vuelvo a repetir
censor and you'll get away with it
sensurar y te saldrás con la tuya con
Twitter users with small channels and so on
twitteros con canales pequeños y demás
You're not going to get away with it with me
conmigo no te vas a salir con la tuya
Champion, I swallowed a lot after those
campeón mucho tragué Después de esas
threats no longer no longer at the moment If the
amenazas ya no ya no de momento Si la
people want it because that is what the people decide
gente quiere porque eso lo decide la
People, the game over is going to stay the same.
gente el game over se va a quedar igual
that has been left on other occasions and
que se ha quedado en otras ocasiones e
Game over is going to stay If people
el game over se va a quedar Si la gente
wants because here what rules is the
quiere porque aquí lo que manda es la
people and at the moment In this live I am
gente y de momento En este directo estoy
showing that you are
demostrando que estás
obsessed the problem is yours but the one who
obseso el problema es suyo pero el que
The last one to laugh is the one who laughs best, always.
rí el último es el que ríe mejor siempre
V He who laughs last is the one who laughs
V El que ríe el último es el que ríe
better always clear here to me
mejor siempre claro aquí a mí me
It shows several things, of course.
demuestra varias cosas claro eh
And how is it that he who laughs last laughs?
e Cómo que el que rí el último ríe
better what am I doing?
mejor qué te estoy
doing to you what am I doing to you
haciendo A ti qué te estoy haciendo
Juanjo, of course, when you say this,
Juanjo claro cuando tú dices esto de
He who laughs last laughs best when
quién ríe el último ríe mejor es cuando
you have a war with someone and
tú tienes una guerra con alguien y
Someone has struck or will strike later.
Alguien ha dado un golpe o luego lo da
the other one doesn't
el otro no
family, that is, he considers that he is in
familia o sea él considera que está en
a war
una guerra
with me, whoever laughs last laughs best
conmigo quien ríe el último ríe mejor
because they have taken away the the the from me
porque me han quitado el el el
report what war you have with me
reporte qué guerra tienes tú conmigo
Juanjo What was I doing to you?
Juanjo Yo qué te estaba haciendo Contigo
was not going to
no iba la
thing like
cosa cómo
because they have taken away my
porque me han quitado el
report who laughs last laughs best
reporte quien ríe el último ríe mejor
What a shame Juanjo, what a shame
qué vergüenza Juanjo qué vergüenza
Juanjo what
Juanjo qué
Shame has brought you together with Loli Huerta
vergüenza te ha juntado con Loli Huerta
Juanjo 5 euros counts as Loli Huerta
Juanjo 5 eur cuenta como Loli Huerta
Now Juanjo is your donor
ahora es tu donadora Juanjo
I don't know which of the two it is
no sé por parte de cuál de los dos es
more humiliating if on her part
más humillante si por parte de ella
because you are a hater of Antonio David
porque tú eres hater de Antonio David
flowers or from you who are a
flores o por parte tuya que eres un
channel
canal
white a point of the
blanco un punto del
objective and that's why he starts talking about
objetivo y por eso comienza hablando de
This leaves me a little freaked out about colors
esto me queda un poco flipando colores
of the Circus eh Of course they have
del Circo eh Por supuesto que se han
past all the limits you can imagine
pasado todos los límites tú imaginaos
that I would have done that eh when I
que yo hubiese hecho eso eh cuando me
They began to attack after having made their
empezaban a atacar haber hecho sus
diets this is very common in him my
dietos esto es muy habitual en él mis
attacks when they attacked me Juan Juan
ataques cuando me atacaron Juan Juan
past 3
pasado 3
years Juan Juan past 3 years nobody you
años Juan Juan pasado 3 años nadie te
Nobody runs into you anymore because you remember what you're doing.
ataca Ya nadie te topa por lo recuerdas
like a battle of a
como una batalla de un
Grandpa like me is that no no no not so right
abuelo como yo es que no no no tan razón
And surely both parts are
Y seguramente eh las dos partes si se
both parties denounce that they end
denuncian las dos partes acaben
both of them are damned with two balls
condenadas con dos [__] las dos
parties if they are reported end up convicted
partes si se denuncian acaben condenadas
surely eh
seguramente eh
Surely Juanjo believes that both
seguramente Juanjo cree que las dos
if the parties report it, they end up condemned
partes si se denuncian acaban condenadas
between Loli Huertas and the other side
entre Loli huertas y el otro bando la
another part point number one why
otra parte punto número uno por qué
You are commenting on this If you have nothing
estás comentando esto Si no tienes nada
what to see if your channel is not about
que ver si tu canal no trata de
youtubers know what Juanjo has done in
youtubers sabé lo que ha hecho Juanjo en
the last times that he has not
los últimos tiempos que no le ha
Juanjo has come out in recent times
salido Juanjo en los últimos tiempos se
He started trying to convince Loli to
puso a intentar convencer a a Loli de
that it was clear that she had to talk
que claro de que ella tenía que hablar
We are going to see that now, for the voucher
de eso lo vamos a ver ahora el por vale
that she stopped answering that
de que ella que dejara de contestar que
would stop making gossip and dedicate himself to
dejara de hacer salseo que se dedicara a
the kitchen to Peppa who would talk about great
la cocina a Peppa que hablara de gran
brother do you know that why Because the
hermano sabéis eso por qué Porque el
I gossip about the bun contained to me and
chismorreo el moño contenido para mí y
we doubled and tripled the audience
le doblamos triplicamos la audiencia
when we are making a bun, he
cuando estamos nosotros haciendo moñe él
believe that if yes we
cree que si si nos
dedicate it to him that we arrive we premiere the
dedicárselo que lleguemos estrenamos el
updated game over
game over actualizado
Okay, and see you there.
vale Y nos vemos allí
Now I wanted to ask you if this is
Ahora yo quería preguntaros si esto es
normal
normal
okay well as if something of what we have
vale bueno como si algo de lo que hemos
seen tonight out normal Not me
visto esta noche fuera normal No yo
I want to ask you if this is normal if
quiero preguntaros si esto es normal si
You see, they are days with different clothes, eh or
veis son días con distintas ropas eh o
be this belongs to several days okay
sea esto pertenece a varios días vale
People who are paying have told me okay
gente que está pagando me han dicho vale
Let's see what they told you, be careful, it's going on
a ver qué te han dicho ojo que se está
paying celebrities three figures that are
pagando a famosos tres cifras que se
is paying celebrities which seems very
está pagando a famosos que me parece muy
Of course I think it's a lie and people
claro yo creo que es mentira y a gente
that collaborates two figures t and people who
que colabora dos cifras t y a gente que
collaborates two figures Ah you have found out You
colabora dos cifras Ah te ha enterado Tú
That's what Ju is about, if we pay that for what?
de eso Ju es que si pagamos eso para que
We work here, so if we pay that much
trabajamos aquí es que si pagamos eso
why is he protesting because people are
para que é protesta porque la gente le
pay the workers, don't you think?
pague a trabajadores anda no le parece
Well I work to save and for the
bien yo trabajo para ahorrar y para el
tomorrow not thinking that this can be done
mañana no pensando que esto se puede
end any day is protesting
acabar cualquier día está protestando
who doesn't like people paying rep
que no le gusta que la gente pague rep
breaking it up like it was I don't know
partiéndolo eso como si fuera no sé
Of course Marian, that's what I think.
Claro marián es que es eso yo creo que
People are here to have a good time
la gente está aquí para pasarlo bien de
heart I for example marug Of course
corazón Yo por ejemplo marug Claro que
He could ask me for money to enter but it is
me podía pedir dinero por entrar pero es
that people are very bad and they have told me
que la gente es muy mala y me han dicho
that this other day is worth the people is very
que esto otro día vale la gente es muy
bad that there are other channels that are
mala que hay otros canales que están
paying money see I don't understand
pagando dinero ver yo no entiendo
also no and they have leaked me How much
también no y me han filtrado Cuánto
They pay them money and everything and I've stayed
dinero les pagan y todo y me he quedado
like my god of my life or rather like
en plan madre mía de mi vida o sea a lo
It's better to lie, logically there's no need to
mejor es mentira lógicamente no hay que
believe that they have leaked to him how much
creerlo que le han filtrado a él cuánto
pay the
paga la
people walk what they tell you No but as
gente anda lo que te dice No pero como
If they continue paying the famous people who
como sigan pagando a los famosos que
If celebrities keep paying, what's going on?
como sigan pagando los famosos Qué pasa
down and such people will not want
abajo y tal la gente no va a querer
come free then for us Ah what
venir gratis luego para nosotros Ah que
What if we continue paying celebrities?
que si le seguimos pagando a los famosos
people are not going to want to go for free with him
la gente no va a querer ir gratis con él
wow, they are angry under because it is clear
vaya está enfadados bajo porquees claro
guests who know that you don't pay here
invitados que saben que aquí no se paga
clear
claro
Well, that's why they don't go.
vaya será por eso por lo que no van
with you guo because you don't pay cone in a
contigo guo porque no pagas cono en un
business for everyone in the end the channel is
negocio para todos al final el canal se
It may fall because this is worth it another day
puede caer porque esto otro día vale
Here you have other clothes, it is worth paying or
aquí tiene otra otra ropa vale pagando o
giving him a proportion of the benefits of the
dándole proporción de los beneficios del
Channel that is being carried out right now
Canal eso se está llevando ahora mismo
You often ask me why Noa
muchas veces me preguntáis Por qué Noa
person why not because they already come from
persona por qué no porque ya vienen de
out entx cados of what you pay and me
fuera entx cados de qué te pag y yo
As far as I can I don't want to do that eh
hasta donde pueda no quiero hacer eso eh
Here again he is giving his opinion on whether
aquí otra vez está opinando sobre si
they pay or not
pagan o no
they pay
pagan
Okay, I don't want to do this, this has to be done.
vale No quiero hacer esto esto tiene que
being a family channel that has always been the
ser un canal familiar que siempre fue la
idea I had has to be a channel
idea que tenía tiene que ser un canal
family and family channels not
familiar y los canales familiares no
Vale and company pay and we can't
pagan Vale y de compañía y no podemos
disorient us from that and I perfectly
desorientarnos de eso y yo perfectamente
It could also bring stars and evil
podría también traer estrellas y mal de
God but Juanjo could have many
Dios pero Juanjo Podría tener muchas
stars Okay but he doesn't do it because he doesn't
estrellas Vale pero no lo hace porque no
He wants the same as Feijo, he doesn't govern
quiere igual que feijo no gobierna
because he doesn't want to, okay Juanjo, no no
porque no quiere vale el Juanjo no no
He wears stars because he doesn't want to
lleva estrellas porque no quiere
then you create another problem you create the
entonces creas Otro problema creas el
dependency problem of these
problema de dependencia de de estas de
If you get rid of the people, of course you create a problem.
fuera la gente claro creas un problema
of dependency the problem of
de dependencia el problema de
dependence on Javi oliveira that has
dependencia de Javi oliveira ese te ha
it didn't matter eh Javi Juanjo Look almost you
dado igual eh Javi Juanjo Mira casi te
We call Javi your illusion the problem of
llamos Javi tu ilusión el problema de
dependence you have on Javi Oliveira
dependencia que tienes con Javi oliveira
You don't care about that one, you haven't cared about that one
ese te da igual de ese no te has
tried
intentado
forget but you care a lot that I
olvidar pero te importa mucho que yo
pay or not pay the people who
pague o no pague a la gente que
work Look, I'll give you my opinion
trabaja Mira te voy a dar mi opinión
about this live everything is worth this is you
sobre este directo vale todo esto es tú
giving an opinion on whether people are paid
opinando sobre si se paga la gente que
collaborate if the famous people are paid the good
colabora si se paga lo famosos el buen
roll that the internet is creating me
rollo que se está creando internet yo
disgust I have never encouraged or cont
asco Yo nunca he incentivado n cont
because it is a fact to expose that I said that what
porque hecho es exponer dije que lo que
which state in the long run is to put ourselves
qui estado a la larga es ponernos
Mission time slots that do not
franjas horarias de Misión que no
we can when we want to control the
podamos cuando queramos controlar los
content that we are going to upload today by
contenidos que vayamos a subir hoy por
Example Quiz: A decree for YouTubers
ejemplo Quiz un decreto a los youtubers
Well, in all these live shows, there are several.
en bueno todos estos directos hay varios
that are on the FJ Channel there is better
que están en el Canal de FJ hay más vale
They are giving their opinion on whether I have to pay
son opinando sobre si yo tengo que pagar
or not paying okay and this is what he did
o no pagar vale e esto lo ha hecho
also
también
Here people who are paying have told me
aquí gente que está pagando me han dicho
Okay, as if it were, I don't know. It's clear.
vale que como si fuera no sé Claro es
What is that, I think people are
que es eso yo creo que la gente está
here to have a good time from the heart
aquí para pasarlo bien de corazón por
example people are very bad yal but no
ejemplo la gente es muy mala yal pero no
I know if it's true or maybe just
sé si es verdad o a lo mejor simplemente
They do it to piss me off, they do it
lo hacen para para picarme que lo hacen
to piss him off, you know, or so? And why?
para picarle a él sabes o sea Y por qué
tea
te
It seems that they might do it for
pica que a lo mejor lo hacen para
to bite him or he considers that
picarle a él o sea él considera que que
I paid a worker to chop him up
yo le pague a un trabajador es picarlo a
Juanjo How important are you?
él Juanjo Qué importancia tienes tú
creature in no one's life
criatura en la vida de nadie de
YouTube for the only people of
YouTube para las únicas personas de
YouTube that you have something important is
YouTube que tienes algo importancia es
for the climb for the aggressive giving of
para la trepa para el agresivo dar de
Troy is worth your white and family channel
Troya vale tu canal blanco y familiar
has as a collaborator ard de Troya
tiene como colaborador a ard de Troya
Hey, maybe you don't have one.
que Oye a lo mejor no tiene una
sentence for the right to honor not it
sentencia por derecho al honor no lo
We know but Ard of Troy is a person
sabemos pero ard de Troya es una persona
who defends not only the husband of
que defiende ya no solo al marido de
Tania like you but also to to to
Tania como tú sino también al al al
Carlota Prado's abuser who Carlota
abusador de Carlota Prado que Carlota
Prado is a case that you have defended
Prado es un caso que tú has defendido
Very much. Well, your collaborator.
muchísimo Bueno pues tu colaborador
defends the abuser says that that
defiende al abusador dice que esa
The sentence is unfair to the kid.
sentencia es injusta para el chaval vale
eh ard Troy is a person who does not
eh ard Troya es una persona que no
He just insults a lot more than me
solamente insulta muchísimo más que yo
but he says that Smurfette should be
sino que dice que a pitufa habría que
split his mouth and burst it open
partirle la boca y reventar seela hasta
that blood
que sangre
em the only ones who care about you in
em a los únicos que le importas en
YouTube is a Troy to climb and to
YouTube es a ard Troya a la trepa y a
all these that are approaching you
todos estos que se te están arrimando
but not because they like you or they like you
pero no porque les gustes o les caigas
well or whatever they are only interested
bien o lo que sea solamente se interesan
for you pay attention to this because this this You
por ti atento a esto porque esto esto Te
It's going to hurt because
va a doler por
me for me and they are fighting among themselves
mí por mí y están entre ellos peleándose
let's see who gets more
a ver quién se queda con más mas
dudes, I don't care about you at all
panas a mí no me importas absolutamente
Nothing Juanjo, if you hadn't mentioned me
nada Juanjo si no me hubieras mencionado
In two years, as we agreed, I would not be here.
en dos años como acordamos yo no estaría
doing this live and tonight I don't know
haciendo este directo y esta noche no se
I would publish the game over that people
publicaría el game over que la gente
He is already asking for 26 out of 50, I don't like it
está pidiendo ya van 26 de 50 a mí no me
you matter I am in
importas Yo estoy en
another on a different wavelength than yours no
otro en otra onda diferente a la tuya no
we have nothing to
tenemos nada que
go ok we are not competition you are
ve vale no somos competencia tú eres
my competition He considers you are
competencia mía Te considera estás
fighting with me in some way
luchando conmigo de alguna manera
imaginary But I don't care I don't
imaginaria Pero a mí no me importa yo no
I pay the workers for
le pago a los trabajadores para
annoy you
fastidiarte a ti
You don't matter Juano But what do you care?
tú no importas Juano Pero a ti qué te
It doesn't matter what I pay the
importa lo que yo le pague a los
collaborators, who cares?
colaboradores a ti quién te importa
whoever comes here that's it
quien venga aquí eso es lo
First, what do you care who comes?
primero Qué te importa quién venga
here what do you
aquí Qué te
matters things that are happening to me and
importa cosas que me están pasando y
I think that's the end of the active way.
creo que que se acabó manera activa ia
the ballast we release depending on whether
el lastre que soltemos dependiendo de si
One day he made a moderator and
un día ha hecho un moderador y de
suddenly This is the pathetic live that
repente Este es el directo patético que
did the other day okay eh vertical here
hizo el otro día vale eh vertical aquí
You can see the number These are the ones that
podéis ver la cifra Estas son las que
are ok I did a live because it had been
son vale hice un directo porque se había
taken for granted because I had said
dado por aludido porque yo había dicho
one fool plus another fool is two fools
un tonto más otro Tonto son dos tontos
I made no allusion to him and it was given
no hice ninguna alusión a él y se dio
by alluded to because I said one more fool
por aludido porque dije un tonto más
another Fool are two fools look alike
otro Tonto son dos tontos parecen en
another channel Or suddenly if we take a look
otro canal O de repente si echamos una
collaborator and suddenly another channel I know
colaboradora y de repente otro canal sé
that life does not mean that we take collaborators
que la vida nu que cogemos colaboradores
yours what you
suyos qué os
It seems like other people's food is not
parece es como la comida de los demás no
I know that eh we create content
sé que eh nosotros creamos contenido
They create content and the rest go
ellos crean contenido y los demás van
like in our slipstream but we are going to
como a rebufo nuestro pero que vamos a
slipstream from him from this creature to see
rebufo de él de esta criatura a ver
you after the night we had
ustedes después de la noche que llevamos
seeing the things we are seeing what
viendo las cosas que estamos viendo qué
Does it seem like magic to you? Listening to this doesn't seem like magic.
os parece Escuchar esto no parecen magia
or cinema
o cine
that is, after the night we had
o sea después de la noche que llevamos
listening to him talk about me for two
escuchándolo hablar de mí durante dos
years that I already tell you that this is not even
años que ya os digo yo que esto no es ni
This will be a
Esto será un
5% obviously
5% evidentemente
Okay, this will be 5% obviously. These
vale Esto será un 5% evidentemente Estos
These are things that people have been passing on to me
son cosas que la gente me ha ido pasando
that by chance they have been seeing this one
que de casualidad han ido viendo é este
day I was expected to open the 5
día se esperaba que yo abriera los 5
minutes answering him now yes yes
minutos contestándole ahora sí que sí
Javi is going to answer me Juanjo I found out
Javi me va a contestar Juanjo me enteré
In two days, uncle, I won't see you.
a los dos días tío no te topo
Juanjo, I can't place you on the map.
Juanjo no te sitúo en el mapa
I'm probably going to put you in tonight
seguramente esta noche te voy a poner en
he
el
map I've probably put on you tonight
mapa seguramente esta noche te he puesto
A little bit on the map I have your clips
un poquito en el mapa tengo clip tuyos
also here where you recognize that
también por aquí donde tú reconoces que
I give you notoriety
yo te doy notoriedad
Juanjo no one will bump into you Juanjo your
Juanjo no te topa nadie Juanjo tus
numbers are these Look
números son estos Mira
King, this is going to be the topic that suits you the most.
Rey este va a ser el tema que más te va
because this is the reason
porque este es el motivo
look this is cool Juanjo from why you
mira este es moo Juanjo del por qué Tú
You've been mentioning a channel to me for 2 years.
llevas 2s años mencionándome un canal
with 600 thousand odd
con 600 y pico mil
subscribers
suscriptores
1000 Anarchy Catches The Anarchy Catches
1000 anarquía coge Las capturas anarquía
anarchy that The captures are not worth the
anarquía que Las capturas no valen a los
10 minutes of me starting directly Okay
10 minutos de yo empezar directo Vale
that's like when you compare the
que eso es como cuando comparas la
the coincidence of Broncano and and
franja la coincidencia de broncano y y
Pablo Moto, okay, he's a brawler.
Pablo moto vale que es que broncano
He's been at it for a while now, huh?
lleva ya un ratito ant empeado eh
13 hours 13 hours 18000 visits
13 horas 13 horas 18000 visitas
15000 7 hours 8 hours Here I had one
15000 7 horas 8 horas Aquí llevaba una
hour most uploaded 200000 19000 These are
hora más subido 200000 19000 Estos son
captures eh These are official data
capturas eh Estos son datos oficiales
This is a live of yours 973 the peak of
esto es un directo tuyo 973 el pico de
That night or afternoon, whatever it was, is worth it here
esa noche o tarde lo que fuera vale aquí
being micaa and we talked mica with 2500 Y
estando micaa y hablamos mica con 2500 Y
you at the same time with
tú a la vez con
100 telesalseo with 2200
100 telesalseo con 2200
1500 this is after you go to the Canal
1500 esto es luego que te vas al Canal
secondary to do live now for what
secundario hacer directos ahora por lo
seen 900 users and because I think that
visto 900 usuarios y porque creo que
you had the geeks there who picks up
tenías a los friky allí quién recoge
collaborators no
colaboradores no
and you can get away with 2000, you'll be fine with 496
e te des alceo con 2000 vale tú con 496
Juanjo but I assure you that that night
Juanjo pero te aseguro que esa noche
You were the most watched channel in Asturias.
Fuiste tú el canal más visto de asturia
Okay, don't take it the wrong way.
vale No te no te lo tomes a mal
eh 7 hours of climbing eh 7 hours later
eh 7 horas de subida eh 7 horas después
to broadcast telegossip 9 hours after
de emitir telesalseo 9 horas después de
broadcast you are worth you with 13,000 telesalseo
emitir tú vale tú con 13000 telesalseo
14 telesalseo has 180,000 subscribers
14 telesalseo tiene 180.000 suscriptores
yours is your channel
el tuyo es tu canal
major
principal
main if we talk about my channel
principal si hablamos de mi canal
[Music]
[Música]
Juanjo de la's target is already
ya objetivo Juanjo de la
night objective we are on our way to
noche objetivo nosotros vamos camino de
meet the second goal of 50 Juanjo
cumplir el segundo objetivo de 50 Juanjo
the second objective of
el segundo objetivo de
50 live telesalseo with 2000
50 telesalseo en directo con 2000
Users reacting to a clip of Ana
usuarios reaccionando a un clip de Ana
Gossip there with your heart 990
Cotilla tú ahí con tu corazón 990
user these are real screenshots eh
usuario esto son capturas reales eh
1000 100 10000 you while mik is
1000 100 10000 tú mientras que mik está
with almost
con casi
100300 this when you fought last week
100300 esto cuando te peleaste la semana
past with Mica with Carmen a kiss to me
pasada con Mica con Carmen un beso a mi
Carmen, here everyone is in charge.
Carmen que aquí todo el mundo se manda
kiss I send you kiss
beso yo te mando beso
Carmen Carmen
Carmen Carmen
Carmen is going to polish you
te Carmen te va pulejo
Carmen was 76 while you were 3
Carmen tenía 76 mientras que tú tenías 3
Juanjo 300 takes a breath
cu coge aire Juanjo 300
34 Carmen has 10,000 subscribers you
34 Carmen tiene 10,000 suscriptores tú
have
tienes
600,000 alive or not
600.000 vivos o no
Okay
vale
1000 1500 telesalseo
1000 1500 telesalseo
you 10000
tú 10000
1900 telesauce watching heart eh or whatever
1900 telesalseo viendo corazón eh o sea
We are looking here at Yuji 100 you
estamos viendo aquí lo de yuji 100 tú
with your
con tus
vertical 1000 100300 telesauce with
verticales 1000 100300 telesalseo con
Marine
Marina
1700 and so it goes down telesalseo goes
1700 y así va bajando telesalseo va
rising during the passing of the
subiendo durante va pasando la
night you go down because when the
noche tú vas bajando porque cuando la
people realize that we are in
gente se da cuenta que estamos en
directly we are going to get into you
directo nosotros se te va meterte en
those
esos
topics Well now we are going to comment It is that
temas Bueno ahora vamos comentar Es que
This is already boring, isn't it? I mean, you want to
esto ya es aburrirnos no O sea quieres
more data than the data itself
más datos que ya lo de los datos no Para
what is absurd look here okay eh
qué es absurdo mira aquí vale eh
Trium 3600 you 1700 I wasn't there Ah
trium 3600 tú 1700 yo no estaba Ah
no good good is that here you are not Nor
no bueno bueno es que aquí no eres Ni
Here you are not even the second, you are the
aquí no eres ni el segundo eres el
third Because look there is Mica and there is and
tercero Porque mira está Mica y está y
There is Trium and you are the last one, so that means
está trium y tú el último vale o sea que
It is absurd to compare these things
es absurdo comparar estas cosas
Ok, it's absurd to compare these things.
vale es absurdo comparar estas cosas
Okay
vale
Regarding the topic of verticals
em respeto al tema de los verticales
Juanjo
Juanjo
Look, I love Oscar because he knows how
Mira Óscar me encanta porque sabe cómo
turn everything around to see This is
darle la vuelta a todo a ver Esto es
When people blame you for
cuando la gente te echa en cara que las
visits from the verticals are false that
visitas de los verticales son falsas que
You know that they are visits like
tú lo sabes que son visitas como de
people who don't look for you and who don't enter
gente que no te busca y que no entra en
your channel's visits from the verticals
tu canal las visitas de los verticales
It works like TikTok, they are people who go
funciona como tikt son gente que van
going through like this and that's why suddenly Tania
pasando así y por eso De repente Tania
in a live stream it had 110,000 views, worth it
en un directo tuvo 110,000 visitas vale
That's why I guano from time to time.
por eso guano de vez en cuando pues
has 40,000 views in a live stream because
tiene 40,000 visitas en un directo pues
They are vertical ones of these horrible ones that I
son verticales de estos horribles que yo
I don't put this to my audience or
no le pongo esto a mi audiencia ni de
Joke to falsify the social Blade is worth it
coña para falsear el social Blade vale
Well then look what he says about
Bueno pues Mirad lo que él dice sobre
I've said it a thousand times about verticals, eh?
los verticales lo he dicho mil veces eh
The vertical audience shape is
la forma de audiencia del vertical es
different from the horizontal the form of
distinto al horizontal la forma de
audience is different man clabo as
audiencia es distinta hombre clabo como
Those who have not come to see you are passing by and
que no han entrado a verte van pasando y
count each one who enters and leaves, enters and
cuenta cada uno que entra y sale entra y
leaves, does not stay
sale no se queda
and it is a way of measuring completely
y es una forma de medir totalmente
different because it recommends a Niche
distinta porque te recomienda un Nicho
from your segment and Ah recommends you a
de tu segmento y Ah te recomienda un
Niche of your segment then recommends
Nicho de tu segmento luego recomienda
people who have nothing to do with you
gente que no tiene nada que ver con tu
community then what happens from now on
comunidad entonces lo que pase a partir
That's why, as you know, it's crazy here.
de ahí como sabéis es de locos aquí
we have a lot of people doing it right or not
tenemos mucha gente hacer vale o no lo
They can do it or not, they do not recommend it
pueden hacer o no no les recomiendan
There are people who can't do it.
hacerlo hay gente que no lo puede hacer
Only he is worth it because they would lose a lot
solo él vale porque perderían mucho
money Okay then that's why I see
dinero Vale entonces yo por eso veo
attacks to the vertical that is why you see
ataques al vertical que que por eso ve
vertical attacks
ataques al vertical
Juanjo, here you stand, here you stand
Juanjo aquí tú te pones aquí tú te pones
to hesitate Antonio David uncle you with your
a vacilar Antonio David tío tú con tu
audience with the numbers you have
audiencia con los números que tienes a
hesitate Antonio David who has 4000 or
vacilar Antonio David que tiene 4000 o
3000 spectators without a title in the
3000 espectadores sin título en los
direct Hash I reveal myself is what
directos Hash yo me revelo es lo que
puts another way that yesterday we did a lot
pone otra manera que ayer hicimos mucha
audience no 140,000 views and others
audiencia no 140,000 visitas y otros
140,000 visits as if they were real
140.000 visitas como si fueran reales
They did a live show until 3 o'clock
hicieron un directo Hasta las 3 de la
morning and they only took out 57,000 when it ended
mañana y solo sacaron 57000 cuando acab
and he starts messing with Antonio David
y se pone a meter con con Antonio David
because he counted less and
porque le contabilizó menos y
Okay, I don't feel well, Juan Juan David
vale que no siento bien Juan juon David
you don't run into us is that none of us run into you
no te topa es que no te topamos ninguno
Juanjo, we don't care if you have
Juanjo que nos da igual como si tienes
500,000 which is that we don't put you in
500.000 que es que no no te ponemos en
the map Juanjo is that you do not
el mapa Juanjo es que no te
We located Good but don't flip out they are very
ubicamos Bueno pero no flipas están muy
pay attention to those crazy, crazy things
pendiente de esas cosas flipas flipasas
You are very aware of these things, aren't you?
Estás muy pendiente de estas cosas no
So Juanjo, when you say this,
entonces Juanjo tú cuando dices esto el
another day thanks because yesterday of the
otro día las gracias porque ayer de del
heart we were again in the first
corazón volvimos a ser en las primeras
hours this is every morning so
horas esto es todas las mañanas por lo
seen okay or every night when he
visto vale o todas las noches cuando él
make direct worth every day is the
haga directo vale todos los días es el
most viewed most viewed in
más visto el más visto en
visualizations in visualizations or in
visualizaciones en visualizaciones o en
what the serer that day or in hats
lo que el serer ese día o en sombreros
Okay, that's what matters. There are people who
vale es lo que importa hay gente que se
what matters in visualizations
qué es lo que importa en visualizaciones
what is it
qué es lo que
matters revels in the golden minutes and there are
importa regodea los minutos de oro y hay
people who revel in the minutes of
gente que se regodea de los minutos de
gold and we won by 6000 by 8000
oro y nosotros ganamos por 6000 por 8000
visits and we earn by 6000 8000
visitas y nosotros ganamos por 6000 8000
visits that I don't know where he has seen that
visitas que no sé dónde ha visto él eso
Every morning waking up and seeing the
cada mañana despertarse y ver la
difference in data each morning
diferencia de datos cada mañana
wake up and see the difference in data
despertarse y ver la diferencia de datos
with respect to competition is with
con respo a la competencia es con
Regarding the competition Juanjo you
respecto a la competencia Juanjo te
you get up every morning and write
levantas todas las mañanas y escribes
Javi Oliveira in the
Javi oliveira en el
search engine seems healthy to you, I ask now
buscador te parece sano pregunto ya
were part of everything we are
fuera parte de todo lo que estamos
watching tonight seems healthy to you
viendo esta noche te parece sano
Do you think it's healthy to get up every morning?
te parece sano levantarte todas las
mornings and Search my name I ask
mañanas y Buscar mi nombre pregunto
because here you are recognizing it
porque aquí lo estás reconociendo tú
Here you are recognizing it
Aquí lo estás reconociendo
you are worth it
tú vale
And yesterday we were the healthiest live here.
e Ayer fuimos el directo más sano aquí
Here this day was not the most seen but
aquí este día no fue el más visto pero
Well it was the healthiest air yesterday was the
bueno fue el más sano aer ayer fuos el
direct healthier Well, well, always
directo más sano Pues bueno pues siempre
more something there is or more something healthier to
más algo hay o sea más algo más sano a
[ __ ] it up the ass okay eh
tomar por culo vale eh
Juanjo How come there are people? Or rather, how come
Juanjo Cómo que hay gente O sea cómo que
The important thing is the
lo importante son las
visits visits count
visitas las visitas cuentan los
unique viewers That is, if you go
espectadores únicos O sea si tú vas
swiping your finger like that and someone falls into your
pasando así el dedo y alguien cae en tu
direct and passes it in half a second
directo y lo pasa al medio segundo
tell how what matters is your
cuenta cómo que lo que importa son tus
visits of the verticals and not the minute
visitas de los verticales y no el minuto
of gold if you said this the other day
de de oro si tú dijiste esto el otro día
About the social being, Juanjo, I'll tell you.
del ser social Juanjo ya te lo digo yo
Oh well, how many unique viewers?
Ah bueno ya Cuántos espectadores únicos
have seen this unique viewers is
han visto esto espectadores únicos es
people who have watched at least one minute of the
gente que ha visto al menos un minuto el
program unique viewers are people
programa espectadores únicos son gente
who have seen at least one minute of the
que han visto al menos un minuto el
program that is useless that
programa que eso no sirve para nada que
That's no good, you can't eat that.
eso no sirve para nada no se come de eso
you don't eat that
no se come de eso
Juano, just like you, doesn't eat from the
Juano igual que tú no comes de los
vertical because they are fake visits
verticales porque son visitas falsas
more than 142,000 views live
más de 142,000 visitas en el directo
main V is that it is a
principal V es que o sea es un
nonsense is worth it because SEP catches you and
sinsentido vale porque SEP te coge y
when people face the best
cuando la gente le echan cara a lo mejor
our objectives something of
los objetivos nuestros alguna cosa de
that says I want to feed my
esa dice yo quiero dar de comer a mi
family does not work for free but if you do
familia no trabajar gratis pero si si te
you make them vertical than what you
pones a ser verticales que lo que te
It's not about the money, so be clear.
importa no es el dinero o sea aclárate
Okay
vale
No, and I'm also in a very calm period.
no y además estoy una época muy calmada
of my life in which I don't look at the data
de mi vida en la que no miro los datos
I am in a very calm time of my life
estoy en una época muy calmada de mi
life in which I don't look at the data But if
vida en la que no miro los datos Pero si
You wake up every morning and look at the
te levantas cada mañana y miras los
data maybe you don't look at yours AND
datos a lo mejor no miras los tuyos Y
look at mine alone
mira los míos solo
no maybe it's not true no look at the
no a lo mejor no es verdad no Mira los
data that I want to enjoy
datos que quiero disfrutar de los
content and that you are enjoying
contenidos y que estás disfrutando de
the contents of mine not of the content
los contenidos del mío no del contenido
mine you are enjoying no
mío estás disfrutando no
and Juanjo's objectives
e objetivos Juanjo
objectives, okay, I repeat, we have already met them
objetivos vale repito ya Hemos cumplido
tonight 1 of 50 we are about to
esta noche 1 de 50 estamos a punto de
to complete the second of 50 we are missing 15 and
cumplir el segundo de 50 nos faltan 15 y
We go to the right and see the gameover
nos vamos a la right y vemos el gameover
and out okay eh the updated gameover
y fuera vale eh el gameover actualizado
and
e
Juanjo, you asked for 20 super colored chats.
Juanjo pediste 20 super chat de color
teal in exchange for signing up for the
verde azulado a cambio de apuntarme al
gym and go
gimnasio e ir
and
e
go eye eh e
ir ojo eh e
go for the next one set another goal and
ir para la próxima pong otro objetivo y
Put and
Pon y
[Laughs]
[Risas]
train
entrenar
zero of
cero de
10 objective no
10 objetivo no
reached you set a goal of 15 and
alcanzado pusiste un objetivo de 15 y
you achieved
lograste
zero because they're not even seeing you oo
cero por no te están viendo siquiera oo
is that they are not even you
es que no te están ni
listening target for a hole
escuchando objetivo para un agujero
zero dependent you didn't arrive either
dependiente cero tampoco llegaste
Guajo you asked people to go in
guajo le pediste a la gente que fuera en
Bison, you achieved your goal today.
bison el objetivo este día conseguiste
three out of 10 today the obo the objective of the
tres de 10 hoy el obo el objetivo del
We didn't like the challenge, but the objective
reto no nos ha gustado eh el objetivo
They didn't like it that day. We were already very
ese día no les gustó no Ya fuimos muy
fast and such but not today's live
rápidos y tal pero hoy no el directo
morning come in if not yes yes did not like it
matinal paséis sino sí sí no gustó
No
no
Juanjo no
Juanjo no
you fulfilled neither
cumpliste ni
This five is a challenge of
este cinco un reto de
five you got two super chat
cinco conseguiste dos super chat
Juanjo two of
Juanjo dos de
five the objective if you met it
cinco el objetivo si lo cumplías
you told five jokes
contabas cinco chistes
spicy everything has to be spicy in
picantes todo tiene que ser picante en
your life You always have to put the
tu vida Siempre tienes que meter la
chili pepper in
guindilla en
all what spicy jokes target
todo qué objetivo chiste picantes
kids But how not
chavales Pero cómo no lo
got done neither was it fulfilled okay
consiguió hecho tampoco se cumplió vale
This goal was Good here is this photo
Este objetivo fue Bueno aquí esta foto
that when they send it to me it is left with a
que cuando me la mandan le queda un
53 minutes left to complete the objective that
minuto 53 para que acabe el objetivo que
you also did not meet that objective
tampoco cumpliste era un objetivo de
five out of five Juanjo out of five
cinco de cinco Juanjo de cinco
you got zero out of five at the time
conseguiste cero de cinco en el momento
that you fulfilled they told me that in the
que cumpliste me dijeron que en el
moment that passed this minute closed the
momento que pasó este minuto cerró el
direct without saying
directo sin decir
Goodbye, the challenge is worth it if I got it, I would read it.
adió vale el reto si lo conseguía leía
something with the vowel
algo con la vocal
but I don't understand why people
a pero yo no entiendo por qué la gente
resisted this goal
se resistió a este objetivo
eh, I don't understand it, but how the
eh es que no lo entiendo pero cómo la
people resist this goal because I
gente se resiste a este objetivo pues yo
I'm going to read something too, eh, I mean, I'm going to
voy a leer algo también eh o sea yo a
See, I'm a little unreliable, eh?
ver yo soy yo voy un poco regulinchi eh
eye eh yes we met the goal of 50
ojo eh yo si cumplimos el objetivo de 50
I'm going to put the game over and Leo gives me
voy a poner el game over y Leo me da
the same with vowels as without vowels
igual con vocales que sin vocales que
with intercalated h's
con h intercaladas
Hey, what are people telling me?
eh que me está diciendo la gente una
which is true the objectives are
cosa que es verdad los objetivos está
working very well. Good [ __ ] great.
funcionando muy bien Bueno de [__] madre
We are destroying, it is breaking
Arrasando vamos se está rompiendo el
YouTube bookmark is coming is coming
marcador de YouTube está vamos está que
you're out you're out Hey let's go
te sales estás Eh vamos
very good but I don't know if people know that
muy bien pero no sé si la gente sabe que
I have a network and that network
yo como tengo una Network Y esa Network
I'm like finishing with her then
estoy como finiquitando con ella pues
now he pays me for 4 months
ahora me paga 4 meses
mother view of
vista madre de
God mother of God And this is the reality
Dios madre de Dios Y esta es la realidad
I mean, I don't care what data you have.
O sea me da igual los datos que tenga
each one because in the end they are
cada uno porque al final son
and in the end they are times, they are seasons
e al final son son épocas son temporadas
Javi pay Carmen double, which is the
Javi a Carmen págale el doble que es la
I'd better put it now, that sounds okay.
mejor voy a poner ya que suene eso vale
the last 14 left and we're leaving
los últimos 14 que quedan y nos vamos
Okay
vale
and in the end I don't like to criticize the subject of
e al final no me gusta criticar tema de
numbers but no but not for nothing javia
números per no pero no por nada javia
Carmen pay him double that is the
Carmen págale el doble que es la
better one
mejor un
I never like the number theme.
beso el tema de número no me gusta nunca
criticizing it is not worth it if in some
criticarlo de nadie vale Si en algún
moment I make some allusion to the subject of
momento hago alguna alusión al tema de
number is because they are doing it on
número es porque la están haciendo sobre
me as is the case no. That is this person
mí como es el caso no O sea esta persona
is recognized by him every day
está todos los días reconocido por él
worth every day every day
vale todos todos todos los días
recognized by him rising by the
reconocido por él levantándose por la
tomorrow to see how much I have had I don't
mañana para ver cuánto he tenido no me
that seems healthy
parece sano eso
family doesn't seem healthy to me
familia no me parece sano
Okay
Vale
so those are the times. Maybe
entonces esos son época A lo mejor de
suddenly next year or next month
repente el año que viene o el mes que
comes a topic that he likes
viene le sale un tema que a él le
It blows me up like Didi's blows me up
revienta como a mí me reventó lo de Didi
Uncle, at Didi's I've had videos of
tío yo en lo de Didi he tenido vídeos de
of 700,000 visits to Daniel's
de 700.000 visitas en lo de Daniel
Sancho I made a great documentary
Sancho hice un pedazo de documental
working juo that had 1,100,000 visits
trabajando juo que tuvo 1,100000 visitas
Ok, but man, what I don't see well
vale pero hombre lo que yo no veo bien
The first thing I don't see well is I don't know
lo primero que yo no veo bien Yo no sé a
You who have appeared live
ustedes que os ha apareció el directo
Tell me your opinion a little bit.
decirme un poco vuestra opinión vale
before we left it doesn't seem to me at all
antes de irnos a mí no me parece ni
It's kind of normal that you end up with a green one
medio normal que tú quedes con una verde
for everyone for a healthy community bowl
para todos por una comunidad sana tazón
of man's deaz bowl making a
de tazón deaz de hombre haciendo una
woman doing cartwheel
voltereta lateral mujer haciendo voleta
lateral to me it doesn't seem
lateral a mí no me parece
eh that's okay ok I'm going to give you 10
eh que esté bien ok os voy a dar 10
minutes to the goal
minutos para el objetivo
Okay, just a second.
Okay un segundito
a
un
secondly, it doesn't seem right to me that a
segundito a mí no me parece bien que una
person
persona
and because of course if you realize one
e porque Claro si os dais cuenta de una
which I think you will have noticed
cosa que creo que sí lo habréis notado
he no he is not saying Well then today
él no él no está diciendo Bueno pues hoy
we have been the ones who have had the most
hemos sido los que hemos tenido más
audience today we have been the ones who have
audiencia hoy hemos sido los que hemos
had more visits no no no
tenido más visitas no no no
He is with Javi but he doesn't have to be with me.
él está con Javi pero no a m a tien que
Look, I've never given super chats but
mira que jamás he dado super chats pero
A Game Over is worth it.
es que un Game Over lo vale cara
Throwing a kiss, I'm glad, Jos Enrique
lanzando un beso me alegro José Enrique
I'm glad, a big kiss, he's Javi Javi
me alegro un beso enorme él es Javi Javi
Javi Javi uncle
Javi Javi tío
eh He's not even close The one with the most
eh No es ni por asomo El que tiene más
audience is neither among the first nor
audiencia ni de los primeros no es ni
by far the one with the largest audience
por asomo El que tiene más audiencia
but it's not even the first one, dude. I mean
pero es que ni de los primeros tío O sea
The thing is that it depends on the season, there are things that
la la cosa Va por época hay cosas que le
They work more to Look at the topic of the
funcionan más a Mira el tema de la
royalty I remember there was a time
realeza me acuerdo que hubo un tiempo
that Diego Arabal swept away his visit and
que Diego arabal arrasó en visita y
each video had two or three videos at a time
tenía cada vídeo dos o tres vídeos al
day with 300,000 600,000 not 200,000
día con 300,000 600.000 no 200.000
24-hour visits, also from Javid's heart
visitas 24 horas corazón también javid
Speaking clearly, it is the one that most sweeps
Hablando claro es el que más arrasa de
visit and that is a reality, that is to say in
visita y eso es una realidad o sea en
matters of the heart I think Javid
temas del corazón Yo creo que javid
Speaking clearly, it is the one that sweeps the most in
Hablando claro es el que más arrasa en
visit and that is so okay and in subject of
visita y eso es así vale e en tema de
straight
directo
Those who have the most are me and the ones who have the most
los que más tienen somos e mik la
first okay Mika doubles us
primera vale Mika nos dobla a nosotros
in live audiences both in
en audiencia de directos tanto en
final visits as in
visitas finales como en en
peaks you understand me
picos me entiendes
em and after mica there is me
em y después de mica estoy yo está
Antonio David and Juanjo is at a point
Antonio David y punto Juanjo está a un
level of a pppa an ar of Troy and things
nivel de una pppa un ar de Troya y cosas
so okay And then in video visits
así vale Y luego en visitas por vídeo
This guy doesn't even reach 10,000 views
este chico no llega ni a 10.000 visitas
by video on the main channel which is
por vídeo en el canal principal que es
Its main channel does not even reach the
su canal principal no llega ni a las
10,000 visits doesn't matter to me I don't wish it
10.000 visitas me da igual No le deseo
I wish good to everyone.
el mal yo le deseo el bien a todo el
real world I mean I don't care
mundo de verdad O sea no me importa a mí
It doesn't take anything away from me what he does
no me quita nada lo que él
have Wait a minute
tenga Espérate un
second we are nowhere to go eh 10 to go
segundo estamos a nada eh Faltan 10 para
overcome the challenge
superar el reto
He's talking to me, Francoa. Wait, here.
me está hablando francoa espérate Toma
my profit sharing face throwing
mi reparto de utilidades cara lanzando
a kiss a kiss
un beso un beso
Look, it's that it doesn't matter to me at all.
vea sea es que a m ni me va ni me vien
the visits that this boy has But
las visitas que tenga este chico Pero
Uncle, you can't be here every day
tío no puedes estar todos los días
trying to belittle
intentando menosprecie
having said is what they are going against
haber dicho es lo que se van en contra
of me
de mí
xa And really and and it seems too much to me
xa Y de verdad y y me parece demasiado
I have dedicated a live broadcast to him, I have.
eh haberle dedicado un directo eh lo he
made in telesalseo because it is that it is that
hecho en telesalseo porque es que es que
have it on my main channel Well the
tenerlo en mi canal principal Pues la
The truth is that I don't think he deserves it or
verdad es que no creo que lo merezca o
it is a it is as if it were Pepa and that
sea es un es como si fuera la [__] y esa
people this no but man eh summary of the
gente este no pero tío eh resumen del
direct I don't know what you have
directo No sé ustedes que os habrá
similar Okay now let's go to Game Over
parecido Vale ahora vamos al Game Over
but summary of the live for me eh
pero resumen del directo para mí eh
a person I don't meet or is
una persona a la que no topo o sea es
that a person that I don't meet at all
que una persona a la que no la topo de
true, I mean, I don't know anything about his life, I don't know
verdad o sea no sé nada de su vida no sé
I don't know anything about your news at all.
nada de sus noticias no sé nada de nada
I will not comment on anything if at some point
de no comento nada si en algún momento
We have mentioned your name because I
hemos mencionado su nombre Porque me lo
you have taken out in the chat because someone
habéis saca en el chat porque alguien me
has asked something because Amador has ha
ha preguntado algo porque Amador ha ha
said something that has come out on TV you know
dicho algo que haya salido la tele sabes
but he has fought with Evita Dynamite me
pero se ha peleado con evita Dinamita me
he sweated it out, he fought with Raquel
la ha sudado se ha peleado con Raquel
Imagine the blood that could have been there
imaginaros la sangre que podía haber
I have actually had a fight with her
hecho yo de eso se ha peleado con la
Olga's sister and Olga's family
hermana de Olga y la familia de Olga
He wants to know nothing about him that I know
quiere saber nada de él que yo lo sé
okay eh he's gotten into I mean you have a
vale eh se ha metido en O sea tienes un
non-aggression pact with me and it has
pacto de no agresión conmigo y se ha
involved in me not defending myself from that
metido en que yo no me defienda de que
They add me, that is, if you have a pact
me agregan a mí o sea si tienes un pacto
with me in which uncle you have each one
conmigo en el que tío tienes cada uno
On the other hand, you have some videos that you
por su lado tienes unos vídeos que te
They leave it in bad shape that they are removed from the
dejan fatal que están quitados del
internet Well then Leon gives him a kiss Leon
internet Bueno pues Leon le un beso Leon
Read tell the truth doc seta tell the truth
Lee di la verdad doc seta di la verdad
He joins Johan Plana and gets to work
Se junta con Johan plana se pone a
defend the half that I have not done
defender a a la miad que no os lo he
position but there is click too
puesto pero hay click también
defending me from his sentence this
defendiendo a mi de su sentencia esta
poor little girl who only uses
chiquilla la pobre que solamente utiliza
I have Twitter to read your sentence
Twitter para leer sus sentencia tengo
more eh I have much more eh if it continues I have
más eh tengo mucho más eh si sigue tengo
much more but not to m a d have to
mucho más pero no a m a d tienen que
member of the three triple channels
miembro de los tres canales triplemente
damned how damned you all are eh
condenada qué condenados estáis todos eh
how damned you all are
qué condenados estáis todos
Hey, man, he's grown a mustache.
eh tío que se ha puesto hasta el bigote
the other day I was looking for one
el otro día que estaba buscando una
excuse to put on a mustache is
excusa para ponerse un bigote es
worrying people come that yes that
preocupante venga gente que ese sí que
It's going to be an interesting Game Over
va a ser un Game Over interesante
Well look, we are only eight away, okay?
Pues mira estamos a ocho solamente vale
we are eight
estamos a ocho
only
solamente
Yes, uncle, he looked for an excuse to put himself
si tío que se buscó una escusa ponerse
a
un
another mustache for the gang of bad guys
bigote otro para la pandilla de malitos
A kiss, Mara Jess, but I don't know who
un beso María Jesús pero no sé a quién
You mean bad man here, no
te refieres con malito hombre aquí no
we have talked about no evil
hemos hablado de ningún malito
condemn me Javi a kiss
condéname Javi un beso
Good core We are missing eight super chats
Core bueno Nos faltan ocho super chat
Okay, I don't know.
vale No sé
what what perfume what perfume is it that I
qué qué perfume qué perfume es el que me
I have to change, okay. But oh well.
tengo que cambiar vale Pero bueno
We will try to find another perfume
intentaremos buscar otro otro perfume
the mustache and the gym are worth the gym
vale el bigote y el gimnasio el gimnasio
It's true, it's true, I hadn't realized
es verdad es verdad no había caído en
That's good but the gym can be
eso S Bueno pero el gimnasio puede ser
plus the gym may be more common
más el gimnasio puede ser más habitual
No
no
that may be more common more
eso puede ser más común más
coincidence by game Let's go then nothing
coincidencia por game Vámonos pues nada
we're going there
nos vamos allá
there are not 3 minutes left
no faltan 3 minutos
Hey, 3 minutes left, I'll be there.
eh faltan 3 minutos voy a estar por allí
I'm not going to do live chat on the
por el chat no voy a hacer directo en la
kids because I'm going to subit tar and
chavalería porque se me va subit tar y
I want to record a video for the main
Quiero grabar un vídeo para el principal
Okay, Aphrodite, yes, yes, we're going, we're going
vale Afrodita Sí sí nos vamos nos vamos
I'm missing, damn, I have six now.
faltan [__] me salen seis ahora
there were less missing
faltaban menos
To you who are missing, damn it doesn't end
a ustedes que faltan [__] no acaba
never the earrings the chain nothing
nunca los pendientes la cadena nada
has a very strange thing with me Now it
tiene una cosa muy rara conmigo Ahora lo
We will remember in the game over Vale
vamos a recordar en el game over Vale
Now we are going to remember that it has one thing
ahora lo vamos a recordar tiene una cosa
very strange with me that I really Ah
muy extraña conmigo que yo de verdad Ah
a fan, a fan, but that's not what he is, man.
un fan un fan pero es que no es eso tío
I mean, he is a fan but it is very strange that
o sea es que es un fan pero muy raro que
He wishes me ill that he is coming closer
me desea el mal que que se va arrimando
and approaching anyone who has
y acercándose a cualquiera que se haya
fought with me
peleado conmigo
Hey, man, capable of defending Tania, man.
eh tío capaz de defender a la Tania tío
to the
a la
Tania the day I least thought it seems with the
Tania el día meos pensaba parece con los
arms full of
brazos llenos de
decal that is very strange uncle are things
calcomanía que es muy raro tío son cosas
very rare but man it's only been two years eh
muy raras pero tío que son dos años eh
That's why you say it's two years. Well.
Por ello son dos años que tú dices Bueno
Well at first you say, Well, we have.
bueno al principio dices tú Bueno Hemos
Once we have reached an agreement, I don't think he wants to.
llegado al acuerdo no creo que quiera
that we fight again, well, not again
que volvamos a pelear bueno no volver
Well, when a couple of weeks pass, no
Bueno cuando pase un par de semanas no
no no no but that's all It's just that it is
no no no pero es que es todo Es que es
even though I have these clicks that I have put
todo y estos clic que os he puesto tengo
many more eh if it continues I have more eh yes
muchos más eh si sigue tengo más eh si
follow I have more this is simply the
sigue tengo más esto es simplemente el
I don't know what you thought of today's live stream
directo de hoy no sé que os ha parecido
but today's live is simply
pero el directo de hoy es simplemente
to give you context of what it is
para para daros contexto de qué es lo
what's happening okay And for someone
que está pasando vale Y para si alguien
It occurs to him to say that this is free
se le ocurre decir que esto es gratuito
I'm not saying he should keep his mouth shut.
que se calle un poco la boca no digo yo
eh I say eh
eh digo yo eh
have
tienen
that a kiss envy Hey there are five missing What
que un beso envidia Oye faltan cinco Qué
Come on, are we going to leave or are we going to stay with
pasa nos vamos o nos vamos a quedar con
the five of
los cinco de
Courage, four are missing, come on, let's go
coraje cuatro faltan venga Vámonos
Hey, thank you all so much for the
Oye Muchísimas gracias a todos por la
number of members Thank you very much
cantidad de miembros Muchísimas gracias
To all of you who have turned I don't know if you
a todos que habéis cumplido No sé si os
you have noticed okay
habéis dado cuenta vale
and I don't know if you have noticed that
e no sé si os habéis dado cuenta de que
You are the best community in the world
sois la mejor comunidad del mundo
Thank you always for not abandoning me
Gracias siempre por por no abandonarme
for not letting go of my hand for being
por no soltarme la mano por estar
always supporting me is okay
siempre apoyándome vale
[Music]
[Música]
in
em
and I don't know if you have noticed
y y que no sé si os habéis dado cuenta
but what is it that we have come to that
pero que que es que Hemos llegado a que
you are about to turn three missing
estáis a punto de cumplir faltan tres
two are missing two one is missing one you have
dos faltan dos uno falta uno habéis
fulfilled two challenges two objectives of
cumplido dos dos retos dos objetivos de
50 each listen to me very important
50 cada uno escucharme muy importante
worth the 3000 people here
vale a las 3000 personas que hay aquí
very important it is worth if a Peta every
muy importante vale si una Peta cada
Spanish but not to m a d they have to night
españ pero no a m a d tienen que noche
anti-obsessed has cures if you let it
anti obsesionados tiene curas si se lo
They propose Yes, for example, not to look at me
Proponen Sí por ejemplo no mirarme por
example not watching my live streams would be a
ejemplo no mirar mis directos sería una
good idea eh guys important okay
buena idea eh chicos importante vale
Now when the ra comes out there are two missing
Ahora cuando salga la ra faltan dos
super chats and we'll leave when the time comes out
super chats y nos vamos cuando salga la
ra on screen Now when I click on it
ra en pantalla Ahora cuando yo le de a
close so you know you are threatened Yes
cerrar que sepas que estás amenazado Sí
Yes, they are already putting it on for me here.
sí si ya me la están poniendo por aquí
who is saying that he is going to put many
que está diciendo que va a poner muchos
strike and that will file many lawsuits
strike y que va a poner muchas demandas
Well then go and explain to him what you
Bueno pues ve y explícale a lo que tú te
you have dedicated for two years and demand
has dedicado durante dos años y demanda
because I made a live broadcast saying
porque te he hecho un directo diciendo
what you have said is very important
lo que tú has dicho urre muchísimas
thanks you just turned the others
gracias acabáis de cumplir los otros
Von updated with quality and
Von actualizado con la calidad y
truths like fists pun Thanks for
verdades como puños pun Gracias por
so much entertainment let's go
tanto entretenimiento vámonos para
There you go, guys. Now when it appears to you that
allá chicos Ahora cuando os aparezca que
I close the live broadcast and Bot will appear.
cierro el directo os va aparecer Bot
you are all condemned to go to the Game
toos condenados para iros al al Game
Over vale Hit the button now
Over vale Dale dale al botón ahora de
Go to the main channel, guys, see you.
iros al Canal principal chicos nos vemos
Tomorrow Thank you very much handsome I love you
mañana Muchas gracias guapos os quiero
a lot of stop stop already stop already
muchísimo parar parar ya parar ya que
We have arrived that you are having a great time
Hemos llegado que lo estáis pasando que
you are getting over it by throwing a kiss
lo estáis sobre pasando lanzando un beso
stop stop stop stop giving super
parar parar parar parar de dar super
chat talk if you want there in the
chat hablar si queréis allí en el
main now okay guys see you
principal ahora vale chicos nos vemos
There OK See you on the channel
allí Vale Nos vemos en el canal
main now you will get the ra if
principal ahora os va a salir la ra si
you don't fall automatically you press the button
no cais automáticamente le dais al botón
Okay, let's go guys, stop, stop, stop.
vale vamos chicos par par par parar
Please stop with the Super chat, okay?
porfa par parar con Los Super chat vale
let's go there let's go there okay
vámonos para allá vámonos para allá vale
And thank you very much for stopping by.
Y muchas gracias de verdad parar par
stop that we have already
parar que ya Hemos
arrived hands clapping hands
llegado manos aplaudiendo manos
clapping hands
aplaudiendo manos
clapping Let's go, we'll miss it
aplaudiendo Vámonos que nos lo perdemos
d The Super chat there if you want in the
d Los Super chat allí si queréis en el
premiere
estreno